<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.confluence"
  version="2.1.0"
  name="Confluence"
  provider-name="Jezz_X, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="ca">Aparença Confluence, per Jezz_X. (Aparença per defecte de l'XBMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Confluence skin by Jezz_X. (XBMC's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Confluence skin por Jezz_X. (skin por defecto)</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Confluence-ulkoasu Jezz_X:ltä. (XBMC:n oletus ulkoasu)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Skin Confluence par Jezz_X. (skin par défaut)</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Confluence arculat. Készítő: Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Confluence 스킨 Jezz_X 만듬 (기본 스킨)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Confluence skin door Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Confluence autorstwa Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema Confluence desenvolvido por Jezz_X. (Tema padrão do XBMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Costum Confluence de Jezz_X. (costum implicit)</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Confluence-skalet av Jezz_X. (XBMC standardskal)s</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Jezz_X开发的Confluence皮肤</summary>
    <description lang="ca">Confluence és l'aparença per defecte de l'XBMC 9.11 i superior. És una combinació de conceptes de moltes aparences populars, i intenta adoptar i integrar les seves bones idees en una aparença que sigui senzilla d'entendre i utilitzar per els nous usuaris d'XBMC.</description>
    <description lang="en">Confluence is the default skin for XBMC 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time XBMC users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="es">Confluence es la skin por defecto de XBMC 9.11 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchas skins populares, e intenta abarcare e integrar lo mejor de ellas en una skin que sea sencilla de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de XBMC.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Confluence on oletus ulkoasu XBMC:n versiosta 9.11 lähtien. Se on yhdistelmä useiden suosittujen ulkoasujen konsepteista, ja yritys omaksua ja integroida heidän hyvät ideat ulkoasuun, jonka pitäisi olla helppokäyttöinen ja -tajuinen kaikille XBMC:n käyttäjille.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Confluence est le skin par défaut de XBMC 9.11 ou supérieur. C'est un condensé d'idées de plusieurs skins populaires. Il tente d'englober et intégrer toutes les bonnes idées que n'importe quel débutant sur XBMC pourrait utiliser avec facilité.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Confluence az alapértelmezett arculat az XBMC-hez a 9.11-es verziótól kezdődően. Merít sok sok népszerű arculat elképzeléséből, megpróbálva vegyíteni a jó ötleteket úgy, hogy az könnyen kezelhető legyen az XBMC-vel először találkozóknak is.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Confluence 는 XBMC 9.11 이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Confluence is de standaard skin voor XBMC 9.11 en hoger. Het combineert de concepten van andere populaire skins, waarbij het tracht hun goede ideëen te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Confluence jest domyślną skórą dla XBMC 9.11 i nowszych. To kombinacja wielu popularnych pomysłów i próba zawarcia tego co w nich najlepsze w skórze, która będzie łatwa do opanowania dla początkującego użytkownika.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O tema Confluence é o tema padrão do XBMC 9.11 e superior. É uma mistura de conceitos de muitos temas populares e tenta integrar as boas ideias destes num tema que deve ser fácil de entender e manusear para utilizadores recentes do XBMC.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Confluence este costumul implicit pentru XBMC 9.11 și versiunile ulterioare. Este o combinație de concepte împrumutate de la mai multe costume populare, care încearcă să îmbrățișeze și să integreze ideile lor bune într-un costum care să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit de către utilizatorii XBMC începători.</description>
    <description lang="zh">在XBMC 9.11之后的版本中Confluence是默认皮肤。它集合了许多流行皮肤的创意，力求把这些优点融合到一个皮肤中，使得首次使用XBMC的用户能更容易上手。</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">Confluence és l'aparença per defecte de l'XBMC, la seva eliminació pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Confluence is the default skin for XBMC, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">Confluence est le skin par défaut de XBMC, l'effacer peut créer des dysfonctionnements</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">A Confluence az alapértelmezett XBMC arculat. Annak eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">Confluence는 XBMC의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 야기될수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Confluence is de standaard XMBC skin, het verwijderen van Confluence kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">Confluence jest domyślną skórą XBMC. Jej usunięcie może powodować problemy.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">O tema Confluence é o tema padrão do XBMC. Removê-lo pode causar problemas. A sério! Deixe-o instalado, mesmo que não o use.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ro">Confluence este costumul implicit pentru XBMC, dacă îl eliminați pot apărea probleme!</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="se">Confluence är standardskalet för XBMC 9.11 och över. Det är en kombination av koncept från många populära skal och försöker fånga och integrera alla goda ideer i ett skal som ska vara enkelt att förstå och använda för förstagångsanvändaren av XBMC.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">Confluence是XMBC的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
