<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.allmusic.com"
       name="AllMusic"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper"
             library="allmusic.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <minversion>20000</minversion>
    <summary>AllMusic Scraper</summary>
    <description>Use AllMusic.com to fill your libray metadata information.
The allmusic website was created in 1995 as a place for music fans to indulge their passion.
The AMG editorial staff, along with hundreds of expert contributors (all music fanatics in their own right), has made allmusic the most comprehensive music reference source on the planet. They are all dedicated to creating and maintaining the knowledgeable, spirited content that music lovers and industry professionals have come to expect from AMG.
All genres and styles of music are covered here, ranging from the most commercially popular to the most obscure. We critique albums and artists within the context of their own genres - from opera to garage rock to traditional country. This ensures that fans of any style of music can depend on us to keep them up-to-date with their favorite artists as well as introduce them to new sounds.</description>
   <description lang="nl">Gebruik AllMusic.com om de metadata van jouw collectie op te halen.
  De AllMusic website is ontstaan in 1995 als webstek voor echte muziekfans.
The AMG redactie, samen met honderden bijdragende experen (allen muziekfans in hun eigen gebied), hebben van allmusic het meest complete muziek naslagwerk gemaakt op deze planeet.
Alle genres en stijlen worden gedekt, gaande van de meest commerciele tot de meest alternatieve. We bekritiseren albums en artiesten in hun eigen genre, van opera tot garagerock tot traditionele country. Dit maakt dat fans van elke muziekstijl bij ons terecht kunnen voor de laatste informatie rond hun favoriete artiesten of om nieuwe muziek te leren ontdekken.</description>
    <supportedcontent>
      <content>albums</content>
      <content>artists</content>
    </supportedcontent>
  </extension>
</addon>
