<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.artists.universal"
       name="Universal Artist Scraper"
       version="3.6.0"
       provider-name="Olympia, XBMC Foundation">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.3.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="2.0.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.8.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.artists"
             language="en"
             library="artistuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Universal Skraper vir Kunstenaars</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">ماسحة الفنان العالمية</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник за информация за артисти</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador universal per artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro umělce</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Crafwr Cyffredinol ar gyfer Artistiaid</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Universel Scraper til Kunstnere</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Universeller Scraper für Interpreten</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Universal Scraper Καλλιτεχνών</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper universal para artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal de Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Universaalne artistide kraabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Universaali artistien tiedonhakija</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecteur universel d'artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur universel pour les artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="he">Universa סקרייפר אמנים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Univerzalni sakupljač informacija izvođača</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Univerzális előadó leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Pengais Universal untuk Artis</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Almenn skafa fyrir Listamenn</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Scraper universale degli artisti</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">汎用アーティストスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Universalus Artistų Scrapers</summary>
    <summary lang="lv">Mākslinieku universālais skrāpis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Pengikis Universal untuk Artis</summary>
    <summary lang="my">အနုပညာရှင်များအတွက် Universal Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Universele scraper voor artiesten</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Universalskraper for artister</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Universal Scraper informacji o artystach muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Colector universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Scraper universal pentru artisti</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Универсальный скрапер для исполнителей</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre umelcov</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Univerzalen ponudnik informacij o izvajalcih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Universiell artistskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">கலைஞர்களின் ஒட்டு மொத்தமான சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Sanatçılar için Evrensel Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Універсальний здирач для виконавців</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu Nghệ sĩ từ nhiều nguồn</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">通用艺术家信息刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">通用演出者訊息搜括器</summary>
    <description lang="af">Hierdie skraper versamel informasie van die volgende ondersteunde werwe: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com, terwyl kunswerke gryp van: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifike informasie wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvanklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval die allmusic skakel nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde van allmusic.com nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
    <description lang="ar">هذه الماسحة تجمع المعلومات من المواقع المدعومة التالية: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, في حين تأخذ عناوين الأعمال الفنية من: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. يمكن أن ترتب حقل تلو حقل حسب الموقع الذي تريد منه تلك المعلومة المحددة.&#10;&#10;البحث الابتدائي يتم دائما على ميوزك برينز. في حال أن رابط كل الموسيقى غير مضاف على حقول موقع ميوزك برينز من allmusic.com لا يمكن الحصول عليها(على الرغم من سهولة إضافة هذه الروابط المفقودة).</description>
    <description lang="be">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не е налична препратка към allmusic.com на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com става невъзможно (добавянето на препратка е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs suportats</description>
    <description lang="cs">Tento zdroj dat získává informace z následujících podporovaných stránek: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Lze nastavit jakou informaci stahovat z jakých stránek.&#10;&#10;Základní hledání je vždy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že schází odkaz allmusic na stránce MusicBrains, nelze stáhnout informace z allmusic.com (avšak je velmi snadné chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="cy">Mae'r crafwr yn casglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, a allmusic.com, tra'n cipio gwaith celf o: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Mae modd ei osod fesul maes i ddewis pa wefan i gasglu gwybodaeth benodol.&#10;&#10;Bydd y chwilio cychwynnol yn cael ei wneud ar MusicBrainz. Rhag ofn nad yw dolen allmusic wedi ei osod ar wefan MusicBrainz nid oes modd estyn meysydd o allmusic.com (mae'n hawdd gosod y dolenni coll hynny).</description>
    <description lang="da">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, fra hvilke sider du ønsker, at få de pågældende informationer fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic linket er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de. Es werden dabei Grafiken von den folgenden Seiten geladen: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Von welcher Seite die Informationen geladen werden, kann einzeln konfiguriert werden.⏎ &#10;⏎&#10;Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm και allmusic.com, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
    <description lang="en">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras que obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="et">See kraabits kogub infot järgmistelt lehtedelt: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm ja allmusic.com, pilte: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Saad välja kaupa määrata, milliselt lehelt mis infot soovid.&#10;&#10;Esmane otsing tehakse alati saidilt MusicBrainz. Kui MusicBrainz lehele pole allmusic  linki lisatud, siis allmusic.com lehelt sisu hankida ei saa (puuduvaid linke saad ise lihtsalt lisada).</description>
    <description lang="fi">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic-linkkiä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle allmusic.com-osoitteessa, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur répertorie les informations des sites suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, Last.fm et allmusic.com tout en assemblant les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez définir la source d'information pour chaque champ.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite à partir de MusicBrainz. xxxxxxxx (en attente du retour de l'équipe Kodi) xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur recueille des informations depuis les sites pris en charge suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm et allmusic.com, alors qu'il récupère les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Il est possible de configurer champ par champ depuis quel site l'information doit être récupérée.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite sur MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où les liens allmusic ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site de MusicBrainz, les champs provenant de allmusic.com ne peuvent pas être récupérés (il est par contre très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="gl">Este scraper recolle información dos seguintes sitios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, mentres que, obtén as imaxes de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir en cada campo o sitio de onde quere obter a información.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial é feita sempre no MusicBrainz, no caso de que a ligazón a allmusic non se teña engadido nos campos do sítio MusicBrainz dende allmusic.com, non se poderán obter (aínda que, é moi doado engadir as ligazóns que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="he">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
    <description lang="hr">Ovaj sakupljač prikuplja informacije sa sljedećih podržanih stranica: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm i allmusic.com, dok preuzima omote filmova sa: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Može poredati popis stranica iz kojih želite sakupiti informacije jednu iza druge.\n&#10;\n&#10;Pretraga uvijek započinje na MusicBrainzu. U slučaju da allmusic poveznica nije dodana na MusicBrainz stranicu, polja sa allmusic.com ne mogu se nabaviti (ali je vrlo jednostavno moguće dodati te nedostajuće poveznice).</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a leolvasó a következő weboldalakról gyűjti be az adatokat:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm és allmusic.com, míg képeket a következő oldalakról gyűjt: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm és allmusic.com. Egyenként beállítható, hogy az adott mezőt melyik weboldalról töltse fel⏎ ⏎ A kiinduló keresés mindig a MusicBrainz. Amennyiben az allmusic utalás nincs hozzáadva MusicBrainz oldalhoz, a mezők nem tölthetők le az allmusic.com oldalról (a hiányzó utalások hozzáadása azonban nagyon egyszerű).</description>
    <description lang="id">Pengais ini mengambil informasi dari berbagai situs yang mendukung: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm dan allmusic.com, sembari mengambil artwork dari: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com. last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ini dapat diatur perbagian dari situ mana informasi tertentu akan diambil.&#10;&#10;Pencarian awal akan dilakukan di MusicBrainz. Apabila tautan dari allmusic belum ditambahkan di situs MusicBrainz, bagian dari allmusic.com tidak dapat ditarik (Namun sangatlah mudah menambahkan tautan tersebut).</description>
    <description lang="is">Þessi skafa safnar sama upplýsingum frá eftirfarandi studdum stöðum: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og á meðan nær hún í myndir frá: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Hægt er að stilla reit fyrir reit hvaðan upplýsingarnar koma.&#10;&#10;Leitin byrjar alltaf á MusicBrainz. Ef allmusic tenglar eru ekki á MusicBrainz veitunni, næst ekki í upplýsingarnar frá allmusic.com (mjög auðvelt að bæta tenglunum við samt).</description>
    <description lang="it">Lo scraper colleziona informazioni da questi siti supportati: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, e allmusic.com, mentre ottiene le grafiche da: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Può essere impostato campo per campo da quale sito vuoi la specifica informazione.&#10;&#10;La ricerca iniziale è sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. Nel caso che il link allmusic non è stato aggiunto al campo del sito MusicBrainz da allmusic.com; non possono essere ottenute (è comunque veramente facile aggiungere questi link mancanti).</description>
    <description lang="ja">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
    <description lang="ko">이 자료수집기는 다음의 사이트에서 정보를 가져옵니다: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com.아트워크는 다음의 사이트에서 가져옵니다: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com. 특정 정보를 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별로 설정할 수 있습니다.&#10;&#10;초기 검색은 항상 MusicBrainz에서 수행합니다. allmusic 링크가 MusicBrainz 사이트의 필드에 추가되어 있지 않은 경우 정보를 가져올 수 없습니다(누락된 링크는 쉽게 추가할 수 있습니다).</description>
    <description lang="lt">Šis Scrapers renka informaciją iš šių palaikomų svetainių: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, ir allmusic.com, ir atsiunčia meno kūrinius iš: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatyti lauko srityje, kurioje svetainėje norite, kad konkrečiu atveju pradinė informacijos pradinis paieška visada bus atlikta remiantis MusicBrainz. Allmusic nuoroda įdėta į MusicBrainz vietoje laukų allmusic.com negali būti (nors tas trūkstamas grandis labai lengva įtraukti).</description>
    <description lang="mk">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="ms">Pengikis ini mendapatkan maklumat dari laman tersokong berikut: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm dan allmusic.com, manakala ia dapatkan kerja seni dari: fanart.tv, htbckdrops.com, last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ia boleh tetapkan medan mengikut medan supaya anda boleh dapatkan maklumat khusus dari laman tertentu.⏎&#10;⏎&#10;Gelintar awalan sentiasa bermula dengan MusicBrainz. Pautan allmusic tidak ditambah ke laman MusicBrainz, medan dari allmusic.com sukar didapati.</description>
    <description lang="my">ဒီ Scraper သည် အချက်အလက်များကို အောက်ဖော်ပြပါ ထောက်ပံ့ထားသော ဆိုဒ်များမှ စုဆောင်းပါသည်။ ထိုဆိုဒ်များမှာ TheAudioDb.com,MusicBrainz,last..fm, နှင့် allmusic.com တို့ဖြစ်သည်။</description>
    <description lang="nl">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde websites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com en tevens pakt hij afbeeldingen van fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Het is mogelijk om per veld aan te geven van welke website je de specifieke informatie wilt halen.&#10;&#10;De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd uitgevoerd op MusicBrainz. Wanneer de allmusic link niet is toegevoegd in de juiste velden op de MusicBrainz website kan de informatie van allmusic.com niet worden opgehaald. (Het is erg makkelijk om deze ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
    <description lang="no">Denne skraperen samler informasjon fra følgende støttede steder: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm og allmusic.com, mens den henter artwork fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan stegvis velge hvilken kilde du ønsker og hente spesifikk informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket er alltid gjort hos MusicBrainz. I tilfeller hvor allmusic-linker ikke er lagt til hos MusicBrainz-siden, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com hentes (det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten ekstraktor pobiera informacje z następujących stron: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane w serwisie MusicBrainz. Gdy wyszukiwanie nie jest wskazane na stronę MusicBrainz, następuje przeszukiwanie serwisu allmusic.com (brakujące linki można łatwo dodać później).</description>
    <description lang="pt">Este colector recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio de onde quer obter as informações. &#10;&#10;A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso um endereço allmusic não tenha sido adicionado no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta).</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="ro">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, și allmusic.com, și opere de artă de la: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm și allmusic.com. Poate fi setat câmp cu câmp de pe care site-ul doriți informații specifice ⏎ ⏎ căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna face pe MusicBrainz.. În cazul în care link-ul Allmusic nu este adăugat la MusicBrainz, allmusic.com nu poate fi folosit (însă este relativ ușor să adăugați aceste link-uri lipsă).</description>
    <description lang="ru">Этот скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm и allmusic.com, при этом получая обложки с: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле может быть настроено для получения определенной информации с желаемого вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Первичный поиск всегда производится на MusicBrainz. Если линк для allmusic не добавлен на сайте MusicBrainz, то поля с allmusic.com не могут быть заполнены (добавить отсутствующие ссылки очень легко).</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera infomácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm a allmusic.com. Grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sl">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm in allmusic.com; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedno na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
    <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm och allmusic.com, medans den samlar konstverk från: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm och allmusic.com. Du kan ange fält för fält från vilken sajt du vill ha den specifika inforamtionen från. Den initiala sökningen är alltid gjord på MusicBrainz. Om inte allmusic.com länken läggs till på MusicBrainz sajten, kan inte fält från allmusic.com hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த சுரண்டியானது TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். திரை குறும்படங்களை fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm மற்றும் allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். ⏎ ⏎ முதன்மை தேடல் எப்போதும் MusicBrainz தான் நடக்கும். allmusic மற்றும் amazon.de சேர்க்கபடாவிட்டால் அவற்றில் இருந்து தகவல்கள் செமிக்கபடமாட்டது (தவறிய இணைப்புகளை சேர்ப்பது மிகவும் எளிது).</description>
    <description lang="uk">Здирач збирає інформацію з наступних сторінок: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm та allmusic.com, тоді як отримує обкладинки з: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm та allmusic.com. Для кожного поля можно вказати з якої сторінки ви бажаєте його заповнити.&#10;&#10;Початковий пошук завжди робиться на MusicBrainz. Якщо посилання з allmusic не додаються на сторінку MusicBrainz, тоді поля з allmusic.com неможливо отримати (однак дуже легко додати ці пропущені посилання).</description>
    <description lang="vi">Trình này thu thập thông tin từ những site được hỗ trợ như: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, và lấy ảnh bìa từ các nguồn: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm và allmusic.com. Bạn có thể tùy chỉnh chọn từng thứ riêng biệt để lấy từ site bạn muốn.\n \n Lần tìm kiếm đầu tiên luôn luôn được sử dụng từ MusicBrainz. Trong trường hợp các link allmusic không có trên MusicBrainz, các trường từ allmusic.com sẽ không thể lấy về được (tuy nhiên rất dễ để tự thêm vào các link này bằng tay).</description>
    <description lang="zh">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm 和 allmusic.com，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm 和 allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从 MusicBrainz 获取，如果 MusicBrainz 网站未加入到 allmusic 的外部链接，则无法获取 allmusic.com 的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">本搜刮器支援從以下網站取得資訊：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm和allmusic.com，並從以下網站取得專輯圖片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm和allmusic.com。您可以指定每一項內容的來源網站。&#10;&#10;初始搜尋結果總是先從MusicBrainz取得，如果MusicBrainz網站未加入到allmusic的外部連結，則無法取得allmusic.com的資訊 (當然您能很輕易地加入遺失的連結)。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=132623</forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>
