<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="screensaver.rsxs.solarwinds"
  version="1.0.0"
  name="Solarwinds"
  provider-name="mogumbo, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.ui.screensaver"
    library_linux="Solarwinds.xbs"
    library_osx="Solarwinds.xbs"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">'n Betoverende deeltjie effek sluimerskerm</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">أداة ساحرة تؤثر بشاشة التوقف</summary>
    <summary lang="be">A mesmerizing particle effects screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Скрийнсейвър с частици, които очароват</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Un estalvi de pantalla amb uns efectes de partícula fascinants</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Spořič obrazovky s fascinujícími částicovými efekty</summary>
    <summary lang="da">En tryllebindende pauseskærm med partikeleffekter</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Ein faszinierender Bildschirmschoner mit Partikeleffekten</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Μία μαγευτική σωματιδιακή προφύλαξη οθόνης</summary>
    <summary lang="en">A mesmerizing particle effects screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Un salvapatallas con unos efectos de partículas fascinantes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Un sorprendente protector de pantalla de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Hüpnotiseeriv osakeste efektiga ekraanisäästja</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Lumoava partikkelitehostenäytönsäästäjä</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Un économiseur envoûtant à effets de particules</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Un hipnotizante gardapantallas con efectos de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="he">שומר מסך מהפנט</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Čuvar zaslona - Očaravajuće kretanje čestica.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Egy igéző részecske-effektus képernyővédő</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Un salvaschermo con effetti particellari ipnotizzanti</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">パーティクルによる幻想的なスクリーンセーバー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">매혹적인 파티클 이펙트 화면보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Itaigus dalelių poveikio ekrano užsklanda</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Een hypnotiserende schermbeveiliging met partikeleffecten</summary>
    <summary lang="no">En hypnotiserende partikkel effekt skjermsparer</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wygaszacz hipnotyzujący efektami cząsteczek</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Protecção de ecrã com um efeito de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Um fascinante screensaver com efeitos de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Un srceensaver cu efecte de particule fascinant</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Завораживающая заставка с эффектами частиц</summary>
    <summary lang="se">En fascinerande skärmsläckare av partikeleffekter</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Fascinujúci šetrič s efektom častíc</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Ohranjevalnik zaslona z učinkom hipnotičnih delčkov</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">En hypnotiserande partikeleffektskärmsläckare</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Заставка із частинок, що має гіпнотизуючий ефект</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">一个迷人的粒子效果屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <description lang="af">Hierdie is 'n uiters betoverende deeltjie effek sluimerskerm. Jy sal vind dat jy 'n ongelooflike aantal verskillende patrone kan bewerkstellig.</description>
    <description lang="ar">أداة ساحرة جدا تؤثر بشاشة التوقف. ستجد أنك تستطيع أن تحقق عدد مذهل من الأنماط المختلفة.</description>
    <description lang="be">This is a very mesmerizing particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="bg">Това е скрийнсейвър, който очарова с частиците си. Ще откриете, че можете да създадете изключително голям брой различни модели.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest és un estalvi de pantalla amb uns efectes de partícules fascinants. Veurà que pot obtenir un nombre increïble de patrons diferents.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Spořič obrazovky s velmi fascinujícími částicovými efekty. Zjistíte, že můžete dosáhnout úžasného množství různých vzorů.</description>
    <description lang="da">Dette er en meget tryllebindende pauseskærm med partikeleffekter. Du vil opdage at man kan opnå et forbløffende antal af forskellige mønstre.</description>
    <description lang="de">Dies ist ein faszinierender Bildschirmschoner mit Partikeleffekten. Du kannst eine verblüffend große Anzahl an verschiedenen Animationen einstellen.</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτή είναι μία μαγευτική σωματιδιακή προφύλαξη οθόνης. Θα διαπιστώσετε ότι μπορείτε να επιτύχετε έναν απίστευτο αριθμό διαφορετικών σχεδίων.</description>
    <description lang="en">This is a very mesmerizing particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="es">Este es un salvapatallas con unos efectos de partículas fascinantes. Verá que puede obtener un número incríble de patrones diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Éste es un sorprendente protector de pantalla de partículas.  Encontrará que puede obtener un gran número de patrones diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="et">See on väga hüpnotiseeriv osakeste efektiga ekraanisäästja. Võimalik on koostada tohutul hulgal erinevaid mustreid.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Erittäin lumoava partikkelitehostenäytönsäästäjä. Tulet huomaamaan uskomattoman määrän erilaisia kuvioita.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Voici un économiseur d'écran à effets de particules particulièrement envoûtant. Vous trouverez qu'il permet d'obtenir un nombre incroyable de modèles et d'effets différents.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Este é un gardapantallas con efectos de partículas moi hipnotizante. Atopará que pode acadar un incrible número de patróns diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="he">זהו שומר מסך מהפנט מאוד. אתה תמצא את עצמך משיג כמויות שונות ומרהיבות של צורות.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Ovo je zaista očaravajuči čuvar zaslona. Moguće je ostvariti zapanjujući broj različitih uzoraka.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez egy lebilincselő hatású részecske-effektus képernyővédő. Hihetetlen mennyiségű különböző minta képes benne kialakulni.</description>
    <description lang="it">Questo è un salvaschermo con effetti particellari è veramente ipnotizzante. E' inoltre possibile ottenere un incredibile numero di differenti schemi.</description>
    <description lang="ja">This is a very mesmerizing particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="ko">매혹적인 파티클 이펙트 화면보호기입니다. 아주 다양한 패턴의 보여줍니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Tai labai itaigus dalelių poveikio ekrano užsklanda. Jūs galite pasiekti nuostabių ivairių modelių nustatymuose. </description>
    <description lang="nl">Dit is een erg hypnotiserende screensaver. Je kunt ongelooflijk veel verschillende patronen bekomen.</description>
    <description lang="no">Dette er en veldig hypnotiserende partikkel effekt skjermsparer. Du får se at der fins en utrolig mengde forskjellige mønster.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Bardzo hipnotyzujący wygaszacz. Przekonaj się, ile niespotykanch wzorów da się osiągnąć.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Protecção de ecrã fantástica com um efeito de partículas. Experimente e verá que obtém um número quase infinito de padrões.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este é um screensaver de partículas com efeitos hipnotizantes. Você vai descobrir que poderá alcançar um incrível número de diferentes padrões.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Acesta este un screensaver cu efecte de particule foarte fascinant. O să vedeți că veți putea obține un număr uimitor de modele diferite.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Завораживающая заставка с эффектами частиц. Для этой заставки на выбор доступно огромное количество вариаций эффектов.</description>
    <description lang="se">Detta är en mycket fascinerande partikeleffektsskärmsläckare. Du kommer att upptäcka att du kan uppnå ett otroligt antal olika mönster.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Toto je veľmi fascinujúci šetrič s efektom častíc. Zistíte, že môžete dosiahnuť neskutočné číslo rôznych vzorov.</description>
    <description lang="sl">To je ohranjevalnik zaslona s presenetiljivim hipnotičnim učinkom delcev. Odkrili boste, da lahko dosežejo neverjetno število različnih vzorcev.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Detta är en väldigt hypnotiserande partikeleffektskärmsläckare. Du kommer att upptäcka att du kan åstadkomma ett häpnadsväckande antal olika mönster.</description>
    <description lang="uk">Це дуже гіпнотизуюча заставка із різноманітних ефектів частинок. Ви побачите надзвичайно велику кількість різноманітних візерунків.</description>
    <description lang="zh">这是一个非常迷人的粒子效果屏幕保护程序。你会发现你能看到惊人数量的不同图案。</description>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

