<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="screensaver.rsxs.solarwinds"
  version="1.0.26"
  name="Solarwinds"
  provider-name="mogumbo, Team-Kodi">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.ui.screensaver"
    library_linux="Solarwinds.xbs"
    library_osx="Solarwinds.xbs"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">'n Betoverende deeltjie effek sluimerskerm</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">أداة ساحرة تؤثر بشاشة التوقف</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Ахоўнік экрану з зачаравальнымі эфэктамі часьціцаў</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Скрийнсейвър от частици, които очароват</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Un estalvi de pantalla amb uns efectes de partícula fascinants</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Spořič obrazovky s fascinujícími částicovými efekty</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Arbedwr sgrin effeithiau gronynnau llesmeiriol</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">En tryllebindende pauseskærm med partikeleffekter</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Ein faszinierender Bildschirmschoner mit Partikeleffekten</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Μία μαγευτική σωματιδιακή προφύλαξη οθόνης</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">A mesmerising particle effects screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">A mesmerising particle effects screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">A mesmerising particle effects screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">A mesmerizing particle effects screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Un protector de pantalla con unos efectos de partículas hipnotizantes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Un salvapantallas con unos efectos de partículas hipnotizantes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Un sorprendente protector de pantalla de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Hüpnotiseeriv osakeste efektiga ekraanisäästja</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">یک محافظ جذاب صفحه نمایش با جلوه های ذرات</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Lumoava partikkelitehostenäytönsäästäjä</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Un économiseur d'écran hypnotisant à effets de particules</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Un économiseur envoûtant à effets de particules</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Un hipnotizante protector de pantalla con efectos de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">שומר מסך עם אפקט חלקיקים מהפנט</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Čuvar zaslona - Očaravajuće kretanje čestica.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Egy igéző részecske-effektus képernyővédő</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Penyelamat layar dengan efek partikel yang mencuri perhatian</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Dáleiðandi skjáhvíla með brellum með agnir</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Un salvaschermo con effetti particellari ipnotizzanti</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">幻想的な粒子エフェクトのスクリーンセーバー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">매혹적인 파티클 이펙트 화면 보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Įtaigaus dalelių poveikio ekrano užsklanda</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Hipnotizējošs daļiņu efekta ekrānsaudzētājs</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Заштита на екран со смирувачки честички</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Penyelamat kesan zarah yang memukau</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">En hypnotiserende skjermsparer med partikkeleffekter</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Een hypnotiserende schermbeveiliging met partikeleffecten</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Wygaszacz hipnotyzujący efektami cząsteczek</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Um protetor de tela hipnotizante com efeitos de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Protector de ecrã com um impressionante efeito de partículas</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Un protector ecran cu efecte de particule fascinant</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Завораживающая заставка с эффектами частиц</summary>
    <summary lang="si_LK">මෝහනය කිරීම් තිරමෙහෙයුම් වෙත ප්‍රයෝගිකව බලපෑම </summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Fascinujúci šetrič s efektom častíc</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Ohranjevalnik zaslona z dih jemajočimi delčki</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Чувар екрана са очаравајућим ефектом честица</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">En hypnotiserande partikeleffektskärmsläckare</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Пардаи экрани аҷоиб бо таъсири зарраҳо</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Büyüleyici bir parçacık efektli ekran koruyucu</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Заставка із частинок, що має гіпнотизуючий ефект</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Một trình bảo vệ màn hình với hiệu ứng thôi miên tạo từ các hạt</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">一个迷人的粒子效果屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">一個令人著迷的粒子效果的螢幕保護程式</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Hierdie is 'n uiters betoverende deeltjie effek sluimerskerm. Jy sal vind dat jy 'n ongelooflike aantal verskillende patrone kan bewerkstellig.</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">أداة ساحرة جدا تؤثر بشاشة التوقف. ستجد أنك تستطيع أن تحقق عدد مذهل من الأنماط المختلفة.</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">This is a very mesmerizing particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Това е скрийнсейвър, който очарова с частиците си. Ще откриете, че можете да създадете изключително голям брой различни модели.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Aquest és un estalvi de pantalla amb uns efectes de partícules fascinants. Veuràs que pot obtenir un nombre increïble de patrons diferents.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Spořič obrazovky s velmi fascinujícími částicovými efekty. Zjistíte, že můžete dosáhnout úžasného množství různých vzorů.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae hwn yn arbedwr sgrin effeithiau gronynnau hynod lesmeiriol. Mae modd cynhyrchu nifer anferthol o batrymau gwahanol.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Dette er en meget tryllebindende pauseskærm med partikeleffekter. Du vil opdage, at man kan opnå et forbløffende antal af forskellige mønstre.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dies ist ein faszinierender Bildschirmschoner mit Partikeleffekten. Du kannst eine verblüffend große Anzahl an verschiedenen Animationen einstellen.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Αυτή είναι μία μαγευτική σωματιδιακή προφύλαξη οθόνης. Θα διαπιστώσετε ότι μπορείτε να επιτύχετε έναν απίστευτο αριθμό διαφορετικών σχεδίων.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">This is a very mesmerising particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This is a very mesmerising particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">This is a very mesmerising particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This is a very mesmerizing particle effects screensaver. You'll find that you can achieve an amazing number of different patterns.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este es un protector de pantalla con unos efectos de partículas hipnotizantes. Descubrirás que puedes obtener un número increíble de patrones diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Este es un salvapantallas con unos efectos de partículas hipnotizantes. Descubrirás que puedes obtener un número increíble de patrones diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Éste es un sorprendente protector de pantalla de partículas.  Encontrará que puede obtener un gran número de patrones diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">See on väga hüpnotiseeriv osakeste efektiga ekraanisäästja. Võimalik on koostada tohutul hulgal erinevaid mustreid.</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">این یک محافظ جذاب صفحه نمایش با جلوه های ذرات است. تعداد پویانماهایی که با این محافظ می توان ساخت بطرز شگفت آوری زیاد است.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Erittäin lumoava partikkelitehostenäytönsäästäjä. Tulet huomaamaan uskomattoman määrän erilaisia kuvioita.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">C'est un économiseur d'écran à effets de particules particulièrement hypnotisant. Il vous permettra d'obtenir un nombre incroyable de modèles différents.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Voici un économiseur d'écran à effets de particules particulièrement envoûtant. Vous trouverez qu'il permet d'obtenir un nombre incroyable de modèles et d'effets différents.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Este é un protector de pantalla con efectos de partículas moi hipnotizante. Atopará que pode acadar un incrible número de patróns diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">זהו שומר מסך עם אפקט חלקיקים מהפנט ביותר. מספר מפתיע של צורות שונות ומרהיבות יתקבלו.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Ovo je zaista očaravajuči čuvar zaslona. Moguće je ostvariti zapanjujući broj različitih uzoraka.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Ez egy lebilincselő hatású részecske-effektus képernyővédő. Hihetetlen mennyiségű különböző minta képes benne kialakulni.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Ini adalah penyelamat layar dengan efek partikel yang sangat mencuri perhatian. Anda akan lihat bahwa Anda bisa mendapat sejumlah yang mengagumkan dari pola yang berbeda.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Þetta er mjög dáleiðandi skjáhvíla með brellum með ögnum. Þú munt komast að því að þú getur fengið ótrúlegan fjölda af mismunandi mynstri.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Questo è un salvaschermo con effetti particellari è veramente ipnotizzante. E' inoltre possibile ottenere un incredibile numero di differenti schemi.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">非常に幻想的な粒子エフェクトのスクリーンセーバーです。驚くほどの様々なパターンを知ることになるでしょう。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">매혹적인 파티클 이펙트 화면보호기입니다. 아주 다양한 패턴의 보여줍니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Tai labai įtaigaus dalelių poveikio ekrano užsklanda. Atrasite, kad galite sukurti neįtikėtina skaičių skirtingų šablonų. </description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Šis ir ļoti valdzinošs daļiņu efekta ekrānsaudzētājs. Jūs redzēsit, ka tas spēj izveidot neticamu skaitu dažādu musturu.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Ова е заштита на екран со смирувачки честички. Ќе откриете дека можете да постигнете зачудувачки шеми.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Ia merupakan penyelamat skrin kesan zarah yang sangat memukau. Anda dapati ia boleh dihasilkan beberapa corak yang sangat mempersonakan.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Dette er en veldig hypnotiserende skjermsparer med partikkeleffekter. Du vil finne ut av at du kan oppnå en utrolig mengde forskjellige mønstre.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Dit is een erg hypnotiserende screensaver. Je kunt ongelooflijk veel verschillende patronen maken.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Bardzo hipnotyzujący wygaszacz. Przekonaj się, ile niespotykanch wzorów da się osiągnąć.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este é um protetor de tela com efeitos de partícula bem hipnotizante. Você verá que pode alcançar um incrível número de diferentes padrões.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Um fantástico protector de ecrã com um impressionante efeito de partículas. Experimente e verá que pode obter um número quase infinito de padrões.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Acesta este un protector ecran cu efecte de particule foarte fascinant. O să vedeți că veți putea obține un număr uimitor de modele diferite.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Завораживающая заставка с эффектами частиц. Для этой заставки на выбор доступно огромное количество вариаций эффектов.</description>
    <description lang="si_LK">මෙම මෝහනය කිරීම් තිරමෙහෙයුම් වෙත ප්‍රයෝගිකව මහත් බලපෑම සහිතයි. පුදුම සහගත විවිධ මෝස්‌තර ප්‍රමාණයක් ඔබට ලබා ගැනීමට හැකි බව ඔබ සොයගනිවී</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Toto je veľmi fascinujúci šetrič s efektom častíc. Zistíte, že môžete dosiahnuť neskutočné číslo rôznych vzorov.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">To je ohranjevalnik zaslona z dih jemajočimi delčki. Odkrili boste, da lahko dosežejo neverjetno število različnih vzorcev.</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Ово је чувар екрана са веома очаравајућим ефектом честица. Можете остварити невероватан број различитих образаца.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Detta är en väldigt hypnotiserande partikeleffektskärmsläckare. Du kommer att upptäcka att du kan åstadkomma ett häpnadsväckande antal olika mönster.</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Ин пардаи экран бо таъсири зарраҳо аҷоиб мебошад. Барои ин парда шумо бисёр таъсирҳои аҷиби нотакрорро пайдо мекунед.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Son derece büyüleyici bir parçacık efektli ekran koruyucu. Birçok değişik şekle ulaşabildiğinizi farkedeceksiniz.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Це дуже гіпнотизуюча заставка із різноманітних ефектів частинок. Ви побачите надзвичайно велику кількість різноманітних візерунків.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Đây là trình bảo vệ có hiệu ứng thôi miên cục kỳ lợi hại. Bạn sẽ thấy sự sáng tạo từ những kiểu kết hợp có thể là không giới hạn</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">这是一个非常迷人的粒子效果屏幕保护程序。你会发现你能看到惊人数量的不同图案。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">這是一個非常令人著迷的粒子效果螢幕保護程式。您會發現可以達到一個另人驚豔的圖形數。</description>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
