<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="visualization.milkdrop"
  version="1.0.27"
  name="MilkDrop"
  provider-name="Team-Kodi">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_windx="MilkDrop_win32dx.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">MilkDrop laat jou sweef deur die klankgolwe wat jy hoor</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">يحلق بك MilkDrop فوق الموجات الصوتية اللتي تسمع</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">"MilkDrop" ще Ви отведе на пътешествие между звуковите вълни, които чувате</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">MilkDrop et porta volant a través de les ones de so que escoltes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">MilkDrop s Vámi proletí skrz zvukové vlny, které slyšíte</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Mae MilkDrop yn eich hedeg drwy'r tannau sain rydych yn eu clywed</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Milkdrop tager dig på en flyvetur gennem lydbølgerne, du lytter til</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">MilkDrop nimmt dich mit auf einen Flug durch deine Musik.</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Το MilkDrop σας ταξιδεύει μέσα στα ηχητικά κύματα που ακούτε</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">MilkDrop takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">MilkDrop the lleva volando a través de las ondas de sonido que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">MilkDrop viib sind lennates läbi kullatavate helilainete</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">MilkDrop lennättää sinut ääniaaltojen läpi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">MilkDrop vous fait voler au travers des ondes sonores que vous entendez</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">MilkDrop vous fait voyager dans les ondes sonores de votre musique</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">MilkDrop lévate voando a través da ondas de son que esta a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">החיזוי MilkDrop לוקח את המאזין לטיסה בין גלי הקול</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">MilkDrop vam omogućuje let kroz zvuk koji čujete</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">A Milkdrop végigrepít a zene hullámain</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">MilkDrop membawa anda terbang melalui gelombang suara yang anda dengarkan</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Með MilkDrop flýgurðu í gegnum hljóðbylgjurnar sem þú heyrir</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">MilkDrop ti fa volare tra le onde sonore di ciò che stai ascoltando</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">MilkDrop - 音楽の波の上を飛ぶ</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">MilkDrop은 사운드웨이브 속으로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여줍니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">MilkDrop nukelia Jus i nuostabu skrydi virs debesu, istiesu fantastisku garsu gausa</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">MilkDrop paņem Jūs līdzi lidojumā cauri skaņu viļņiem, kurus dzirdat</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">MilkDrop ве прелетува преку брановите на музиката која ја слушате</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">MilkDrop memikat pendengaran anda melalui gelombang bunyi yang dihasilkan</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">MilkDrop tar deg med på en flyreise gjennom lydbølgene du hører</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Met MilkDrop vliegt u mee door de geluidsgolven die je hoort</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">MilkDrop zabiera Cię w niesamowity lot w chmurach aktualnie słuchanych dźwięków</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">O MilkDrop leva você para voar nas ondas sonoras que está ouvindo</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">O MilkDrop leva-o num voo através das ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">MilkDrop vă face să zburați printre undele audio pe care le auziți</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Milkdrop отправит вас в полёт через звуковые волны, которые вы слышите</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">MilkDrop s Vami poletí zvukovými vlnami, ktoré počúvate</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">MilkDrop vas popelje skozi zvočne valove, ki jih poslušate</summary>
    <summary lang="sq_AL">MilkDrop të bën të fluturosh nëpër valet të tingullit që e dëgjonë</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Milkdrop för dig flygande genom de ljudvågor du hör.</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">MilkDrop бо мавҷҳои садояш фораму роҳатбахш аст</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">MilkDrop นำคุณโบยบิน ผ่านคลื่นเสียงที่คุณกำลังรับฟัง</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">MilkDrop sizi duymakta olduğunuz ses dalgalarının içine çeker</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">MilkDrop забере вас в політ крізь хвилі музики яку ви слухаєте</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">MilkDrop giúp bạn bay bổng trong âm thanh bạn đang nghe</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">MilkDrop 带你与声波一起飞翔</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">MilkDrop帶您穿越聆聽中的音樂饗宴</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">MilkDrop was oorspronklik 'n musiek visualisering "plug-in" vir die Winamp musiek speler. Soos jy na jou musiek luister, laat MilkDrop jou deur die klankgolwe sweef wat jy hoor, en gebruik klop waarnemings om 'n magdom psigedeliese effekte te aktiveer, en 'n visuele reis deur klank te skep.</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">ميلك دروب كان أصلا عارض موسيقى لمشغل الموسيقى وين امب. عندما تستمع لموسيقاك, كيلك دروب يطير بك خلال موجات صوتية تسمعا حيقيةً, ,و يستخدم كشف الوقع الموسيقي ليؤدي إلى تأثيرات كثيرة, منشئاً رجلة صوت مرئية قيمة.</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">MilkDrop was originally a music visualizer "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Първоначално "MilkDrop" е замислена като приставка за музикалния плеър Winamp. Докато слушате музикалната си колекция "MilkDrop" ще Ви накара да "полетите", измежду звуковите вълни, които чувате. Ползва ритъма за да създаде безброй еуфорични ефекти. Така създава едно богато визуално пътешествие в звука.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">El MilkDrop era originalment un afegitó de visualització musical pel reproductor Winamp. Mentre escoltes la música MilkDrop et porta volant a través de les ones de so que estàs escoltant al moment, i utilitza detecció de tempo per activar una munió d'efectes psicodèlics i crea un enriquidor viatge visual a través del so.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">MikDrop bylo původně vizualizační rozšíření pro přehrávač hudby Winamp. Při poslechu vaší hudby s Vámi MikDrop prolétá skrze zvukové vlny, které slyšíte, a používá detekci taktů, pro spuštění spousty psychedelických efektů, vytvářejíce tak zajímavou vizuální cestu skrze zvuk.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Roedd MilkDrop yn wreiddiol yn "ategyn" delweddu cerddoriaeth ar gyfer Winamp. Wrth i chi wrando ar MilkDrop mae MilkDrop yn eich hedeg drwy'r tonnau sain rydych yn eu clywed gan ddefnyddio canfodydd trawiad i gychwyn effeithiau seicadelig amrywiol gan greu taith weledol cyfoethog drwy'r sain.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Milkdrop var oprindeligt et musikvisualisering "plug-in" til Winamp musikafspilleren. Mens du lytter til din musik, tager Milkdrop dig på en flyvetur gennem de faktiske lydbølger du hører og bruger beat-genkendelse til at udløse en myriade af psykedeliske effekter, der skaber en visuel rejse gennem lyd.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">MilkDrop war ursprünglich ein Musik-Visualizer "Plug-in" für den Musik-Player Winamp.Wenn Sie Ihre Musik hören, fliegen Sie mit MilkDrop durch die aktuellen Klangwellen die Sie hören. Und die Beat-Erkennung wird genutzt um unzählige psychedelische Effekte auslösen, die Schaffung einer visuellen Reise durch den Klang.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το MilkDrop ήταν αρχικά ένα "plug-in" μουσικών οπτικοποιήσεων του Winamp. Καθώς παίζετε τη μουσική σας, το MilkDrop σας ταξιδεύει μέσα στα πραγματικά ηχητικά κύματα που ακούτε, και χρησιμοποιεί ανίχνευση ρυθμού για να ενεργοποιήσει ένα πλήθος ψυχεδελικών εφέ, δημιουργώντας ένα πλούσιο οπτικό ταξίδι μέσα στον ήχο.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">MilkDrop was originally a music visualiser "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger a myriad of psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">MilkDrop was originally a music visualiser "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">MilkDrop was originally a music visualiser "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">MilkDrop was originally a music visualizer "plug-in" to the Winamp music player. As you listen to your music, MilkDrop takes you flying through the actual soundwaves you're hearing, and uses beat detection to trigger myriad psychedelic effects, creating a rich visual journey through sound.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">MilkDrop era originalmente un plug-in visualizador de música para Winamp. Mientras escuchas música, MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando, y utiliza la detección del ritmo para activar una gran cantidad de efectos psicodélicos, creando una rica experiencia visual a través del sonido.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">MilkDrop era originalmente un plug-in visualizador de música para Winamp. Mientras escuchas música, MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando, y utiliza la detección del ritmo para activar una gran cantidad de efectos psicodélicos, creando una rica experiencia visual a través del sonido.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">MilkDrop originalmente fue un "plug-in" visualizador de música para el reproductor de música Winamp. Mientras escuchas tu músuca, MilkDrop te lleva volando a través de las ondas de sonido que estás escuchando en ese momento, y usa detección de ritmo para desencadenar múltiples efectos psicodélicos, creando un rico recorrido visual a través del sonido.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">MilkDrop oli algselt muusika visuaal plugin Winamp'ile. Muusikat kuulates viib MilkDrop sind lennates läbi kuulatavate helilainete. MilkDrop kasutab rütmituvastust, et päästa valla tohutu hulk psühhedeelseid efekte luues visuaalidest rikka teekonna läbi heli.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">MilkDrop oli alunperin Winampin visualisaattorilisäosa. Kuunnellessasi musiikkia MilkDrop lennättää sinut kuulemiesi ääniaaltojen läpi ja käyttää tahdintunnistusta lukemattomien psykedeelisten tehosteiden toistamiseen, luoden visuaalisen matkan musiikin läpi.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">MilkDrop était à l'origine un plugiciel de visualisation musicale pour le lecteur audio Winamp. Alors que vous écoutez votre musique, Milkdrop vous fait voler au travers des ondes sonores, et utilise la détection rythmique pour déclencher une myriade d'effets psychédéliques, créant un voyage visuel et sonore.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">MilkDrop était à l'origine une extension de visualisation musicale pour le lecteur audio Winamp. Pendant que vous écoutez votre musique, Milkdrop vous fait voyager à travers les ondes sonores que vous entendez, détectant le rythme pour déclencher une myriade d'effets psychédéliques, créant ainsi une riche expérience visuelle et sonore.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">MilkDrop foi orixinalmente un plugin de Visualización para múica do reprodutor de música Winamp. Nametres vostede escoita a súa música, MilkDrop lévao voando a través das ondas de son que esta a ouvir, e emprega a detección de ritmo para activar milleiros de efectos psicodélicos, creando unha rica viaxe visual a través do son.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">החיזוי MilkDrop במקור הינו הרחבה לנגן המוזיקה Winamp. בעת האזנה למוזיקה, MilkDrop יקח את המאזין לטיסה בין גלי הקול שנשמעים, וישתמש ביכולת זיהוי קצב מוזיקה להפעלת מספר עצום של אפקטים פסיכדלים, בכך יוצר מסע חזותי עשיר לגלי הקול.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">MilkDrop je orginalno bio zamišljen kao "dodatak" za Winamp glazbeni svirač. Dok slušate svoju glazbu, MilkDrop vam omogućuje let kroz zvuk koji čujete i koristi otkrivanje taktova da bi pokrenuo bezbroj psihodeličnih efekata, tako stvarajući bogato vizualno  zvučno putovanje.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A Milkdrop eredetileg egy beépülőmodul volt a Winamp zenelejátszóhoz. Ahogy hallgatod a zenét, a Milkdrop keresztülrepít a hallható hanghullámokon, felhasználva a dobritmust pszihedelikus effektusok létrehozására gazdag látványvilág megteremtésével.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">MilkDrop awalnya adalah pengaya visualisasi musik untuk Winamp. Sembari mendengarkan musik, MilkDrop akan membawa Anda terbang melalui gelombang suara yang Anda dengarkan, dan menggunakan deteksi ketukan untuk menampikan banyak sekali efek psikedelik, menciptakan suatu perjalanan visual yang kaya melalui suara.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Milkdrop var upprunalega viðbót við Winamp tónlistarspilarann. Þegar þú hlustar á tónlistina, fer Milkdrop með þig á flug í gegnum hljóðbylgjurnar sem þú heyrir og notar taktskynjun til að setja af stað allskonar effekta sem skapa myndrænt ferðalag í gegnum tónlistarupplifunina</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">MilkDrop era, in origine, un "plug-in" di visualizzazione per Winamp. Mentre ascolti la musica, MilkDrop ti fa volare tra le onde sonore di ciò che stai ascoltando usando la rilevazione del ritmo per sincronizzare una miriade di effetti psichedelici, creando un ricco viaggio visuale attraverso il suono.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">MilkDrop は元々 Winamp 音楽プレーヤーのビジュアライザープラグインでした。音楽を再生すると、音楽にあわせた波の上を飛んでいるような視覚効果が現れ、ビート検出により無数のサイケデリックな効果が生まれ、音による視覚的体験を生み出します。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">MilkDrop는 원래 윈앰프의 음악 시각화 플러그인입니다. 음악을 들으면서 사운드 웨이브로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여주며 비트 감지를 해서 다양한 싸이키데릭한 효과를 만들어 풍부한 시각적 경험을 하게합니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">MilkDrop vizualizacija, gauta is Winamp. Klausantis muzikos, MilkDrop nukelia jus i nuostabu skrydi virs debesu, naudojamas ritmo aptikimas, kuris sinchronizuoja muzikos vaizdo efektus.</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">MilkDrop sākotnēji bija mūzikas vizualizācijas "spraudnis" Winamp mūzikas atskaņotājā. Kamēr tu klausies mūziku, MilkDrop paņem tevi līdz lidojumā cauri skaņas viļņiem, kuri skan, un izmanto ritma noteikšanu, lai palaistu myriad psihodēliskos efektus, radot bagātu vizuālo ceļojumu cauri skaņai.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">MilkDrop беше визуализација допонување на Winamp music player. Како што ја слушате музиката, MilkDrop ве прелетува преку актуелните музички бранови, и користи детекција на битот за да покрене myriad психоделични ефекти, креирајќи богато визуелно патување низ звукот.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">MilkDrop pada asalnya adalah pemalam pengvisual untuk pemain muzik Winamp. Ketika anda mendengar muzik, MilkDrop memaparkan gelombang bunyi yang dengari dan guna pengesanan rentak untuk memicu kesan psikedelik tak terkira banyaknya, dan menghasilkan perjalanan visual yang sempurna menerusi bunyi.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">MilkDrop var originalt et visualiseringstillegg til musikkavspilleren Winamp. Mens du lytter til musikken din, tar MilkDrop deg med på en reise gjennom de faktiske lydbølgene du hører. Visualiseringen oppdager takten i musikken og bruker denne for å skape en rik, visuell ferd gjennom utallige, psykedeliske effekter.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Milkdrop was oorspronkelijk een muziekvisualisatieplug-in voor de Winamp-muziekspeler. Terwijl u uw muziek beluistert vliegt Milkdrop u door de soundwaves die u op dat moment hoort. Op basis van de beat produceert het een veelvoud aan psychedelische effecten.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">MilkDrop jest wizualizacją pochodzącą z odtwarzacza Winamp. W czasie słuchania muzyki, MilkDrop zabiera użytkownika w niesamowity lot pomiędzy aktualnie odtwarzanymi falami dźwiękowymi, używając detekcji beatu, która synchronizuje efekty wizualne z muzyką.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">MilkDrop era originalmente uma visualização do reprodutor de música Winamp. Ao ouvir a sua música, o MilkDrop leva-o a voar nas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir, usando detecção de batida para desencadear uma miríade de efeitos psicodélicos. Cria, assim, uma viagem visual inesquecível pelo som.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Originalmente, o MilkDrop era uma visualização do leitor de música Winamp. Ao ouvir a sua música, o MilkDrop leva-o a voar pelas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir, detectando o ritmo da música e desencadeando uma variedade de efeitos psicadélicos. Cria, assim, uma viagem inesquecível pelo som.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">MilkDrop a fost original un „modul” de vizualizare pentru lectorul de muzică Winamp. În timp ce ascultați muzica, MilkDrop vă face să zburați printre undele audio actuale pe care le auziți și folosește detecția bătăii pentru a activa miriada de efecte psihedelice, creând o călătorie vizuală bogată printre sunete.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">MilkDrop изначально был модулем визуализации музыки для проигрывателя Winamp. Когда вы слушаете музыку, MilkDrop создает визуальное ощущение полёта по звуковым волнам, а также использует обнаружение ритма для активации множества психоделических эффектов.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">MilkDrop bol pôvodne hudobným vizualizačným rozšírením Winamp prehrávača. Pri počúvaní hudby s Vami MilkDrop letí zvukovými vlnami, ktoré počúvate a použitím detekcie rytmu spúšťa nespočetné psychodelické efekty, a vytvára bohatú vizuálnu cestu zvukom.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">MilkDrop je bila prvotno vizualizacija za predvajalnik Winamp. Ko poslušate vašo glasbo, vas MilkDrop popelje skozi dejansko valovanje, ki ga slišite, in uporablja zaznavanje ritma, kar omogoči psihedelični efekt in bogato vizualno izkušnjo predvajanja glasbe.</description>
    <description lang="sq_AL">Milkrop fillimisht ishte një "plug-in" për vizualizimin e muzikës për riprodhuesin Winamp. Ndërsa dëgjonë muzikën tënde, Milkdrop vizualizon valët që i dëgjon dhe përdor zbulimin e tingullit për efekte të ndryshme.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Milkdrop var ursprungligen ett visualiserarande ljudplug-in till Winamp. Medan du lyssnar på din musik så för dig Milkdrop flygande genom de ljudvågor du hör och använder rytmavkänning för att ge dig psykedeliska effekter som skapar en mäktig visuell resa via ljudet.</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">MilkDrop аз ибтидо плагини таҷассуми мусиқие барои плеери мусиқии Winamp буд. Вақте ки шумо мусиқиро мешунавед, MilkDrop бо мавҷҳои садояш фораму роҳатбахш аст, ва муайянкуни битҳои мусиқиро барои эҷоди таъсирҳои девонагӣ истифода мекунад ва шуморо ба сайёҳии мусиқӣ мебарад.</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">MilkDrop แต่เดิมเป็น "ปลั๊ก-อิน" การแสดงแสงสีประกอบเพลง ของโปรแกรมเล่นเพลง Winamp.  ในขณะที่คุณฟังเพลงของคุณ, MilkDrop นำคุณบินผ่านคลื่นเสียงที่เกิดขึ้นตามที่คุณได้ยิน, และใช้การจับจังหวะ ในการส่งผลต่อเอฟเฟคภาพลวงตา อันหลากหลาย, สร้างภาพอันตื่นตาในการเดินทางไปตามเสียงเพลง.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">MilkDrop aslında Winamp müzik çalıcısı için görsel bir "eklenti" dir. Müziğinizi dinlerken, Milkdrop size işittiğiniz ses dalgaları arasında uçuyormuşcasına bir his ve ritm algılayıcısı ile de en çılgın efektleri yaşıyormuşçasına görsel bir şölen sunar.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">MilkDrop спочатку був додатком візуалізації музики для програвача музики Winamp. MilkDrop створює багату гаму візуалізації музики, використовуючи власний механізм визначення музичних тактів.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">MilkDrop ban đầu là một "plug-in" trình diễn nhạc cho Winamp. Khi bạn nghe nhạc, MilkDrop sẽ làm bạn bay bổng trong âm thanh bạn đang nghe, và sử dụng bộ dò giai điệu để kích hoạt vô số những hiệu ứng ảo, tạo ra một cuộc hành trình âm thanh qua mắt thường</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">MilkDrop 是来自于 Winamp 音乐播放器的可视化效果插件。在你听音乐时，MilkDrop 通过节拍检测触发的无数迷幻的效果，带你与声波一起飞翔，给你带来丰富的音乐和视觉旅程。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">MilkDrop是來自於Winamp音樂播放器的視覺效果插件。在您在聽音樂時，MilkDrop通過節奏偵測觸發的無數夢幻的效果，帶您穿越聆聽中的音樂饗宴，也給您帶來豐富的聲音和視覺效果的奇幻旅程。</description>
    <platform>windx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
