<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="screensaver.xbmc.builtin.slideshow"
       name="Slideshow"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension point="xbmc.ui.screensaver" library=""/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Скрийнсейвър, изобразяващ слайдшоу от картини</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Screensaver that displays an image slideshow</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Bildschirmschoner, welcher eine Bilder-Slideshow anzeigt</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Un salvapantallas que muestra una presentación de imágenes</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Diaesitys</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Economiseur affichant un diaporama</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Képernyővédő ami diavetítést csinál</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">이미지 슬라이드쇼를 보여주는 화면보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Schermbeveiliging die een diavoorstelling toont</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wygaszacz ekranu wyświetlający pokaz slajdów</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Protecção de ecrã que mostra uma apresentação de fotografias</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Protector ecran care afișează o prezentare de diapozitive</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Хранитель экрана показывающий слайдшоу из изображений</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skärmsläckare som visar ett bildspel</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">幻灯片屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Скрийнсейвърът Slideshow изобразява слайдшоу от картини с разнообразни ефекти при прехода между отделните картини. Можете да зададете като източник на картини fanart от видео/музикалната си библиотеката или персонална папка с изображения.</description>
    <description lang="en">The Slideshow screensaver will show you a slide show of images using various transition effects. It can be configured to show your libraries music or video fanart, or a custom folder of images</description>
    <description lang="de">Der Slideshow-Bildschirmschoner zeigt eine Bilder-Slideshow mit verschiedenen Übergangseffekten. Er kann so konfiguriert werden, dass Musik oder Video Fanarts aus der Bibliothek, oder Bilder eines bestimmten Ordners angezeigt werden.  </description>
    <description lang="es">El salvapantallas Slideshow mostrará una presentación de imágenes varios efectos de transición. Puede ser configurado para mostrar los fanart de tus bibliotecas de música o video, o las imágenes de una carpeta.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Slideshow-näytönsäästäjä näyttää diaesityksen käyttäen erilaisia siirtymätehosteita. Sen voi asettaa näyttämään musiikki- tai videokirjastojen fanitaidetta tai valitusta kuvakansiosta.</description>
    <description lang="fr">L'économiseur Diaporama affichera un diaporama en utilisant divers effets de transition. Il peut afficher votre collection de fanarts vidéos ou musicaux, ou un dossier d'images en particulier.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Slideshow képernyővédő diavetítés-szerűen képeket mutat egymás után különböző váltási effektussal. Beállítható úgy hogy a médiatárból mutasson zenei-, vagy film fanartképeket, vagy egy egyedi mappából mutassa azokat.</description>
    <description lang="ko">슬라이드쇼 화면보호기는 다양한 화면 전환효과를 이용해 이미지 슬라이드쇼를 보여줍니다. 설정을 통해 음악, 비디오 팬아트나 사용자 폴더의 사진을 지정할수 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl">De Diavoorstellingsschermbeveiliging zal u een diavoorstelling tonen met verschillende overgangseffecten. U kan muziek- of videofanart uit uw bibliotheek tonen of zelf een map opgeven die afbeeldingen bevat.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten wygaszacz ekranu to pokaz slajdów obrazów, przy użyciu różnych efektów przejść. Może być skonfigurowany tak, aby pokazywał fanart filmów, muzyki lub dowolny folder ze zdjęciami.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Protecção de ecrã que lhe mostra fotografias usando vários efeitos de transição. Pode ser configurado para visualizar fanart das bibliotecas de música e vídeo ou uma pasta com as suas imagens.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Protectorul de ecran Slideshow va afișa imagini folosind diferite efecte de tranziție. Poate fi configurat să afișeze imagini fanart din mediateca audio sau video sau dintr-un dosar personalizat.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Хранитель экрана Slideshow покажет вам слайдшоу из изображений используя различные эффекты переходов. Он может быть настроен для показа фанарта музыки и видео из вашей библиотеки мультимедиа, или папки с изображениям.</description>
    <description lang="se">Bildspelsskärmsläckaren visar ett bildspel med en variation av övergångseffekter. Den kan konfigureras att visa ditt biblioteks musik eller videofanart, eller en egen mapp med bilder</description>
    <description lang="zh">幻灯片屏保将使用各种过渡效果以幻灯片形式显示您的图片。你可以设置它显示音乐或视频资料库同人画，或某个文件夹中的图片。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
