<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="repository.pvr-ios.xbmc.org"
		name="XBMC.org PVR Add-ons"
		version="1.1.14"
		provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.pvr" version="1.9.0"/>
  </requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository"
		name="Official XBMC.org PVR Add-on Repository">
		<info compressed="true">http://mirrors.xbmc.org/addons/gotham/pvr/ios/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>http://mirrors.xbmc.org/addons/gotham/pvr/ios/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">http://mirrors.xbmc.org/addons/gotham/pvr/ios</datadir>
		<hashes>true</hashes>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="am">ከ XBMC.org የ PVR ተጨማ-ሪዎች መግጠሚያ </summary>
		<summary lang="ar">ثبت اضافة البي في ار PVR من موقع xbmc.org</summary>
		<summary lang="bg">Инсталира PVR добавки от XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="ca">Instal·la complements PVR des de XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="cs">Nainstalovat rozšíření PVR z XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="cy">Gosod Ychwanegon PVR o XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="da">Installer PVR add-ons fra XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Installiere PVR Addons von XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Εγκατάσταση Πρόσθετων PVR από το XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Install PVR Add-ons from XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">Install PVR Add-ons from XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Install PVR Add-ons from XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Install PVR Add-ons from XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Instalar Complementos de PVR de XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Instalar complemento PVR desde XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Instalar Complementos PVR de XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="es_VE">Instalar Add-ons para PVR de XMBC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="et">Paigalda videosalvesti lisasid lehelt XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="eu">Instalatu PVR gehigarriak XBMC.org-etik</summary>
		<summary lang="fi">Asenna PVR-lisäosia XBMC.orgista</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Installer des extensions Magnétoscope numérique depuis XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Installer des addiciels de numériscopes depuis XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Instalar Engadidos de PVR dende XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="he">התקן הרחבות PVR מ-XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="hr">Instaliraj PVR dodatke s XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">PVR kiegészítők telepítése az XBMC.org-ról</summary>
		<summary lang="id">Pasang Pengaya PVR dari XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="is">Settu inn viðbætur fyrir persónulegan mynd upptökubúnað (PVR) frá XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Installa addon da XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="ja">XBMC.org から PVR アドオンをインストール</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">XBMC.org에서 PVR 애드온 설치</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">Įdiekite PVR priedą iš XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="lv">Instalēt PVR pielikumus no XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="mr">XBMC.ORG  वरून PVR अद्डोंस इंस्टाल करा </summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Installeer PVR Add-ons van XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="no">Installer tillegg fra XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Instaluj klienty TV z XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Instalar Add-ons PVR de XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Instalar Add-ons de PVR do repositório XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Установить дополнения с сайта XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="sk">Inštalovať PVR doplnky z XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="sl">Namestite dodatke PVR z XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">Installera PVR-tillägg från XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="ta_IN">XBMC.org இணையத்தில் இருந்து PVR துணை நிரல்களை நிறுவவும்</summary>
		<summary lang="tg">Насб кардани барномаи иловагии PVR аз XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="th">ติดตั้งส่วนเสริม PVR จาก XBMC.org</summary>
		<summary lang="tr">XBMC.org'dan PVR Eklentilerini Yükle</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">从 XBMC.org 安装 PVR 插件</summary>
		<description lang="ar">نزل ونصب اضاقة البي في ار من موقع اكس بي ام سي الرسمي مستودع الاضافات "repository". باستخدامك للمستودع الرسمي ستستفيد من تعدد سيرفراتنا التي ستعطيك سرعة اكبر في تنزيل بجعلك تنزل من منطقة قريبة منك. كل الملفات في هذا المستودع مر على اختبارات مبدئية ولكن اذا وجدت اي خلل او خطأ في </description>
		<description lang="bg">Сваля и инсталира PVR добавки от официалното хранилище за добавки на XBMC.org. Ползвайки добавката ще се възползвате от системата ни от огледални сървъри - за да сваляте с висока скорост, от сървър близък до Вас. Добавките от хранилището са минали няколко теста, но ако се натъкнете на неработеща или проблемна добавка, моля уведомете екипа на XBMC, за да бъдат предприети необходимите действия.</description>
		<description lang="cs">Stáhnout a nainstalovat rozšíření z oficiálního repozitáře XBMC.org. [CR]  Použitím oficiálního repozitáře získáte rozsáhlý systém zrcadel, který vám umožní rychlé stažení z blízkého regionu.[CR]  Všechna rozšíření v repozitáři prošla základním testováním. Pokud najdete rozbitý, nebo nefunkční rozšíření, nahlaste jej prosím týmu XBMC, abychom mohli dle potřeby zakročit.</description>
		<description lang="da">Download og installer PVR add-ons fra det officielle XBMC.org add-on repository.[CR] Ved at benytte det officielle repository drager du fordel af vores distributionsservice som gør at du kan downloade hurtigere fra en placering tæt på dig.[CR] Alle add-ons i dette repository har gennemgået basale tests. Skulle du finde en defekt x add-on så rapporter det venligst til Team XBMC, så de kan tage de nødvendige handlinger.</description>
		<description lang="de">Dies ist das offizielle XBMC.org PVR-Addon-Verzeichnis.[CR]Dieses Addon-Verzeichnis ermöglicht aufgrund umfangreicher Spiegelserver in der Nähe schnelle Downloads.[CR]Alle Addons in diesem Verzeichnis wurden einfachen Tests unterzogen. Sollte dennoch ein Addon nicht richtig funktionieren benachrichtige bitte Team XBMC damit wir reagieren können.</description>
		<description lang="el">Λήψη και εγκατάσταση πρόσθετων από το επίσημο αποθετήριο του XBMC.org.[CR]  Χρησιμοποιώντας το Επίσημο Αποθετήριο μπορείτε να εκμεταλλευτείτε τους εκτεταμένους διακομιστές αρχείων μας για ταχύτερες λήψεις από μία κοντινή σας περιοχή.[CR]  Όλα τα πρόσθετα σε αυτό το αποθετήριο έχουν περάσει τις στοιχειώδεις δοκιμές, αν βρείτε ένα κατεστραμμένο ή ανενεργό πρόσθετο παρακαλούμε να το αναφέρετε στην Ομάδα XBMC ούτως ώστε να ληφθούν οι απαραίτητες ενέργειες.</description>
		<description lang="en">Download and install PVR add-ons from the Official XBMC.org add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have under gone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team XBMC so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="en_AU">Download and install PVR add-ons from the Official XBMC.org add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have undergone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team XBMC so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Download and install PVR add-ons from the Official XBMC.org add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have under gone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team XBMC so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Download and install PVR add-ons from the Official XBMC.org add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have under gone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team XBMC so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="es">Descarga e instala complementos de PVR desde el repositorio oficial de XBMC.[CR] Usando el repositorio oficial tendrás las ventajas de nuestro servicio de mirrors para ayudarte a conseguir unas descargas más rápidas de un sitio cercano a ti.[CR] Todos los complementos en este repositorio han pasado por un periodo de pruebas básico, pero si encuentras algún complemento que no funciona, por favor informa de ello al equipo de XBMC para solucionar el problema.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Descarga e instala el complemento desde el repositorio oficial de XBMC.org.[CR] Usando el repositorio oficial tendrá las ventajas de nuestro servicio de réplicas para ayudarle a conseguir unas descargas más rápidas de un sitio cercano a su región.[CR] Todos los complementos en este repositorio han pasado por un periodo de pruebas básico, pero si encuentra algún complemento que no funciona, por favor infórmelo al equipo de XBMC para que podamos tomar las acciones necesarias.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Descarga e instala complementos del repositorio oficial XBMC.org.[CR] Al usar el repositorio oficial, tendrá la ventaja de nuestro servicio extenso de espejos para ayudarle a tener descargas mas rapidas desde una region mas cerca de usted.[CR] Todos los complementos en este repositorio se han probado de manera básica, si encuentra alguno que no funciona o roto, favor de reportarlo al Equipo de XBMC para poder tomar las medidas necesarias.</description>
		<description lang="es_VE">Descarga e instala add-ons de PVR del repositorio oficial de XBMC.org.[CR] Al hacer uso del repositorio oficial podrás tomar ventaja de nuestro extenso servicio para descarga de archivos a gran velocidad desde una región cercana a la tuya. [CR] Todos los add-ons en este repositorio han sido probados de forma básica, si algún add-on no puede ser descargado o no funciona por favor repórtalo al Equipo de XBMC para de esta manera tomar cualquier acción que sea necesaria.</description>
		<description lang="et">Lae alla ja installi videosalvesti lisasid ametlikust XBMC.org hoidlast.[CR]  Ametliku hoidla kasutamise eeliseks on võimalus kasutada meie ulatuslikku failide peegelteenust laadides faile sulle kõige lähemast serverist.[CR]  Kõik lisad selles hoidlas on läbinud elementaarse testimise. Siiski, kui sa leiad vigase või mittetöötava lisa, siis palun teavita sellest XBMC meeskonda, et me saaksime vajaliku abi osutada.</description>
		<description lang="fr">Télécharger et installer des extensions à partir du dépôt officiel XBMC.org.[CR]  En utilisant le dépôt officiel, vous bénéficierez de notre service de serveurs miroirs vous permettant de télécharger rapidement depuis une région proche de vous.[CR]  Toutes les extensions de ce dépôt ont été testées de manière basique, si vous trouvez une extension corrompue ou inutilisable, merci d'en informer la Team XBMC afin que nous puissions prendre les mesures nécessaires.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Télécharger et installer des addiciels de numériscopes depuis le dépôt officiel de XBMC.org.[CR] En utilisant le dépôt officiel vous pourrez bénéficier de notre service étendu de miroirs de fichiers favorisant des téléchargements plus rapides depuis une région proche de vous.[CR] Tous les addiciels de ce dépôt ont subi des tests de base. Si vous trouvez un addiciel non fonctionnel ou brisé, veuillez le rapporter à l'équipe XBMC afin que nous puissions agir.</description>
		<description lang="gl">Descargar e instalar Engadidos de PVR dende o repositorio oficial de XBMC.org.[CR] Empregando o repositorio oficial, vostede poderá gozar das vantaxes do seu extenso servizo de replicación de ficheiros que lle permite unhas descargas máis rápidas dende unha rexión preto a vostede.[CR] Tódolos Engadidos deste repositorio pasaron por comprobacións básicas. Se atopa algún Engadido roto ou non funcional, por favor reporteo ó equipo de XBMC para que poidan actuar en consecuencia.</description>
		<description lang="he">ניתן להוריד ולהתקין תוספי PVR מהמאגר הרשמי של Official XBMC.org.[CR]‎ השימוש במאגר הרשמי מקנה לך את היתרון שבשימוש בשירות שיקוף הקבצים שלנו ובכך לסייע לך להוריד מהר יותר מהאזור המועדף עליך.[CR] כל התוספים במאגר זה עברו בדיקה בסיסית, אם מצאת שאחד מהם פגום או בלתי פעיל נא לדווח עליו לצוות של XBMC כדי שנוכל לפעול בהתאם.</description>
		<description lang="hr">reuzmite i instalirajte PVR dodatke sa službenog XBMC.org repozitorija dodataka.[CR]  Korištenjm službenog repozitorija biti ćete u mogućnosti iskoristiti prednost našeg zrcalnog poslužitelja u svrhu bržeg preuzimanja iz regije bliže vama.[CR]  Svi dodaci na ovom repozitoriju prošli su osnovno testiranje. Ako pronađete slomljeni ili dodatak koji ne radi, prijavite ga XBMC timu da ga možemo popraviti.</description>
		<description lang="hu">PVR Kiegészítők letöltése és telepítése a hivatalos XBMC.org tárolóhelyről.[CR] A hivatalos tárolóhely használatával kihasználhatod szerteágazó tükör-kiszolgáló hálózatunkat, ami segít a gyorsabb letöltésben egy hozzád közelebb eső körzet használatával.[CR]  Minden kiegészítő ezen a tárolóhelyen átment egy alaptesztelésen. Ha mégis hibás vagy nem működő kiegészítőt találsz, kérünk jelezd az XBMC csapatnak, hogy megtegyük a szükséges lépéseket.</description>
		<description lang="id">Unduh dan pasang pengaya dari repositori pengaya resmi XBMC.org. [CR] Dengan menggunakan repositori resmi anda akan mendapat keuntungan dari miror berkas kami yang luas dimana dapat membantu anda untuk lebih cepat mengunduh dari daerah yang dekat dengan anda. [CR] Semua pengaya pada repository telah melalui uji coba standar, jika anda menemukan pengaya yang rusak atau tidak bekerja tolong laporkan kepada tim XBMC agar kami bisa menindak lanjutinya.</description>
		<description lang="is">Halaðu niður og settu inn viðbætur fyrir myndupptöku frá viðurkenndu viðbótasafni frá XBMC.org.[CR] Með því að nota opinbera geymsluna þá geturðu nýtt þér skráaspeglunarþjónustu okkar til að fá hraðara niðurhal frá stað nálægt þér.[CR] Allar viðbætur í þessari geymslu hafa farið í gegnum grunn prófanir, ef þú finnur bilaða viðbót eða einhverja sem virkar ekki þá tilkynntu það til Team XBMC svo við getum gripið til viðeigandi aðgerða.</description>
		<description lang="it">Scarica ed installa gli addon dalla libreria ufficiale di XBMC.org[CR]  Usando la libreria ufficiale avrai il vantaggio di ottenere download più veloci con mirror più vicini alla tua località.[CR]  Tutti gli addon in questa libreria sono stati sottoposti a test di base, se ne trovi uno non funzionante o corrotto, per favore riporta il problema al team di XBMC così potremmo prendere provvedimenti.</description>
		<description lang="ja">オフィシャルの XBMC.org リポジトリから PVR アドオンをダウンロードします。[CR] オフィシャルリポジトリを使うことで、お住まいのエリアに近いミラーサーバーから高速にアドオンをダウンロードすることが可能です。[CR] このリポジトリ上のアドオンは全て、簡単な動作テストを受けてはいますが、もしアドオンがおかしかったりうまく動作しなかったりした場合は、XBMC チームに連絡をお願いします。</description>
		<description lang="ko">공식 XBMC.org 애드온 저장소에서 PVR 애드온을 다운로드하여 설치합니다.[CR] 공식 저장소를 사용하면 파일 미러링 서비스를 통해 사용자와 가까운 곳에서 빠르게 다운로드할 수 있습니다.[CR] 저장소의 모든 애드온은 기본 테스트를 거치지만 작동이 되지 않거나 손상된 애드온을 발견하면 필요한 조치를 취할 수 있게 Team XBMC로 알려주시기 바랍니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt">Atsisiųskite ir įdiekite PVR priedą iš oficialios XBMC.org priedų saugyklos. [Cr] Naudojant oficialią saugyklą galėsite pasinaudoti mūsų  failų Veidrodine saugyklos paslauga katra padės jums greičiau parsisiųsti iš artimiausios vietos šalia jūsų. [CR] Visi priedai šioje saugykloje yra perėję pagrindinį testavimą, jei atsisiuntėte neveikiantį ar/arba sugadintą priedą praneškite 'Team XBMC', kad galėtume imtis visų būtinų priemonių klaidai ištaisyti.</description>
		<description lang="lv">Lejupielādējiet un instalējiet PVR pielikumus no oficiālā XBMC.org pielikumu repozitorija.[CR]  Izmantojot oficiālo repozitoriju, varēsiet izmantot mūsu plašo spoguļu pakalpojumu, lai iegūtu ātrākas lejupielādes no reģiona, kas vistuvāk.[CR]  Visi pielikumi šajā repozitorijā ir izgājuši pamata testēšanu, bet, ja atrodat saplīsušu vai nestrādājošu pielikumu, lūdzu, ziņojiet par to Team XBMC, lai varam izpildīt nepieciešamās labošanas darbības.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Download en installeer PVR add-ons van het officiële XBMC.org add-on depot.[CR] Wanneer u het officiële depot gebruikt beschikt u over onze uitgebreide mirrorservice, waardoor u snel kan downloaden van locaties in uw buurt.[CR] Alle add-ons in dit depot ondergingen standaardtests; indien u een defecte of niet-werkende add-on vindt, meld dit dan aan Team XBMC zodat zij actie kunnen ondernemen.</description>
		<description lang="no">Last ned og installer tillegg fra den offisielle XBMC.org pakkebrønnen.[CR] Når du benytter den offisielle brønnen drar du fordel av vår utvidede filspeilingstjeneste slik at du får raskere nedlastinger fra en server nær deg.[CR] Alle tillegg i denne brønnen har gått gjennom en grunnleggende testing, men hvis du finner et tillegg som ikke fungerer, vennligst rapporter det til Team XBMC så vi får sett på det.</description>
		<description lang="pl">Pobieraj i instaluj klienty TV z oficjalnego repozytorium XBMC.org.[CR] Używając oficjalnego repozytorium korzystasz z serwerów lustrzanych, rozsianych po całym świecie. Wybierany jest ten, który znajduje się najbliżej ciebie, zapewniając dużą prędkość połączenia.[CR]Wszystkie klienty znajdujące się w tym repozytorium są testowane, ale mogą okazać się niesprawne. Zgłoś wówczas błąd, aby zespół XBMC mógł podjąć odpowiednie działanie.</description>
		<description lang="pt">Transferir e instalar add-ons PVR do repositório oficial XBMC.org.[CR] Ao usar o repositório oficial, os nossos servidores garantem-lhe sempre transferências rápidas a partir da localização mais próxima.[CR] Todos os Add-ons neste repositório foram alvo de testes preliminares. Na improvável hipótese de encontrar um Add-on que não funcione, por favor contacte a equipa do XBMC, para que a situação se resolva.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Transfira e instale add-ons de Tv ao Vivo, a partir do repositório oficial do XBMC.org.[CR]|Ao utilizar o repositório oficial, você será capaz de tirar proveito do nosso serviço de espelhamento de arquivos, auxiliando em downloads mais rápidos a partir de uma região perto de você.[CR]|Todos os add-ons neste repositório passam por testes básicos, se você encontrar algum quebrado ou que não esteja funcionando, por favor reporte para a equipe do XBMC, para que possamos tomar as ações necessárias.</description>
		<description lang="ru">Загружайте и устанавливайте обновления из официального репозитория XBMC.org[CR]Используя официальный репозиторий, вы сможете воспользоваться преимуществами распределенного хранилища для быстрой загрузки файлов с ближайшего к вам сервера.[CR]Все дополнения в данном репозитории прошли тестирование. Если вы обнаружили нерабочее дополнение, сообщите об этом разработчикам XBMC.</description>
		<description lang="sk">Stiahnuť a nainštalovať PVR rozšírenia z oficiálneho zdroja rozšírení XBMC.org.[CR] Použitím oficiálneho zdroja získavate možnosť využiť rozsiahly systém zrkadiel, ktorý Vám umožní rýchlejšie sťahovanie z Vám blízkeho regiónu.[CR] Všetky rozšírenia v tomto zdroji boli podrobené základnému testovaniu. Ak nájdete poškodené alebo nefunkčné rozšírenie, oznámte to prosím týmu XBMC aby mohol podľa potreby zakročiť.</description>
		<description lang="sl">Prenos in namestitev dodatkov PVR iz uradnega skladišča XBMC.org.[CR] Z uporabo uradnega skladišča, boste lahko izkoristili hitrejšo povezavo, ki bo izbrana glede na vašo lokacijo.[CR] Vsi dodatki tega skladišča so bili osnovno stestirani, če pa boste našli pokvarjen ali nedelujoč dodatek, to sporočite ekipi XBMC, da bomo lahko odpravili napake.</description>
		<description lang="sv">Ladda ner och installera PVR-tillägg från det officiella XBMC.org tilläggsförrådet.[CR] Genom att använda det officiella förrådet kommer du att få fördelen att kunna använda vår omfattande spegeltjänst som hjälper dig till snabbare nedladdningar från en plats nära dig.[CR] Alla tillägg i detta förråd har genomgått grundläggande tester. Hittar du ett trasigt eller icke fungerande tillägg, vänligen meddela detta till Team XBMC så att vi kan vidta nödvändiga åtgärder.</description>
		<description lang="ta_IN">அதிகாரப்பூர்வ XBMC.org துணை பயன் களஞ்சியத்திலிருந்து துணை பயன்களை பதிவிறக்கம் மற்றும் நிறுவல் செய்யலாம். [CR] அதிகாரப்பூர்வ களஞ்சியத்தை பயன்படுத்துவதால் நீங்கள் உங்கள் இருப்பிடத்திருக்கு அருகாமையில் உள்ள களஞ்சியத்தில் இருந்து சீக்கிரமாக சேவைகளை பெறமுடியும்.[CR] இங்குள்ள அணைத்து துணை பயன்களும் நன்கு பரிசொதிக்கபட்டவை, சரியாக இயங்கவில்லை என்றால் XBMC குழுவிடம் சொல்லவும்.</description>
		<description lang="tg">Барномаҳои иловагии PVR-ро аз анбори нармафзори расмии XBMC.org боргирӣ кунед ва насб кунед.[CR]  Агар анбори нармафзори расмиро истифода баред, метавонед нармафзори иловагиро аз серверҳои наздиктарин ба шумо боргирӣ намоед.[CR]  Ҳамаи нармафзори анбори зикршуда аз санҷиши асосӣ мегузаранд, ва агар шумо ягон барномаи иловагии вайроншуда ё ғайрифаъолро пайдо кунед, метавонед дар бораи он гузоришро ба Гурӯҳи кории XBMC фиристонед, то ки барномасозон тавонанд камбудиҳои пайдошударо ҳал кунанд.</description>
		<description lang="th">ดาวน์โหลดและติดตั้งส่วนเสริม PVR จากเว็บไซต์หลัก XBMC.org [CR] โดยการใช้ที่เก็บส่วนเสริมอย่างเป็นทางการของเว็บไซต์จะทำให้คุณได้ประโยชน์จากแหล่งดาวน์โหลดที่หลากหลายที่จะช่วยให้คุณดาวน์โหลดได้ไวขึ้นจากภูมิภาคที่ใกล้ที่สุด [CR] ส่วนเสริมทั้งหมดบนที่เก็บนี้ได้ผ่านการทดลองแล้ว หากคุณพบการชำรุดหรือส่วนเสริมที่ไม่ทำงานโปรดแจ้งทีมงาน XBMC เพื่อการดำเนินการต่อไป</description>
		<description lang="tr">PVR Eklentilerini Resmi XBMC.org eklenti deposundan indir ve yükle.[CR]Resmi yazılım depomuzu kullanarak size en yakın bölgeden en hızlı biçimde indirme yapmanızı sağlayacak gelişkin dosya aynalama servisini kullanma avantajını elde edeceksiniz.[CR]Bu yazılım deposundaki tüm eklentiler temel testlerden geçerler, şayet hatalı ya da çalışmayan bir eklenti bulur iseniz lütfen düzeltilmesi için bu durumu XBMC Takımına bildiriniz.</description>
		<description lang="zh">从官方 XBMC.org 插件库下载和安装 PVR 插件。[CR]　通过官方程序库你将能利用我们广泛的镜像服务优势，使你能够就近下载资源。[CR]　官方库中的所有插件都经过了基本的测试，如果你发现有失效或不能正常工作的插件，请向 XBMC 开发团队报告，以便及时处理。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af">Die XBMC span het nie al die byvoegsels in die kodebank gemaak nie en is nie verantwoordelik vir hulle inhoud nie</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="am">የ XBMC ቡድን እዚህ ማጠራቀሚያ ውስጥ ያሉትን የ ተጨማ-ሪዎች ይዞታ አልፈጠሩም ስለዚህም ምንም አይነት ሀላፊነት አይወስዱም</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar">فريق برنامج إكس بى إم سى لم يُصنِع جميع اﻹضافات فى هذا المستودع وغير مسؤول عن ما قد تسببه لك</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be">Team XBMC did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg">Team XBMC (Екипът зад XBMC) не е автор на всички добавки в хранилището и не носи отговорност за съдържанието им</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca">L'equip de l'XBMC no ha fet tots els complements d'aquest repositori i per tant no són responsables del seu contingut.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs">Tým XBMC nevytvořil všechna rozšíření v tomto repozitáři a není zodpovědný za jejich obsah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy">Nid Team XBMC wnaeth yr holl ychwanegion yn y storfa hon ac nid ydynt yn gyfrifol am eu cynnwys.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da">Team XBMC har ikke lavet alle add-ons i dette fjernlager og er ikke ansvarlig for deres indhold</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de">Die Addons in diesem Verzeichnis wurden nicht alle vom Team XBMC erstellt. Verantwortlich für den Inhalt sind die jeweiligen Autoren.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el">Η Ομάδα XBMC δεν δημιούργησε όλα τα πρόσθετα σε αυτό το αποθετήριο συνεπώς δεν είναι υπεύθυνοι για το περιεχόμενό τους</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Team XBMC did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_AU">Team XBMC did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Team XBMC did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Team XBMC did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es">El equipo de XBMC no ha hecho todos los Complementos en este repositorio y no son responsables de su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">No todos los add-ons en este repositorio han sido creados por el equipo de XBMC y este no es responsable de su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">El equipo de XBMC no hizo todos los add-ons en este repositorio y no es responsable de su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_VE">El equipo de XBMC no creó todos los add-ons en este repositorio y no son responsables por su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et">XBMC meeskond ei teinud kõiki lisasid selles hoidlas ja ei vastuta ka nende sisu eest.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu">XBMC taldeak ez ditu biltegi honetako gehigarri guztiak sortu eta ez da beren edukien erantzule.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi">Team XBMC ei ole tehnyt kaikkia tässä säilössä olevia lisäosia, eikä siten ole vastuullinen kyseisten lisäosien sisällöstä</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr">La Team XBMC n'est pas l'auteur de toutes les extensions de ce dépôt et n'est pas responsable de leur contenu</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">L'équipe XBMC n'a pas créé tous les addiciels de ce dépôt et n'est pas responsable de leur contenu</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl">O equipo de XBMC non creou todos os Engadidos deste repositorio e non é responsábel do seu contido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he">צוות XBMC לא יצר את כל ההרחבות שבמאגר זה ואינו אחראי על תוכנם</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr">XBMC tim nije autor svih dodataka u ovom repozitoriju te kao takvi ne odgovaraju za njihov sadržaj</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu">Nem minden itt található kiegészítőt az XBMC csapat készített és nem vállal felelősséget azok tartalmáért</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id">Tim XBMC tidak membuat semua pengaya pada repository ini dan tidak bertanggung jawab atas isinya.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is">XBMC teymið gerir ekki allar þessar viðbætur og er ekki ábyrgt fyrir innihaldi þeirra.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it">Il team di XBMC non ha creato tutti gli addon di questa libreria e non è responsabile per il loro contenuto</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja">XBMC チームが、このリポジトリ上の全アドオンを作ったわけではありません。また、その内容についても責任は負いかねます。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko">Team XBMC는 이 저장소의 모든 애드온을 제작하지 않았으며, 애드온 콘텐츠에 대한 책임이 없습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ku">تیمی XBMC هەموو پێوەکراوەکانی دروست نەکردووە بۆیە بەرپرسیار نیە لە پێکهاتە و ناوەڕۆکەکانی</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt">XBMC komanda netestavo priedų šioje saugykloje ir neatsako arba nėra atsakinga už jų turinį</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lv">XBMC komanda nav izveidojusi visus šīs krātuves paplašinājumus un nav atbildīga par to saturu</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="mk">XBMC тимот ги нема направено сите овие додатоци и не е одговорен за нивната содржина</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="mr">हे अद्डोंस XBMC संघाने नाही बनीवले अहेत . आणि त्यातील सामग्री बद्दल XBMC संघ जबाबदार नाही आहे </disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl">Team XBMC heeft niet alle add-ons in dit depot geschreven en is niet verantwoordelijk voor hun inhoud.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="no">Team XBMC har ikke produsert alle tilleggene i denne pakkebrønnen og er ikke ansvarlig for deres innhold</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl">Zespół XBMC nie tworzy wszystkich dodatków i nie bierze odpowiedzialności za ich zawartość</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt">A equipa XBMC não desenvolveu todos os Add-ons neste repositório e não é responsável pelo seu conteúdo.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">O Time do XBMC não produziu todos os add-ons deste repositório, e portanto não é responsável ​​por seu conteúdo</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro">Echipa XBMC nu a creat toate aceste suplimente din acest depozit și nu este responsabilă pentru conținutul lor.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru">Разработчики XBMC не являются авторами всех дополнений в данном репозитории и не несут ответственность за их содержимое.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="se">Team XBMC har inte skapat alla tillägg på detta förråd och är inte ansvariga för deras innehåll</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk">Team XBMC nevytvoril všetky rozšírenia v tomto zdroji nie je zodpovedný za ich obsah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sl">Ekipa XBMC ni naredila vseh dodatkov v tem skladišču in ne odgovarja za njihovo vsebino</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv">Team XBMC har inte gjort alla tillägg och är inte ansvariga för innehållet i dessa.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ta_IN">இந்த களஞ்சியத்தில் உள்ள துனை பயன்களை XBMC அணியால் உருவாக்கப்படவில்லை மற்றும் அவற்றின் உள்ளடக்கம் தங்கள் பொறுப்பு அல்ல.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tg">Гурӯҳи кории XBMC дар ин анбори нармафзор соҳиби ҳамаи барномаҳои иловагӣ намебошад ва барои мӯҳтавояшон ҷавобгар намебшад</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th">ทีม XBMC ไม่ได้จัดทำ ส่วนเสริม ทั้งหมดในแหล่งข้อมูลโปรแกรมนี้ และจะไม่รับผิดชอบต่อเนื้อหาเหล่านั้น</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr">XBMC takımı bu depodaki tüm eklentileri geliştirmemiştir ve bunların içeriklerinden sorumlu değildir.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk">Зауважте, що не всі додатки в цьому Репозиторії створені Командою XBMC, і тому Команда не несе відповідальності за їх вміст.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi">Đội ngũ XBMC không làm ra tất cả các add-on có trên kho chứa này và sẽ không chịu trách nhiệm về nội dung của các add-on đấy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh">本库中插件不完全由 XBMC 团队开发，XBMC 团队对他人提交的内容不承担责任</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">這個附加元件庫的附加元件並非全部由 XBMC 團隊製作的，所以我們不對這些內容負責。</disclaimer>
		<platform>ios</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
