<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="visualization.fishbmc"
  version="4.0.19"
  name="FishBMC"
  provider-name="26elf">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="fishbmc.vis"
    library_osx="fishbmc.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Visualisasie wat Golwe en Wasigheid effek wys</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">إسلوب تخيلي يُظهِر مؤثراتاً بصرية تتضمن موجات ومؤثرات عين السمكة (مؤثرات ضبابية)</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Визуализацията представя вълни и размиващи ефекти</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Visualització que mostra efectes d'ona i taques</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Vizualizace zobrazující vlny a rozmazané efekty</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Delweddu'n dangos Tonau ac Effeithiau Pylu</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Visualisering som viser Waves og Blur effekter</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Visualisierung mit Wellen- und Weichzeichnungs-Effekten</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Οπτικοποίηση προβολής Κυμάτων και Εφέ Θαμπώματος</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Visualization showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Visualización que muestra efectos de ondas y difuminado.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Visualización que muestra efectos de ondas y desenfoque</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización que muestra olas y efectos de desenfoque</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Laine- ja uduefektidega visuaal</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">مجسم ساز با جلوه های موج گونه و محو کننده</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Aalto- ja sumennustehosteita näyttävä visualisaatio</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Visualisation à effet de vague et flou</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Visualisation montrant des vagues et des effets de flou</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Unha visualización con Ondas e efectos de Desenfoque</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">חיזוי המציג אפקטי גלים וטשטוש</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Vizualizacija prikazuje valove i zamućene efekte</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">A vizualizáció Hullámokat és Elmosás Effekteket mutat.</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Visualisasi menunjukkan efek gelombang dan efek kabur.</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Sjónræn upplifun með bylgjum og afskerpuáhrifum</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Visualizzazione mostrando Onde e Sfumature</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">ウェーブとブラー エフェクトを表示するビジュアライザー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">물결 효과와 흐림 효과를 보여주는 시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Vizualizacija atvaizduojanti bangas ir suliejimo efektus</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Vizualizācija, rādot viļņus un izpludināšanas efektu</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Визуализација која покажува Бранови и Заматени Ефекти</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Pengvisualan menunjukkan Kesan Gelombang dan Kabur</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Visualisering viser bølge- og uskarpeffekter</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Visualisatie waarbij Golven- en Blureffecten worden getoond </summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Wizualizacja wyświetlająca efekty fali i rozmycia</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização mostrando Ondas e Efeitos Borrados</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Uma visualização com Ondas e Efeitos de Desfocagem</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Vizualizare care arată valuri și efecte de încețoșare</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Визуализация показывает волны и эффект размытия</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca vlnky a efekty rozmazania</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Vizualizacija prikazuje valovanje in učinke zamegljenosti</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Visualisering bestående av vågor- och blur-effekter</summary>
    <summary lang="szl">Wizualizacyjŏ, co pokŏzuje wele i mazy</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Таҷассум бо шамоиши мавҷҳо ва таъсирҳои хирагӣ</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Görselleştirme Dalga ve Bulanıklık Efektlerini gösteriyor</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Візуалізація показу ефектів Хвилі та Розмиття</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Hiển thị sử dụng hiệu ứng Sóng và Làm mờ</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">呈现波浪和模糊效果的可视化效果</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">fishBMC is gebasseer op fische, 'n onafhanklike klank visulasasie program. Die basiese prinsiep is: teken die golflente en smeer die tekening langs Vooraf gedefinieerde vektore. fische sluit ook gevorderde tempo ondekking in, wat 'n besondere visuele ervaring verseker.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">fishBMC е създадена въз основа на fische - самостоятелен инструмент за визуализиране на звук. Основния принцип е изчертаване на вълнова функция и размиване по предварително определени вектори. В допълнение fische съдържа и разширена функция за засичане на ритъма, което би трябвало да гарантира великолепно визуално изживяване.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">fishBMC je založeno na fische - samostatném nástorji pro vizualizaci zvuku. Základní princip: nakresli waveform a rozmaž obrázek podle předdefinováných směrů. Avšak fische také přidává pokročilou detekci rytmu a to garantuje nádherný vizuální zážitek.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">MAe fishBMC yn seiliedig ar fisch, offeryn delweddu sain. Y prif elfen yw: llunio'r ffurf ton a'i lusgo ar hyd fectorau wedi eu diffinioo ymlaen llaw. Hefyd, mae fisch yn cynnwys dull o ganfod curiad uwch, sy'n gwarantu profiad gweledol trawiadol.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">fishBMX er baseret på fische, et standard visualiserings værktøj. Det basale princip er: tegn waveformen og tvær tegning langs de prædefinerede vektorer. fische inkluderer også avanceret beat registrering, som garanterer en god visuel oplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">fishBMC basiert auf fische, einem eigenständigen Ton-Visualisierungs-Programm. Das Grundprinzip ist: Zeichne das Wellen-Spektrum und verwische die Zeichnung entlang festgelegter Vektoren. fische verfügt jedoch auch über eine fortgeschrittene Rhytmus-Erkennung, die ein großartiges visuelles Erlebnis garantiert.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το fishBMC είναι βασισμένο στο fische, ένα ξεχωριστό εργαλείο ηχητικών οπτικοποιήσεων. Η βασική του αρχή είναι: σχεδίαση μιας κυματομορφής και χρωματισμός της εικόνας κατά μήκος προκαθορισμένων διανυσμάτων. Παρ'όλα αυτά, το fische περιλαμβάνει και ανεπτυγμένες μεθόδους εντοπισμού παλμών, γεγονός που εγγυάται μια εκπληκτική οπτική εμπειρία.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualization tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">fishBMC esta basado en fische, una herramienta independiente de visualización de sonidos. El principio básico es: dibujar la forma de onda y difuminar el dibujo a lo largo de los vectores predefinidos. Sin embargo fische También incorpora detección del ritmo avanzado, que garantiza realmente una gran experiencia visual.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">fishBMC está basado en fische, una herramienta de visualización de sonido. El principio básico es dibujar la forma de onda y extenderla a lo largo de vectores predefinidos. Sin embargo, fische también incluye una avanzada detección de ritmos, lo cual garantiza una gran experiencia visual. </description>
    <description lang="es_MX">fishBMC se basa en fische, una herramienta independiente de visualización de sonido. El principio principal es: dibujar la forma de onda y esfumar el dibujo en conjunto a vectores predefinidos. No obstante, fische también incorpora una detección avanzada de compás, lo que garantiza una gran experiencia visual.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">fishBMC baseerub fische visualiseerimistööriistal. Põhiprintsiibiks on: joonista laine ja määri see ettenähtud suundades laiali. fische sisaldab lisaks veel edasijõudnud rütmituvastajat, garanteerides nii vaatajale suurepärase elamuse. </description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">fishBMC بر پایه fische، که یک برنامه مجسم سازی صوتی مجزا است، تهیه شده است. اصل اساسی آن این است: رسم طیف موج و محو کردن تصویر در راستای بردارهای از پیش تعیین شده. fische از یک سیستم پیشرفته تشخیص ریتم نیز برخوردار است که امکان یک تجربه واقعا جالب دیداری را فراهم می آورد.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">fishBMX est basé sur fische, un outil de visualisation audio autonome. Le principe de base est : dessiner la forme de l'onde et altère le dessin suivant des vecteurs prédéfinis. Cependant fische incorpore aussi une détection améliorée du tempo, ce qui garantie une expérience visuelle de qualité</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">fishBMC est basé sur fische, un outil de visualisation sonore. Le principe de base est : dessiner des ondes et déplacer le tracé sur les vecteurs prédéfinis. Cependant fische incorpore aussi un système de détection du rythme, ce qui garantie une grande expérience visuelle.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">fishBMC está baseado en fische, unha ferramenta autónoma de visualización de sons. O principio básico é: debuxar as formas de onda e pintalas ao longo dos vectores predefinidos. E posíbel que fische tamén incorpore detección avanzada de golpes, que realmente garante unha grande experiencia visual.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">החיזוי fishBMC מבוסס על fische, כלי לחיזוי קול. העיקרון הבסיסי אך: ציור צורת גל ומריחת הציור לאורך וקטורים המוגדרים מראש. עם זאת fische גם כולל יכולת מתקדמת לזיהוי קצב מוזיקה, דבר המעניק חוויה חזותית נהדרת.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">fishBMC je temeljen na fische, samostalnom alatu zvučne vizualizacije. Osnovno načelo je: iscrtati valni oblik i razmazati crtež unaprijed određenim vektorima. Međutim fische isto uključuje napredno otkrivanje taktova, koje uistinu jamči sjajno vizualno iskustvo.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">fishBMC a fische-n alapul, egy önálló hangvizualizációs eszköz. A fő célkitűzése: a hanghullám kirajzolása és előre megadott vektorok szerinti módosítása. Viszont a fische szintén alkalmaz egy haladó ütemérzékelőt, ami tényleg garantálja a nagyszerű vizuális élményt.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">fishBMC didasarkan fische, alat visualisasi suara yang berdiri sendiri. Prinsip dasarnya adalah mengambar gelombang dan mengaburkannya sepanjang vektor yang telah ditentukan. Namun fische juga mengikutsertakan deteksi ketukan yang canggih, yang akan menjamin pengalaman visual yang hebat.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">fishBMC er byggður á fische, sjálfstæðu tóli fyrir sjóræna upplifun á hljóði. Grunnuppbyggingin er: teikna bylgjuformið og smyrðu það út eftir skilgreindum vektorum. En fische er líka með þróaða taktskynjun, sem tryggir frábæra sjónræna upplifun.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">fishBMC si basa su fische, uno strumento di visualizzazione del suono standalone. Il principio di base è: disegnare la forma d'onda e spalmare il disegno lungo i vettori predefiniti. Tuttavia fische incorpora anche il rilevamento di battito avanzato, che garantisce un'ottima esperienza visiva.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">fishBMC は、fische というスタンドアロンの音声可視化ツールを基礎にしています。基本的な原理は、描いた波形を事前に定義したベクトルに沿ってにじませます。また fische には高度なビート検出が組み込まれており、本当に素晴らしいビジュアル体験を保証します。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">fllshBMC는 fische에 기반을 둔 음성 시각화 도구입니다. 기본 동작원리는 미리 정의된 벡터에 따라 선과 번짐을 표시하는 것입니다. 거기에다 검증된 멋진 비주얼 경험에 기반한 향상된 비트 검출 결과도 더해 집니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">fishBMC paremtas fische, atskiru garso vizualizavimo įrankiu. Pagrindinis principas yra: piešti bangos formą ir ištaškyti piešinį išilgai iš anksto nustatytų vektorių. Taip pat fische turi įtrauktą pažangų dūžių aptikimą, kuris garantuoja didžiulį vizualinį įspūdį.</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">fishBMC pamatā ir savrups skaņas vizualizācijas rīks "fische". Pamatdoma ir zīmēt skaņas viļņus un iztriept tos pa iepriekš noteiktiem vektoriem. Tomēr fische iekļauta arī papildus ritma noteikšanas metode, kas patiešām garantē lielisku vizuālo baudījumu.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">fishBMC е базирано на fische, кое е самостојна алатка за аудио визуелизација. Основниот принцип е: нацртај ја брановата форма и размачкај ја сликата по предефинирани вектори. Но fische исто така имплементира и напредна детекција на ритам, што навистина гарантира неверојатно визуелно искуство.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">fishBMC adalah berasaskan pada fische, alat pengvisualan bunyi berdiri-sendiri. Prinsip asasnya: membentuk gelombang dan dilukis sepanjang vektor pra-takrif. Selain itu fische juga menggabungkan pengesanan beat termaju, yang pasti menjaminkan pengalaman visual yang hebat.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">fishBMC er basert på fische, et selvstendig lydvisualiseringverktøy. Det grunnleggende prinsippet er: tegn bølgeformen og smør tegningen langs forhåndsdefinerte linjer. I tillegg inkluderer fische avansert rytmedeteksjon, noe som garanterer en flott, visuell opplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">FishBMC is gebaseerd op fische, een zelfstandige geluidsvisualisatie tool. Het basis principe is: Teken de golfvorm en veeg de tekening rond ingestelde richtingen. Fische brengt eveneens geavanceerde beatdetectie, wat echt een grote visuele beleving garandeerd.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">fishBMC bazuje na fische, samodzielnym narzędziu do wizualizacji muzyki. Podstawową zasadą jest generowanie wykresu fali i rozmazywanie go wzdłuż zdefiniowanych wektorów. Ponadto fische zawiera również zaawansowaną detekcję rytmu, co gwarantuje wspaniałe wrażenia wizualne.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">fishBMC é baseado no fische, uma ferramenta de visualização de som independente. O princípio básico é: desenhar a forma de onda e esmaecer o desenho ao longo de vetores pré-definidos. Entretanto fische também incorpora detecção avançada de batidas, o que realmente garante uma grande experiência visual.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">O fishBMC é baseado no fische, uma ferramenta autónoma de visualização de sons. O princípio básico é desenhar a onda e deformar o desenho através de vectores pré-definidos. No entanto, o fische também incorpora detecção avançada de ritmos, garantindo uma excelente experiência visual.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">fishBMC основан на fische, являющейся самостоятельной утилитой для визуализации звука. Принцип работы: рисует форму волны и растягивает рисунок вдоль предопределенных векторов. При этом fische предлагает куда более продвинутый алгоритм определения ритма, гарантирующий потрясающее качество визуализации.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">fishBMC je založený na fische, samostatnom nástroji na vizualizáciu. Základným princípom je: nakresliť priebeh signálu a rozmazať kresbu pozdĺž predefinovaných vektorov. Navyše fische obsahuje aj pokročilú detekciu rytmu, čo garantuje skutočný vizuálny zážitok.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">fishBMC temelji na fischeu, samostojnem zvočno vizualizacijskem orodju. Osnovno načelo je: nariši valovni način in ga razmaži vzdolž vnaprej določenih vektorjev. Fische prav tako vključuje tudi napredno zaznavanje ritma, ki resnično zagotavlja odlično vizualno izkušnjo.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">fishBMC är baserat på fische, ett fristående verktyg för ljudvisualisering. Den grundläggande principen är: rita en vågform och smeta ut den längs förbestämda vektorer. fische inkluderar även avancerad rytmdetektion, vilket verkligen garanterar en härlig visuell upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="szl">fishBMC je podparte na fische, ôddziylnym nŏczyniu wizualizacyje źwiynku. Nŏjważniyjsze prawidło to je naszkryflać welã i ôzmazać jã podle nŏjprzōd nasztalowanych wektorōw. Fische ale mŏ tyż zaawansowane ôdkrywaniy szlagōw, co gwarantuje nŏjlepsze widoki.</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">fishBMC дар асоси fische, абзори алоҳида барои таҷассуми садо, амал мекунад. Қоидаи асосӣ: кашидани векторҳои мавҷшакл ва бетартиб. Инчунин fische муайянкунии зарбазании иловагии дарунсохтро таъмин менамояд, ки дар ҳақиқат таҷассуми аҷибро замонат медиҳад.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">fishBMC, fische tabanlı kendi başına çalışabilir bir ses görselleştirme aracıdır. Temel ilkesi: ses biçimini çizmek ve çizimi önceden tanımlı vektörler ile yaymaktır. Ancak fische mükemmel bir görsel deneyimi garantileyen gelişmiş bir ritm algılama da içerir.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">fishBMC 基于一个独立的声音可视化工具 fische。基本原理是：绘制波型并按预定的顶点涂抹。fische 还采用了先进的节拍检测，从而真正保证了绝佳的视觉体验。</description>
    <disclaimer lang="af_ZA">As dit iets breek, bly die stukke joune.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ar_SA">إذا سبب هذا تحطم أى شيئ، فستبقي القطع ملكك!</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Ако "счупи" нещо - парчетата остават за Вас!</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Když se rozbije všechno, ještě ti zůstanou ty kousky.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Os yw'n torri rhywbeth, eich darnau chi ydyn nhw.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da_DK">Hvis dette ødelægger noget, er stykkerne dine.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Für eventuelle Schäden wird keine Haftung übernommen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Αν σπάσει τίποτα, θα σας μείνουν τα κομμάτια.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_AU">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_AR">Si esto rompe algo, los pedazos son tuyos.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Si esto rompe alguna cosa, te puedes quedar con los trozos.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Si esto rompe algo, las piezas siguen siento tuyas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="et_EE">kui see midagi lõhub, siis võid tükid endale jätta</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fa_IR">در قبال خسارات احتمالی مسئولیتی متوجه ما نخواهد بود.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Si ça brise, vous gardez les morceaux.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Si cela casse quelque chose, les pièces restent les vôtres.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Se isto estraga algunha cousa, pode quedar cas pezas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he_IL">אם זה שובר משהו, החתיכות ישארו שלך.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Ako ovo slomi nešto, komadići ostaju vama.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Ha ez összetör valamit attól a darabok még a tieid maradnak.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="id_ID">Kalau ini merusakkan suatu, pecahannya tetap menjadi milik anda.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="is_IS">Ef þetta brýtur eitthvað þá máttu eiga brotin.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it_IT">se si rompe qualcosa, i cocci sono vostri.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ja_JP">これが何かを壊しても、あなたにはかけらが残ります。</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko_KR">발생하는 모든 문제는 사용자의 책임하에 있습니다. </disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Jei tai ką nors sugadins, gabalėliai liks jums.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lv_LV">Ja tas kaut ko saplēš, lauskas paliek tev.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk_MK">Ако било што се расипе, деловите ти преостануваат тебе.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Jika ini merosakkan apa sahaja, bahagian in kekal milik anda.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Hvis noe blir ødelagt, så må du ordne opp selv.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Gebruik maken van deze visualisatie is op eigen risico.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Jeśli to rozbije cokolwiek, kawałki pozostaną Twoje.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">se isto quebrar algo, as peças serão suas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_PT">Se isto quebrar alguma coisa, pode ficar com as peças.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Если что-то сломается, это ваши проблемы.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Ak toto niečo rozbije, kúsky vám ostanú.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl_SI">V primeru, da to karkoli zlomi, koščki ostanejo vaši.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Om detta skulle förstöra något så kan du behålla resterna.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="szl">Jeźli coś sie popsuje, to sie to weź.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tg_TJ">Агар ин чизеро вайрон кунад, шумо қисмҳоро мегиред.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Eğer bu bir şeyi bozarsa, sorumluluk size aittir.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Якщо це щось знищить, шматки лишаються вашими.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">用者责任自负。</disclaimer>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
