<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.album.universal"
       name="Universal Album Scraper"
       version="3.1.3"
       provider-name="Olympia, Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="2.1.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.8.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.albums"
             language="en"
             library="albumuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Universele Skraper vir Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="ast">Scraper universal pa álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Универсален източник за информация за албуми</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Arreplegador universal per àlbums</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro alba</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Crafwr Albymau Cyffredinol</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Universel Scraper til Albummer</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Universeller Scraper für Alben</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Universal Scraper Άλμπουμ</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Scraper universal para álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Albumes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal para Álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Universaalne albumite kraabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Universaali tiedonhakija albumitiedoille</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Scraper universel pour les Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur universel pour les albums</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Scraper Universal para Álbums</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">סקרייפר אוניברסלי עבור אלבומים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Univerzalni sakupljač informacija albuma</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Univerzális album leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Pengais Universal Album</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Universal Scraper fyrir Hljómplötur</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Ricercatore Universale per Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">汎用アルバムスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Universalus albumų skreperis</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Albumu universālais skrāpis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Универзален превземач за Албуми</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Pengikis Universel untuk Album</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Universele Scraper voor Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Universalskraper for album</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Uniwersalny ekstraktor informacji o albumach muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Colector universal para álbuns</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Álbuns</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO"> Scraper universal pentru albume</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Универсальный скрапер для альбомов</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre albumy</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Univerzalni ponudnik informacij o albumih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Universiell albumskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">ஆல்பங்களின் ஒட்டு மொத்தமான சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Albümler için Evrensel Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Універсальний здирач для альбомів</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Trình lấy dữ liệu album từ nhiều nguồn</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">通用音乐专辑信息刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">通用音樂專輯訊息搜刮器</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Hierdie skraper kollekteer inligting vanaf die volgende ondersteunde werwe: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de, terwyl kunswerke gegryp word vanaf: fanart.tv, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifieke inligting wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvaklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval skakels van allmusic en/of amazon.de nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde vanaf allmusic.com en/of amazon.de nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
    <description lang="ast">Esti scraper recueye información de les siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mentanto obtién les imáxenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quier obtener la información pa cada campu. ⏎ ⏎ La gueta inicial faise siempre en MusicBrainz. En casu de que los enllaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de nun tean amestaos na web de MusicBrainz, nun van poder obtenese los campos d'información d' estos dos sitios (magar que ye mui fácil amestar esos enllaces que falten)</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не са налични препратки към allmusic и/или amazon.de на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com и/или amazon.de става невъзможно (добавянето им е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, alhora que agafa art de: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Es pot configurar camp a camp des de quin lloc voleu aquella informació específica. &#10;&#10;La cerca inicial es realitza sempre a MusicBrainz. En el cas que els enllaços d'allmusic i amazon.de no s'afegeixin al lloc MusicBrainz els camps d'allmusic i amazon.de i/o amazon.com no es poden obtenir (tot i que són fàcils d'afegir aquests enllaços restants).</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Tento zdroj získává data z následujících podporovaných stránek: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možno podrobně nastavit, které informace si přejete získat ze kterých stránek.&#10;&#10;Prvotní vyhledání je vžy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že odkaz pro allmusic a nebo amazon.de není přidaný na stránku MusicBrainz, není možné údaje z allmusic.com a amazon.de stáhnout (avšak je velmi snadné tyto chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae'r crafwr yn casglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol:  MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ac amazon.de, tra'n cipio gwaith celf o: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. Mae modd ei osod fesul maes i ddewis pa wefan i gasglu gwybodaeth benodol.&#10;&#10;Bydd y chwilio cychwynnol yn cael ei wneud ar MusicBrainz. Rhag ofn nad yw dolen allmusic wedi ei osod ar wefan MusicBrainz nid oes modd estyn meysydd o allmusic.com (mae'n hawdd gosod y dolenni coll hynny)</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, hvilke sider du ønsker, at få den pågældende information fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic og/eller amazon.de linkene er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de. Es werden dabei Grafiken von den folgenden Seiten geladen: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Von welcher Seite die Informationen geladen werden, kann einzeln konfiguriert werden.⏎ &#10;⏎&#10;Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com και amazon.de, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic ή/και το amazon.de στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com ή/και το amazon.de (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic y/o amazon.de no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com y/o amazon.de no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">See kraabits kogub infot järgmistelt lehtedelt: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de, pilte: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Saad välja kaupa määrata, milliselt lehelt mis infot soovid.&#10;&#10;Esmane otsing tehakse alati saidilt MusicBrainz. Kui MusicBrainz lehele pole allmusic ja/või amazon.de linke lisatud, siis neilt lehtedelt sisu hankida ei saa (puuduvaid linke saad ise lihtsalt lisada).</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja:MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic- ja/tai amazon.de-linkkejä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Ce collecteur utilise les informations des sites suivant : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de et télécharge les artwork depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez spécifier quel site utiliser pour récupérer chaque information.&#10;&#10;Le premier résultat est toujours en provenance de MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site MusicBrainz, les champs de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être traités (il est toutefois très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur recueille des informations depuis les sites pris en charge suivants : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de, alors qu'il récupère les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Il est possible de configurer champ par champ depuis quel site l'information doit être récupérée.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite sur MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où les liens allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site de MusicBrainz, les champs provenant de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être récupérés (il est par contre très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Este scraper obtén a información dende os seguintes sitios: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentres que as ilustracións as obtén dende: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pódese definir dende que sitios se obterá a información específica de cada campo.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial faise sempre en MusicBrainz. No caso de non estar engadidas as ligazón de allmusic e/ou amazon.de no sitio de MusicBrainz, os campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de non se poderán obter (aínda que é moi doado engadir as ligazóns).</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Ovaj sakupljač prikuplja informacije sa sljedećih podržanih stranica: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, dok preuzima omote filmova sa: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Može poredati popis stranica iz kojih želite sakupiti informacije jednu iza druge.&#10;&#10;Pretraga uvijek započinje na MusicBrainzu. U slučaju da allmusic i/ili amazon.de poveznice nisu dodane na MusicBrainz stranicu, polja sa allmusic.com i/ili amazon.de ne mogu se nabaviti (ali je vrlo jednostavno moguće dodati te nedostajuće poveznice).</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A leolvasó szöveges infókat gyűjt a támogatott oldalakról: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, valamint képeket a : fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com-ról. Beállítható hogy honnan, és milyen infót gyűjtsön. A keresés mindig a MusicBrainz-on folyik, de könnyen hozzáadhatjuk a hiányzó találatokat az allmusic.com, vagy az amazon.de-ről.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Pengais ini mengambil informasi dari berbagai situs yang mendukung: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, sembari mengambil artwork dari: fanart.tv, lastfm dan allmusic.com. Ini dapat diatur perbagian dari situ mana informasi tertentu akan diambil.&#10;&#10;Pencarian awal akan dilakukan di MusicBrainz. Apabila tautan dari allmusic dan/atau amazon.de tidak ditambahkan di situs MusicBrainz, bagian dari allmusic.com dan/atau amazon.de tidak dapat ditarik (Namun sangatlah mudah menambahkan tautan tersebut).</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Þessi skafa nær í upplýsingar frá eftirfarandi stöðum sem eru studdir: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, og nær í myndefni frá: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Hægt er að stilla reit fyrir reit hvaðan upplýsingarnar koma.&#10;&#10;Leitin byrjar alltaf á MusicBrainz. Ef allmusic og/eða amazon.de tenglar eru ekki á MusicBrainz veitunni, næst ekki í upplýsingarnar frá allmusic.com og/eða amazon.de (mjög auðvelt að bæta tenglunum við samt).</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Questo ricercatore prende informazioni dai seguenti siti: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentre prende grafica da: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Puoi impostare campo per campo cosa prendere e da dove.⏎ ⏎La ricerca iniziale viene sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. In caso i links a allmusic e/o amazon.de non sono stati messi su MusicBrainz, i campi da questi siti non possono essere recuperati (è molto facile aggiungere quei link, comunque).</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic や amazon.de のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com / amazon.de からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">이 자료수집기는 다음의 사이트에서 정보를 가져옵니다: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de. 아트워크는 다음의 사이트에서 가져옵니다: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. 특정 정보를 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별로 설정할 수 있습니다&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Šis skreperis surenka informaciją iš šių palaikomų puslapių: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ir amazon.de bei atsiunčia iliustracijas iš: fanart.tv, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatytas laukas po laiko, kad nurodyti iš kokio puslapio paimti konkrečią informaciją.&#10;&#10;Pradinė paieška visada atliekama MusicBrainz puslapyje. Jei kartais allmusic ir/raba amazon.de nuorodos nepridėtos į MusicBrainz puslapį, laukai iš allmusic.com ir/arba amazon.de negalės būti gauti (tačiau labai lengva pridėti tas trūkstamas nuorodas).</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.⏎ ⏎ The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Pengikis ini mendapatkan maklumat dari laman tersokong berikut: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com dan amazon.de, manakala ia dapatkan kerja seni dari: fanart.tv, last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ia boleh tetapkan medan mengikut medan supaya anda boleh dapatkan maklumat khusus dari laman tertentu.⏎&#10;⏎&#10;Gelintar awalan sentiasa bermula dengan MusicBrainz. Pautan allmusic dan/atau amazon.de tidak ditambah ke laman MusicBrainz, medan dari allmusic.com dan/atau amazon.de sukar didapati.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde sites: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de. Afbeeldingen worden verzameld van de volgende sites: fanart.tv, Last.fm en allmusic.com. Per veld kan aangegeven worden van welke site je de specifieke informatie wil halen. De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd gedaan van MusicBrainz.&#10;&#10;In het geval dat links naar allmusic en/of amazon.de niet zijn toegevoegd op de MusicBrainz site, kunnen velden niet worden opgehaald bij deze sites. (Het is niet moeilijk om de ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Denne skraperen innsamler informasjon fra følgende nettsteder: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, mens den henter grafikk fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan selv bestemme hvilken kilde du ønsker å hente informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket blir alltid gjort med MusicBrainz. Hvis allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de linker ikke tilgjengelig hos MusicBrainz, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de hentes (dog er det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Ten scraper zbiera informacje z następujących stron: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com oraz amazon.de, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane na MusicBrainz. Gdy linki do allmusic i/lub amazon.de nie są dodane na stronie MusicBrainz, nie można pobrać tych pól z allmusic.com i/lub amazon.de (pomimo to brakujące linki można bardzo łatwo dodać).</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Este colector recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio do qual quer obter as informações. A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso os endereços allmusic e/ou amazon.de não tenham sido adicionados no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta). </description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com și amazon.de. Elementele de grafica sunt accesate din: fanart.tv, last.fm și allmusic.com. Acesta poate fi setat câmp cu câmp pentru ca informatiile colectate sa fie cele dorite.⏎ &#10;⏎ &#10;Căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna pe MusicBrainz. În cazul în care Allmusic și/sau link-ul amazon.de nu sunt adăugate pe MusicBrainz, câmpurile din allmusic.com și/sau amazon.de nu pot fi colectate (este foarte ușor însă de adăugat aceste legături lipsă).</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Данный скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de, при этом получая обложки из: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле можно настроить так, чтобы оно получало желаемую информацию с определенного вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Начальный поиск всегда проводится на  MusicBrainz. Для allmusic и/или amazon.de ссылки на сайт MusicBrainz отсутствуют, поля с allmusic.com и/или amazon.de не могут быть заполнены (добавить пропущенные ссылки очень просто).</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera informácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com a amazon.de, zatiaľ čo umeleckú grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic a/alebo amazon.de nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com a/alebo amazon.de (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com in amazon.de; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedno na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com in/ali amazon.de, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com och amazon.de, och konstverk från: fanart.tv, last.fm och allmusic.com. Det kan anges fält för fält vilken sajt du vill få den specifika informationen.⏎ ⏎ Den initiala sökningen är alltid utförd på MusicBrainz sajt, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de länkarna läggs inte till på MusicBrainz sajten, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de kan inte hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த சுரண்டியானது MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com மற்றும் amazon.de ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். திரை குறும்படங்களை fanart.tv, last.fm மற்றும் allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். ⏎ ⏎ முதன்மை தேடல் எப்போதும் MusicBrainz தான் நடக்கும். allmusic மற்றும் amazon.de சேர்க்கபடாவிட்டால் அவற்றில் இருந்து தகவல்கள் செமிக்கபடமாட்டது (தவறிய இணைப்புகளை சேர்ப்பது மிகவும் எளிது).</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Bu scraper bilgileri toplamak için şu siteleri desteklemektedir:  MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ve amazon.de, çizimleri için ise: fanart.tv, last.fm ve allmusic.com desteklenmektedir. Her bilginin özellikle nereden alınacağını tek tek ayarlayabilirsiniz.&#10;&#10;İlk olarak arama daima MusicBrainz'de yapılır. MusicBrainz'e allmusic ve/veya amazon.de linkleri eklenmemiş olması durumunda allmusic.com'dan ve/veya amazon.de'den ilgili alanlar alınamaz (gerçi bu eksik linkleri eklemek çok kolaydır).</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Здирач збирає інформацію з наступних сторінок: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com та amazon.de, тоді як отримує обкладинки з: fanart.tv, last.fm та allmusic.com.&#10;&#10;Початковий пошук завжди робиться на MusicBrainz. Якщо посилання з allmusic і/або amazon.de не додаються на сторінку MusicBrainz, тоді поля з allmusic.com і/або amazon.de неможливо отримати (однак дуже легко додати ці пропущені посилання).</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Trình này thu thập thông tin từ những site được hỗ trợ như: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de, và lấy ảnh bìa từ các nguồn: fanart.tv, last.fm và allmusic.com. Bạn có thể tùy chỉnh chọn từng thứ riêng biệt để lấy từ site bạn muốn.\n \n Lần tìm kiếm đầu tiên luôn luôn được sử dụng từ MusicBrainz. Trong trường hợp các link allmusic và/hoặc amazon.de không có trên MusicBrainz, các trường từ allmusic.com và/hoặc amazon.de sẽ không thể lấy về được (tuy nhiên rất dễ để tự thêm vào các link này bằng tay).</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com 和 amazon.de，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、last.fm 和 allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从 MusicBrainz 获取。如果 MusicBrainz 网站没有到 allmusic 和/或 amazon.de 的外部链接，则无法获取 allmusic.com 的/或 amazon.de 的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">本搜刮器支援從以下網站取得資訊：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com和amazon.de，並從以下網站取得專輯照片：fanart.tv、last.fm和allmusic.com。您並可以指定每一項內容的來源網站。&#10;&#10;初始搜尋結果總是先從MusicBrainz取得。如果MusicBrainz網站沒有加入到allmusic和/或amazon.de的外部連結，則無法取得allmusic.com的/或amazon.de的信息(當然您能很輕易地加入遺失的連結)。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=133547</forum>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
