<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="visualization.dxspectrum"
  version="1.0.0"
  name="DirectX Spectrum"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_windx="Spectrum_win32dx.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Визуализация представяща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Pyörivä 3D-spektrianalysaattori</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Visualisation montrant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vizualizáció 3D spektrum analizátorral</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 보여지는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">DirectX-visualisatie die een roterende 3D-spectrumanalyse weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazująca obracający się analizator widma w 3D (DirectX)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D (DirectX)</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Vizualizare care afișează un analizator de spectre 3D rotativ</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">显示旋转三维频谱分析图像的可视化效果</summary>
    <description lang="bg">DirectX Spectrum е визуализация изобразяваща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор (рендването се извършва от DirectX). Ротацията е според ритъма на музиката и предизвиква вълнови ефект по спектралната решетка.
Можете да настройвате височината на спектралната лента, скоростта и рендването (solid, points, wire frame). Характеризира се с отличен вид, като същевременно почти не натоварва процесора.</description>
    <description lang="en">DirectX Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in DirectX that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.
It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
   <description lang="es">DirectX Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando renderizado con DirectX que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.
Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Näyttää pyörivän 3D-spektrianalysaattorin, joka liikkuu musiikin tahdissa tuottaen aaltotehosteen spektrikuvaajaan.
Spektripalkin korkeuden, nopeuden, ja piirtotavan (täytetyt, pisteet, ääriviivat) voi asettaa asetuksista. Spectrum on kevyt visualisointi joka näyttää hyvältä.</description>
    <description lang="fr">DirectX Spectrum est une visualisation montrant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation sous DirectX. Il réagit au tempo de la musique créant un effet d'onde sur la grille.
Il possède quelques paramètres pour ajuster la hauteur de barre du spectre, sa vitesse, et le rendu des barres (plein, en points, en fil de fer). Une visualisation légère, agréable à regarder.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A DirectX Spectrum egy olyan vizualizáció ami egy 3D hang spektrum analizátort mutat DirectX segítségével megjelenítve, ami a zene ritmusára mozog egy hullám-effektust képezve a teljes spektrumhálón.
Beállítható a spektrum oszlopok magassága, mozgási sebessége és hogy az oszlopok hogyan jelenjenek meg (teli, pontok, drótváz). Ez egy kis erőforrásigényű vizualizáció ami nagyon jól mutat.</description>
    <description lang="ko">DirectX 스펙트럼은 회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 통해 음악시각화를 보여주며 음악의 비트가 만들어내는 웨이브 효과를 스펙트럼 그리드에 보여줍니다. 설정에서 스펙트럼 바의 높이, 속도, 바의 갯수 (채워짐, 점, 와이어 프레임)를 지정할수 있습니다. 가볍고 CPU를 많이 사용하지 않습니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl">DirectX-spectrum toont een roterende 3D-spectrumanalyse via DirectX. Het beweegt mee met de beat van de muziek, waarbij een golfeffect ontstaat over het spectrumraster.
U kunt de hoogte, snelheid en weergave (vol, stippen, ...) van de spectrumbalk zelf instellen. Deze visualisatie vereist weinig geheugen en belast processor nauwelijks.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazuje obracający się, trójwymiarowy analizator widma, renderowany przy użyciu DirectX. Możesz ustawić wysokość słupków, ich prędkość i wygląd.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O DirectX Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativavo, renderizado em DirectX, que se sincroniza com a batida, criando assin um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.
Pode-se definir a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que utiliza pouco o CPU e com um visual fantástico.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Spectrul DirectX este o vizualizare care afișează un analizator de spectre 3D rotativ randat în DirectX care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii creând un val dea-lungul grilei spectrale.
De asemenea, are setări pentru ajustarea înălțimii bărilor spectrale, a vitezei, și a modului în care bările sunt randate (umplere, puncte, contur). Este o vizualizare cu consum redus al procesorului care arată fantastic de bine.</description>
    <description lang="se">DirectX Spectrum är en visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator renderad i DirectX som rör sig i takt med musiken och skapar vågor av effekter över spektrumområdet.
Det har också inställningar för att justera spektrumhöjden, hastigheten och hur staplarna är renderade (solida, punkter, ramverk) och det är lätt, liten cpuanvändning samt ser bra ut</description>
    <description lang="zh">DirectX Spectrum可视化效果是DirectX渲染的一个旋转的三维频谱分析图像，频谱矩阵随着音乐节拍而象波浪起伏。
你还可以设置频谱棒的高度、变换速度、以及呈现效果（固体、点、框架）。这是一个不错的轻量级，低CPU使用率的可视化效果。</description>
    <platform>windx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
