<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.albums.allmusic.com"
       name="AllMusic"
       version="2.0.1"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="1.8.1"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.0.7"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.albums"
             language="en"
             library="allmusic.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">AllMusic album information</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Alben Scraper für AllMusic.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de Álbums de AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper d'albums musicaux AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">AllMusic.com -albumitietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">AllMusic.com album információk</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">AllMusic-albuminfo</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Informacje o albumach z AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de músicas AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Catalog AllMusic pentru informații albume</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Информация об альбоме из AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="se">AllMusic albuminformation</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">AllMusic音乐专辑信息</summary>
    <description lang="en">Use AllMusic.com to fill your library metadata information.
The allmusic website was created in 1995 as a place for music fans to indulge their passion.
The AMG editorial staff, along with hundreds of expert contributors (all music fanatics in their own right), has made allmusic the most comprehensive music reference source on the planet. They are all dedicated to creating and maintaining the knowledgeable, spirited content that music lovers and industry professionals have come to expect from AMG.
All genres and styles of music are covered here, ranging from the most commercially popular to the most obscure. We critique albums and artists within the context of their own genres - from opera to garage rock to traditional country. This ensures that fans of any style of music can depend on us to keep them up-to-date with their favorite artists as well as introduce them to new sounds.</description>
     <description lang="de">Benutze den AllMusic.com-Scraper um deine Musik-Bibliothek mit Metadaten zu füllen. 
AllMusic.com wurde 1995 gegründet, um Musikliebhabern einen Platz zu geben, Ihre Leidenschaft auszuleben.
Die AMG Redaktion, zusammen mit hunderten Experten (alles Fachmänner auf Ihrem Gebiet) als Beitragende, machte AllMusic.com zur umfangreichsten Quelle für Musikinformationen auf dem Planeten. Sie sind alle engagiert, um den lebhaften Inhalt, welcher von Musikliebhabern und der Musikindustrie von AMG erwartet wird, zu Erstellen und Pflegen. 
Alle Genres und Stile der Musik werden hier abgedeckt, reichend von Mainstream bis zum Underground. Wir schreiben Kritiken zu Alben, im Kontext zu dem passenden Genre - von Oper über Garagen Rock bis hin zu traditioneller Country Musik. Das garantiert Fans jeglicher Musikrichtung, dass sie sich auf uns verlassen können, weil wir sie immer up-to-date über Ihre Liblingskünstler halten und Ihnen auch neue Sounds vorstellen</description>
    <description lang="es">Este scraper utiliza Allmusic.com para rellenar la información de la librería musical.
La página web allmusic fue creada en el 1995 cómo un sitio donde los fans podíaan compartir su pasión por la música.
El equipo de AMG, junto con cuentos de colaboradores expertos (todos ellos fans de la música) han hecho de allmusic uno de los sitios más extensos del planeta. Todos ellos intentan crear y mantener unos contenidos que los amantes de la música y los profesionales del sector obtienen de AMG.
Todos los géneros y estilos musicales tienen cabida, desde los más comerciales hasta los más oscuros. En allmusic se critican los álbumes y los artistas en el entorno que les corresponde - desde opera, pasando por rock hasta country tradicional. Así se asegura que los fans de cualquier estilo de música puedan depender de nosotros para mantenerse al día de las novedades de sus artistas favoritos y descubrir nuevos sonidos.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Käytä AllMusic.com -sivustoa täyttämään kirjastosi metatiedot.
AllMusic.com -sivusto luotiin vuonna 1995 paikaksi, jossa musiikkifanit voivat tyydyttää intohimonsa musiikkiin.
AMG-toimituksen henkilökunta, satojen asiansa tuntevien lahjoittajien kanssa (kaikki musiikkifanaatikot), ovat tehneet AllMusic.com -sivustosta koko planeetan kattavimman musiikkitietolähteen. He ovat kaikki sitoutuneita luomaan ja ylläpitämään asioista perillä olevaa henkevää sisältöä, jota musiikista pitävät ja musiikkialan ammattilaiset odottavat AMG:ltä.
Kaikki musiikin lajityypit ja tyylisuunnat ovat edustettuina täällä, vaihdellen kaupallisesti suosituimmista kaikista huomaamattomimpiin. Me arvostelemme albumit ja esittäjät heidän oman lajityyppinsä sisällä - oopperasta ja autotallirokista aina perinteiseen country-musiikkiin. Tämä varmistaa, että minkä tahansa tyylisuunnan fanit voivat luottaa, että samalla kun pidämme heidät ajan tasalla heidän lempiartististansa, niin esittelemme myös heille uusia äänimaailmoita.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Utiliser AllMusic.com pour la récupération des méta-données.
Le site web AllMusic a été créé en 1995 afin que les fans de musique puissent assouvir leur passion.
L'équipe rédactionnelle d'AMG, forte de ses centaines de contributeurs avisés (tous passionnés de musique à part entière), a fait de AllMusic la source de référence la plus complète de toute la planète. Chacun s'investissant dans la construction et la maintenance d'un contenu aussi passionné et judicieux que tout amoureux de musique ou tout professionnel de l'industrie serait en droit d'attendre d'AMG.
Tous les styles et tous les genres y sont représentés, allant du plus commercial au plus confidentiel. Nous critiquons albums et artistes dans le cadre de leur propre style - de l'opéra à la country traditionnelle en passant par le rock garage. Pour les fans de chaque style musical, c'est l'assurance que nous les tenons informés sur leurs artistes préférés ou à l'apprentissage de nouvelles sonorités.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Az AllMusic.com használata a médiatáradatok feltöltésére. Ez a webhely 1995-ben a zenerajongók szenvedélyének kiszolgálására jött létre.
Az AMG szerkesztői csapata a szakértő közreműködőkkel együtt (mind zenei fanatikus a maga nemében), az allmusic-ot a legátfogóbb zenei információforrássá tették a világon.
Minden létező stílus és zenei irányzat feldolgozásra kerül itt. Kezdve a legpopulárisabbtól a legismeretlenebbig. Mi kritikát mondunk a lemezekről és előadókról, az operától a garázs rock-on át a hagyományos country zenéig. Ez biztosítja, hogy bármely stílus rajongói napra készek legyenek a kedvenc előadóikkal, ugyanakkor az új hangzások is eljussanak hozzájuk.</description>
    <description lang="nl">AllMusic.com gebruiken om de metadata van uw collectie op te halen.
De AllMusic-website werd in 1995 opgericht om muziekfans een online thuis te bieden.
De AMG-redactie heeft van AllMusic het meest complete muzieknaslagwerk gemaakt op deze planeet, mede dankzij de bijdragen van honderden experts. Het is hun missie om de hoogstaande inhoud te blijven aanbieden die muziekliefhebbers en professionals ondertussen van AMG verwachten.
Alle genres en stijlen - of het nu de meest commerciële of de meest obscure zijn - krijgen hier een plaatsje. We bespreken albums en artiesten in de context van hun eigen genre, van opera over garagerock tot traditionele country. Hierdoor kunnen fans van elke muziekstijl bij ons terecht voor de laatste informatie over hun favoriete artiesten, of om nieuwe muziek te leren ontdekken.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Używa AllMusic.com do pobierania informacji o albumach z Twojej muzycznej biblioteki.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Use o AllMusic.com para obter a informação da sua Biblioteca de música. O site allmusic foi criado em 1995 para alimentar a paixão dos fans de música.
O pessoal da redacção da AMG, em conjunto com centenas de especialistas (todos fanáticos por música à sua maneira), tornaram o allmusic o mais completo site de referência musical do planeta. Continuam dedicados a criar e manter o conhecimento, espírito e conteúdos que fans de música e profissionais da indústria se habituaram a obter da AMG.
Todos os géneros e estilos de música podem ser encontrados aqui, desde o mais comercial e popular até à música mais rara. Nós revemos e criticamos álbuns e artistas dentro do contexto do seu género - the ópera a rock de garagem, de pop a música country. Isto assegura que fans de qualquer género podem depender de nós para os manter actualizados sobre os seus artistas favoritos bem como de novos sons.</description>
     <description lang="ro">Folosiți AllMusic.com ca sursă pentru mediateca dumneavoastră.
Site-ul allmusic a fost creat în 1995 ca un loc unde iubitorii de muzică să se răsfețe. Echipa editorială AMG, împreună cu sute de contribuitori experți (niște fanatici după muzică în felul lor), au făcut allmusic cea mai cuprinzătoare sursă de referințe muzicale de pe planetă. Toți sunt dedicați să creeze și să întrețină conținutul pe care iubitorii de muzică și profesioniștii din industrie îl așteaptă de la AMG.
Toate genurile și stilurile de muzică sunt incluse aici, începând de la cele mai populare către cele mai obscure. Noi criticăm albumele și artiștii în contextul genurilor proprii. Toți fanii oricărui stil de muzică pot conta pe noi să îi ținem la curent cu artiștii lor favoriți, dar și să le prezentăm noi cântece.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Используйте AllMusic.com для добавления мета-данных в вашу библиотеку.
Сайт allmusic был создан в 1995 как место для фанатов музыки, где они могли бы удовлетворять свою страсть.
Редакторский состав AMG, вместе с сотнями участников-экспертов (каждый по-своему фанат музыки), сделали allmusic самым полным источником информации о музыке на планете. Все они посвятили себя созданию и поддержке полезного, и познавательного, контента который любители музыки, и профессионалы индустрии, ожидают от AMG.
Здесь представлены все стили и жанры музыки, от самых коммерчески популярных до наиболее неизвестных. Мы критикуем альбомы и исполнителей в контексте их собственного жанра - от оперы и гаражного рока до традиционного кантри. Это обеспечивает то, что фанат любого стиля музыки может полагаться на нас в поддержке актуальности своих познаний о любимом исполнителе и также расширять свои знания.</description>
    <description lang="se">Låt AllMusic.com fylla dina mappar med metadatainformation.
AllMusic's webbplats skapades 1995 som en plats för musikälskare där de kunde njuta av sin passion.
AMG's redaktion har tillsammans med hundratals experter och bidragsgivare, alla musikfanatiker på sina egna sätt, gjort AllMusic till den mest omfattande källan inom musikreferens på den här planeten. De är alla kunniga och engagerade med att skapa och upprätthålla ett innehåll på webbplatsen, som musikälskare och branschfolk förväntar sig av AMG.
Alla genrer och stilar av musik behandlas här, allt från det mest kommersiellt populära till det mest suspekta. De kritiserar album och artister inom ramen för sina egna genrer, allt från opera, garagerock till traditionell countrymusik. Detta säkerställer att alla fans oavsett musikstil kan lita på dem och hålla sig uppdaterade med sina favoritartister och bli introducerade till nya ljud.</description>
    <description lang="zh">从AllMusic.com网站获取音乐资料。
allmusic网站创建于1995年，它是音乐爱好者的乐园。
AMG的编辑和许多专业撰稿人（都是音乐狂热分子）共同把allmusic建成世界上最全面的音乐资料库。他们致力于创造和维护音乐爱好者和业内专业人士期望从AMG得到的知识和精神产品。
这里涵盖了所有的音乐流派和风格，评价从最流行到晦涩和冷门的音乐，讨论不同风格的专辑和艺术家 - 从歌剧到摇滚乐到传统的乡村音乐。力求让所有音乐爱好者都能在这里了解他所喜爱的艺术家最新动态，并为他们介绍新的音乐。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
