<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.albums.allmusic.com"
       name="AllMusic"
       version="1.0.2"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.albums"
             language="en"
             library="allmusic.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">AllMusic album information</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Zenei információk letöltése az AllMusic.com-ról</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de músicas AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">AllMusic音乐刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="en">Use AllMusic.com to fill your libray metadata information.
The allmusic website was created in 1995 as a place for music fans to indulge their passion.
The AMG editorial staff, along with hundreds of expert contributors (all music fanatics in their own right), has made allmusic the most comprehensive music reference source on the planet. They are all dedicated to creating and maintaining the knowledgeable, spirited content that music lovers and industry professionals have come to expect from AMG.
All genres and styles of music are covered here, ranging from the most commercially popular to the most obscure. We critique albums and artists within the context of their own genres - from opera to garage rock to traditional country. This ensures that fans of any style of music can depend on us to keep them up-to-date with their favorite artists as well as introduce them to new sounds.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Az AllMusic.com használata a médiatár adatok feltöltésére, amely webhely 1995-ben jött létre a zenerajongók szenvedélyének kiszolgálására.
Az AMG szerkesztői csapata a szakértő közreműködőkkel együtt (mind zenei fanatikus a maga nemében), az allmusic-ot a legátfogóbb zenei információforrássá tették a világon.
Minden létező stílus és zenei irányzat feldolgozásra kerül itt. Kezdve a legpopulárisabbtól a legismeretelenebbig. Mi kritikát mondunk a lemezekről és előadókról a saját stílusukon belül az operától a garázs rock-on át a hagyományos coutry zenéig. Ez biztosítja, hogy bármely stílus rajongói napra készek legyenek a kedvenc előadóikkal, ugyanakkor az új hangzások is eljussanak hozzájuk.</description>
   <description lang="nl">Gebruik AllMusic.com om de metadata van jouw collectie op te halen.
  De AllMusic website is ontstaan in 1995 als webstek voor echte muziekfans.
The AMG redactie, samen met honderden bijdragende experen (allen muziekfans in hun eigen gebied), hebben van allmusic het meest complete muziek naslagwerk gemaakt op deze planeet.
Alle genres en stijlen worden gedekt, gaande van de meest commerciele tot de meest alternatieve. We bekritiseren albums en artiesten in hun eigen genre, van opera tot garagerock tot traditionele country. Dit maakt dat fans van elke muziekstijl bij ons terecht kunnen voor de laatste informatie rond hun favoriete artiesten of om nieuwe muziek te leren ontdekken.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Use o AllMusic.com para obter a informação da sua Biblioteca de música.
+O site allmusic foi criado em 1995 para alimentar a paixão dos fans de música.
+O pessoal da redacção da AMG, em conjunto com centenas de especialistas (todos fanáticos por música à sua maneira), tornaram o allmusic o mais completo site de referência musical do planeta. Continuam dedicados a criar e manter o conhecimento, espírito e conteúdos que fans de música e profissionais da indústria se habituaram a obter da AMG.
+Todos os géneros e estilos de música podem ser encontrados aqui, desde o mais comercial e popular até à música mais rara. Nós revemos e criticamos álbuns e artistas dentro do contexto do seu género - the ópera a rock de garagem, de pop a música country. Isto assegura que fans de qualquer género podem depender de nós para os manter actualizados sobre os seus artistas favoritos bem como de novos sons.</description>
    <description lang="zh">从AllMusic.com网站获取音乐资料。
allmusic网站创建于1995年，它是音乐爱好者的乐园。
AMG的编辑和许多专业撰稿人（都是音乐狂热分子）共同把allmusic建成世界上最全面的音乐资料库。他们致力于创造和维护音乐爱好者和业内专业人士期望从AMG得到的知识和精神产品。
这里涵盖了所有的音乐流派和风格，评价从最流行到晦涩和冷门的音乐，讨论不同风格的专辑和艺术家 - 从歌剧到摇滚乐到传统的乡村音乐。力求让所有音乐爱好者都能在这里了解他所喜爱的艺术家最新动态，并为他们介绍新的音乐。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
