<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="visualization.projectm"
  version="1.0.1"
  name="projectM"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="projectM.vis"
    library_wingl="projectM_win32.vis"
    library_osx="projectM.vis">
    <settings>
      <userdirs>
        <userdir path="special://profile/addon_data/visualization.projectm"/>
      </userdirs>
    </settings>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">projectM ще ви отведе на пътешествие между звуковите вълни, които чувате</summary>
    <summary lang="en">projectM takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="es">projectM te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">projectM lennättää sinut ääniaaltojen läpi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">projectM vous entraine à travers les ondes sonores que vous écoutez</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">projectM-visualisatie</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A projectM végigrepít a zene hullámain</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">projectM 은 사운드웨이브 속으로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여줍니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">projectM zabiera Cię w niesamowity lot w chmurach aktualnie słuchanych dźwięków</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">O projectM leva-o a voar nas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="se">projectM tar dig flygande genom ljudvågorna du hör</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">projectM带你与声波一起飞翔</summary>
    <description lang="bg">projectM е страхотна визуализация, плод на упорит труд от страна на общността. В света на Unix не съществува нищо по-добро. Потребители, като вас, създават предварително комбинации от настройки, които ползват като модел за визуализацията и така свързват звука с невероятни визуални ефекти. Пробвайте!
Визуализацията projectM е преработка на Milkdrop под лиценза LGPL, основана на OpenGL.
Всичко необходимо на projectM е видео карта с 3D и любимата ви музика.</description>
    <description lang="en">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!
projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL
All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="es">projectM es un fantástico visualizador de música. No hay nada mejor en el universo Unix. La grandeza de projectM proviene del duro trabajo de la comunidad. Usuarios como usted pueden crear ajustes preestablecidos que conecten la música con visualizaciones increibles. ¡Pruébelo!
projectM Visualization es una reimplantación de Milkdrop bajo licencia LGPL y renderizado en OpenGL.
Todo lo que projectM necesita es una tarjeta de vídeo con aceleración 3D y su música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="fi">projectM on uskomaton musiikkivisualisointi, joka on yhteisön kovan työn tulos. Käyttäjät voivat luoda esiasetuksia, jotka yhdistävät musiikin kuviin.
projectM -visualisointi on LGPL-lisensoitu Milkdropin uudelleenimplementointi OpenGL:llä.
projectM tarvitsee vain 3D-kiihdyttävän näytönohjaimen ja lempimusiikkisi.</description>
    <description lang="fr">projectM est un fantastique visualiseur musical. Il n'y a rien de meilleur dans l'univers Unix. L'ampleur de projectM vient du travail énorme de la communauté. Des utilisateurs comme vous peuvent créer des préréglages qui connecteront la musique avec des visuels incroyables. Essayez-le!
Le visualisation projectM est un réalisation sous LGPL de Milkdrop en OpenGL.
Le seul pré-requis de projectM est une carte graphique avec accélération 3D et votre musique.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A projectM egy fantasztikus zenei vizualizáció. Nincs ennél jobb a Unix világban. A projectM különlegessége, hogy egy egész fejlesztői közösség nehéz munkájából jött létre. A felhasználók, mint te egyedi beállításokat hozhatnak létre ami összekapcsolja a zenét a hihetetlen látványelemekkel. Próbáld ki!
A projectM Vizualizáció a Milkdrop újrakódolása LGPL licenc alatt, OpenGL videókártya támogatást használva.
Minden projectM látványbeállításhoz 3D gyorsításra képes videókártya és a kedvenc zenéd szükséges.</description>
    <description lang="ko">projectM은 멋진 음악 시각화입니다. Unix에는 이것보다 좋은것은 없습니다. projectM은 많은 사람들에 의해 개발되었습니다. 여러분과 같은 유저들이 음악을 표현하는 프리셋을 만들었습니다. projectM 음악시각화는 OpenGL에서 작동하도록 Milkdrop를 새로 만든것입니다. 모든 projectM은 3D 가속이 되는 비디오카드와 음악이 필요합니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl">ProjectM is een geweldige muziekvisualisatie. Er bestaat niets beters in de UNIX-wereld. Het success van ProjectM is het resultaat van het harde werk van de XBMC-gemeenschap. U kunt hun eigen presets instellen die muziek linken aan verbluffende visualisaties. Probeer het uit!
ProjectM-visualisatie is beschikbaar onder de LGPL-licentie en is een herimplementatie van Milkdrop (OpenGL). Alles wat projectM vereist is een videokaart met 3D-versnelling en jouw favoriete muziek.</description>
    <description lang="pl">projectM to rewelacyjna wizualizacją muzyki. Nie ma nic lepszego w świecie Unixa. Wspaniałość projectM wywodzi się ciężkiej pracy społeczności. Użytkownicy tacy jak Ty, mogą tworzyć efekty łączące muzykę z niesamowitymi efektami wizualnymi. Przekonaj się!
projectM jest reimplementacją Milkdropa na licencji LGPL i używa OpenGL
Wszystko czego wymaga projectM, to karta graficzna wspierająca akcelerację 3D oraz zasoby Twojej muzyki.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O projectM é um fantástico visualizador de música. Não existe nenhum melhor no mundo Unix. A grandeza do projectM advém do trabalho árduo da comunidade. Utilizadores como você podem criar pré-definições que ligam a música a visualizações incríveis. Experimente!
O visualizador projectM é uma reimplementação do Milkdrop OpenGL sob uma licença LGPL. Tudo o que o projectM necessita é de uma placa gráfica com aceleração 3D e a sua música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="se">projectM är en fantastisk musikvisualisering. Det finns inget bättre i Unixvärlden. projectM's storhet kommer från hårt arbete i gemenskapen. Användare som dig kan skapa förval som anluter musiken med dom otroliga visualiseringarna. Prova det!
projectM visualiseringen är en LGPL återskapning av Milkdrop från OpenGL
Alla projectM kräver ett grafikkort med 3D-acceleration och din favoritmusik.</description>
    <description lang="zh">projectM是一个音乐可视化效果。它是Unix世界中最好的。它的伟大来自于社区的辛苦工作。使用者可以创建预设参数把音乐和难以置信的可视化效果连接起来。试试吧！
projectM可视化效果是用OpenGL按照LGPL协议对Milkdrop的重新实现
projectM所要求的仅是一块有3D加速功能的显卡和你喜爱的音乐。</description>
    <platform>linux osx wingl</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
