<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="visualization.projectm"
  version="1.0.1"
  name="projectM"
  provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="projectM.vis"
    library_wingl="projectM_win32.vis"
    library_osx="projectM.vis">
    <settings>
      <userdirs>
        <userdir path="special://profile/addon_data/visualization.projectm"/>
      </userdirs>
    </settings>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="ar">مشروع M يجعلك تطير بين موحات الصوت التي تسمعها</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">"projectM" ще Ви отведе на пътешествие между звуковите вълни, които чувате</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">projectM et porta volant a través de les ones que escoltes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">projectM s Vámi proletí zvukovými vlnamy, které posloucháte</summary>
    <summary lang="da">projectM tager dig på en flyvetur gennem lydbølgerne du lytter til</summary>
    <summary lang="de">projectM lässt euch durch den Sound fliegen, den Ihr gerade hört</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το projectM σας ταξιδεύει μέσα στα ηχητικά κύματα που ακούτε</summary>
    <summary lang="en">projectM takes you flying through the soundwaves you're hearing</summary>
    <summary lang="es">projectM te lleva volando a través de las ondas que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">projectM te lleva volando a través de las ondas de sonido que estás escuchando</summary>
    <summary lang="et">projectM viib sind lennates läbi helilainete mida kuulad</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">projectM lennättää sinut ääniaaltojen läpi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">projectM vous entraine à travers les ondes sonores que vous écoutez</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">projectM lévao voando a través das ondas de son que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="he">projectM לוקח אותך לתעופה דרך גלי הסאונד שאתה שומע</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">projectM vam omogućuje let kroz zvuk koji čujete</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A projectM végigrepít a zene hullámain</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Með projectM flýgurðu í gegnum hljóðbylgjurnar sem þú heyrir</summary>
    <summary lang="it">projectM ti fa volare tra le onde sonore di ciò che stai ascoltando</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">projectM - 音楽の波の上を飛ぶ</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">projectM 은 사운드웨이브 속으로 날아가는듯한 효과를 보여줍니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">projectM nukelia Jus į nuostabų skrydį virš debesų, ištiesų fantastiškų garsų gausą</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">projectM-visualisatie</summary>
    <summary lang="no">projectM tar deg på en reise flygende gjenom lydbølgene du hører</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">projectM zabiera Cię w niesamowity lot w chmurach aktualnie słuchanych dźwięków</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">O projectM leva-o num voo através das ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">O projectM leva-o a voar nas ondas sonoras que está a ouvir</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">projectM îți oferă o senzație auditivă unică astfel încât simți că zbori printre undele sonore pe care le asculți</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">projectM отправит вас в полёт через звуковые волны, которые вы слышите</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">projektM s Vami poletí zvukovými vlnami, ktoré počúvate</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">projectM vas popelje čez valovanje zvoka kot ga slišite</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">projectM tar med dig på en flygtur genom ljudvågorna du hör</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">projectM забирає вас в політ крізь хвилі музики яку ви слухаєте</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">projectM带你与声波一起飞翔</summary>
    <description lang="ar">مشروع M هو مصورللموسقى رائع. لا شي في العالم أفضل من Unix. عظمة مشروع M تأتي من عمل المجتمع الجاد. يستطيع مستخدمون مثلك إنشاء مسبقات تتصل بالموسقى لصور رائعة. جربه&#10;تصوير مشروع M &#10;كل ما يتطلبه مشروع M هو كرت شاشة بتسارع 3D و موسيقاك المفضلة.</description>
    <description lang="bg">"projectM" е страхотна визуализация, плод на упорит труд от страна на общността. В света на Unix не съществува нищо по-добро. Потребители, като Вас, създават предварително комбинации от настройки, които се ползват като модел за визуализацията и така свързват звука с невероятни визуални ефекти. Пробвайте!&#10;Визуализацията "projectM" е преработка на Milkdrop под лиценза LGPL, основана на OpenGL.&#10;"projectM" изисква видео карта с 3D ускорение и любимата Ви музика.</description>
    <description lang="ca">El projectM és un visualitzador de música impressionant. No hi ha res millor al món Unix. La grandesa de projectM prové del dur treball de la comunitat. Els usuaris com tu poden crear predefinits que connecten la música amb visualitzacions increibles. Prova-ho!&#10;La Visualització projectM és una re-implementació en LGPL de Milkdrop baix OpenGL&#10;Tot el que projectM requereix és una tarja amb acceleració 3D i la teva música preferida.</description>
    <description lang="cs">projectM je úžasný hudební vizualizér. Ve světě Unixu neexistuje nic lepšího. Velikost projectuM pochází z tvrdé práce komunity. Uživatelé, jako jste vy, mohou vytvářet předvolby, které spojují hudbu s fantastickými vizuálními zážitky. Zkuste to!&#10;projectM vizualizace je LGPL reimplementace Milkdropu pod OpenGL.&#10;Vše co projectM vyžaduje je grafická karta s 3D akcelerací a Vaše oblíbená hudba.</description>
    <description lang="da">projectM er en fantastisk musikvisualiserer. Der findes intet bedre i Unix-verdenen. projectMs storhed kommer fra brugersamfundets hårde arbejde. Brugere, som dig selv, kan skabe forudindstillinger som forbinder musik med utrolige visualiseringer. Prøv det!&#10;projectM Visualization er en LGPLed reimplementation af Milkdrop under OpenGL.&#10;Alt hvad projectM kræver er et grafikkort med 3D-acceleration og din yndlingsmusik.</description>
    <description lang="de">projectM ist eine unglaublicher Musik-Visualisierung. In der Unix-Welt gibt es nichts besseres. Die Einzigartigkeit kommt durch die harte Arbeit der Community. User wie du können "Presets" schreiben, welche sich mit der Musik verbinden. Versuche es selber!&#10;projectM ist die LGPL Reimplementierung von Milkdrop als OpenGL Variante&#10;Alles was prjectM benötigt ist eine Grafikkarte mit 3D Beschleunigung und deine Lieblingmusik</description>
    <description lang="el">Το projectM είναι ένας φοβερός μουσικός οπτικοποιητής. Δεν υπάρχει τίποτα καλύτερο στον κόσμο του Unix. Το μεγαλείο του projectM πηγάζει από τη σκληρή δουλειά της κοινότητας. Χρήστες όπως εσείς μπορούν να δημιουργήσουν προρυθμίσεις συνδέοντας τη μουσική με απίστευτες απεικονίσεις. Δοκιμάστε το!&#10;Η Οπτικοποίηση projectM αποτελεί μία νέα LGPL υλοποίηση του Milkdrop υπό το OpenGL&#10;Το μόνο που απαιτείται από το projectM είναι μία κάρτα γραφικών με τρισδιάστατη (3D) επιτάχυνση, και την αγαπημένη σας μουσική.</description>
    <description lang="en">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="es">projectM es un fantástico visualizador de música. No hay nada mejor en el universo Unix. La grandeza de projectM proviene del duro trabajo de la comunidad. Usuarios como usted pueden crear ajustes preestablecidos que conecten la música con visualizaciones increibles. ¡Pruébelo!&#10;projectM Visualization es una reimplantación de Milkdrop bajo licencia LGPL y renderizado en OpenGL.&#10;Todo lo que projectM necesita es una tarjeta de vídeo con aceleración 3D y su música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">projectM es un visualizador de música sorprendente. No hay nada mejor en el mundo de Unix. La grandeza de projectM proviene del duro trabajo de la comunidad. Usuarios como tú pueden crear preaujstes que conectan la música con increíbles imágenes. Inténtalo!&#10;La visualización projectM es una reimplementación en LGPL de Milkdrop bajo OpenGL.&#10;Todo lo que projectM necesita es una tarjeta de video con aceleración 3D y tu música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="et">projectM on äge muusika visuaal. Unixi maailmas pole midagi paremat. projectM'i suurus on saavutatud kogukonna ühise raske töö tulemusena. Kasutajad nagu sina saavad luua eelseadeid, mis ühendavad muusika imeliste visualidega. Proovi seda! projectM visualiseerimine on litsentseeritud (LGPL) uuskasutus Milkdrop'ist OpenGL keskkonnas.&#10;Ainus mida projectM vajab, on 3D kiirendusega videokaart ja sinu lemmikmuusika.</description>
    <description lang="fi">projectM on uskomaton musiikkivisualisointi, joka on yhteisön kovan työn tulos. Käyttäjät voivat luoda esiasetuksia, jotka yhdistävät musiikin kuviin.&#10;projectM -visualisointi on LGPL-lisensoitu Milkdropin uudelleenimplementointi OpenGL:llä.&#10;projectM tarvitsee vain 3D-kiihdyttävän näytönohjaimen ja lempimusiikkisi.</description>
    <description lang="fr">projectM est un fantastique visualiseur musical. Il n'y a rien de meilleur dans l'univers Unix. L'ampleur de projectM vient du travail énorme de la communauté. Des utilisateurs comme vous peuvent créer des préréglages qui connecteront la musique avec des visuels incroyables. Essayez-le!&#10;Le visualisation projectM est un réalisation sous LGPL de Milkdrop en OpenGL.&#10;Le seul pré-requis de projectM est une carte graphique avec accélération 3D et votre musique.</description>
    <description lang="gl">projectM é unha impresionante Visualización de música. Non hai nada mellor no mundo Unix.  A grandeza de projectM ven da dura xeira da comunidade. Usuarios coma vostede poden crear preconfiguracións que conectan a música con incribles visualizacións. Próbeo!&#10;A Visualización projectM é unha reimplementación de Milkdrop empregando OpenGL e con licencia LGPL.&#10;Todo o que precisa projectM é unha tarxeta gráfica con aceleración 3D e a súa música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="he">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="hr">projectM je fenomenalan glazbeni visualizer. Ne postoji ništa bolje u svijetu Unix-a. Veličina projectM-a dolazi zbog predanosti njegove zajednice. Korisnici kao što ste vi, mogu stvoriti zadane postavke koje povezuju muziku i nevjerovatne vizuale. Isprobajte! projectM Vizualizacija je LGPL reimplementacija Milkdrop-a pod OpenGL&#10;Sve što projectM zahtjeva je video kartica sa 3d ubrzanjem i vašu omiljenu glazbu.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A projectM egy fantasztikus zenei vizualizáció. Nincs ennél jobb a Unix világban. A projectM különlegessége, hogy egy egész fejlesztői közösség nehéz munkájából jött létre. A felhasználók, mint te egyedi beállításokat hozhatnak létre ami összekapcsolja a zenét a hihetetlen látványelemekkel. Próbáld ki!&#10;A projectM Vizualizáció a Milkdrop újrakódolása LGPL licenc alatt, OpenGL videókártya támogatást használva.&#10;Minden projectM látványbeállításhoz 3D gyorsításra képes videókártya és a kedvenc zenéd szükséges.</description>
    <description lang="is">projectM er frábær myndskreyting. það er ekkert betra í Unix heiminum. Gæði projectM koma til vegna framlags samfélagsins.Notendur eins og þú geta búið til forstillingar sem tengja tónlist við ótrúlega myndræna upplifun. Prófaðu!⏎ projectM myndskreyting er LGPL útgáfa af Milkdrop með OpenGL⏎ Allt sem projectM þarfnast er skjákort með þrívíddar hraðli  3D og uppáhalds tónlistin þín.</description>
    <description lang="it">projectM è un incredibile visualizzazione musicale. E' il meglio del mondo Unix. La grandezza di projectM proviene dal duro lavoro della comunità. Gli utenti come te possono creare preset che connetto la musica con incredibili grafiche. Provalo!&#10;projectM è una reimplementazione LGPL di Milkdrop sotto OpenGL&#10;Tutti i projectM richiedono una scheda video con accelerazione 3D e la tua musica preferita.</description>
    <description lang="ja">projectM is an awesome music visualizer. There is nothing better in the world of Unix. projectM's greatness comes from the hard work of the community. Users like you can create presets that connect music with incredible visuals. Try it!&#10;projectM Visualization is an LGPL'ed reimplementation of Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;All projectM requires is a video card with 3D acceleration and your favorite music.</description>
    <description lang="ko">projectM은 멋진 음악 시각화입니다. Unix에는 이것보다 좋은것은 없습니다. projectM은 많은 사람들에 의해 개발되었습니다. 여러분과 같은 유저들이 음악을 표현하는 프리셋을 만들었습니다. projectM 음악시각화는 OpenGL에서 작동하도록 Milkdrop를 새로 만든것입니다. 모든 projectM은 3D 가속이 되는 비디오카드와 음악이 필요합니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">ProjectM yra išskirtinė muzikos vizualizacija. Nėra nieko geriau, Unix pasaulyje. ProjectM spindesys tai sunkus darbas bendruomenėje. Naudotojai, tokie kaip Jūs galite sukurti ir suderinti muziką su puikiais vizualizacijos  efektais. Sužinokite!&#10;ProjectM yra įgyvendinimas iš Milkdrop pagal LGPL licenciją, ir naudoja OpenGL&#10;Viskas ko reikia projectM tai vaizdo plokštės su 3D akceleracija (greitėjimu) ir geros muzikos.</description>
    <description lang="nl">ProjectM is een geweldige muziekvisualisatie. Er bestaat niets beters in de UNIX-wereld. Het success van ProjectM is het resultaat van het harde werk van de XBMC-gemeenschap. U kunt hun eigen presets instellen die muziek linken aan verbluffende visualisaties. Probeer het uit!&#10;ProjectM-visualisatie is beschikbaar onder de LGPL-licentie en is een herimplementatie van Milkdrop (OpenGL). Alles wat projectM vereist is een videokaart met 3D-versnelling en jouw favoriete muziek.</description>
    <description lang="no">projectM er en awesome musikk visualisering. Der er ingenting bedre i Unix verden. projectM er så flott takket være et hardt arbeidende felleskap. Brukere som deg kan lage forhåndsinnstillinger som kobler musikk med utrolige visualiseringer. Prøv det!&#10;projectM visualiseringen er en LGPL reinplimentasjon av Milkdrop under OpenGL&#10;Alt projectM trenger er et grafikkort med 3D støtte og din favoritt musikk</description>
    <description lang="pl">projectM to rewelacyjna wizualizacją muzyki. Nie ma nic lepszego w świecie Unixa. Wspaniałość projectM wywodzi się ciężkiej pracy społeczności. Użytkownicy tacy jak Ty, mogą tworzyć efekty łączące muzykę z niesamowitymi efektami wizualnymi. Przekonaj się!&#10;projectM jest reimplementacją Milkdropa na licencji LGPL i używa OpenGL&#10;Wszystko czego wymaga projectM, to karta graficzna wspierająca akcelerację 3D oraz zasoby Twojej muzyki.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O projectM é uma visualização fantástica de música. Não há melhor no mundo Unix. A grandeza do projectM advém do trabalho árduo da comunidade. Qualquer utilizador pode criar pré-selecções que combinam a música com visualizações incríveis. Experimente!&#10;O visualizador projectM é uma reimplementação do Milkdrop OpenGL sob uma licença LGPL. Tudo o que o projectM precisa é de uma placa gráfica com aceleração 3D e a sua música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O projectM é um fantástico visualizador de música. Não existe nenhum melhor no mundo Unix. A grandeza do projectM advém do trabalho árduo da comunidade. Utilizadores como você podem criar pré-definições que ligam a música a visualizações incríveis. Experimente!&#10;O visualizador projectM é uma reimplementação do Milkdrop OpenGL sob uma licença LGPL. Tudo o que o projectM necessita é de uma placa gráfica com aceleração 3D e a sua música favorita.</description>
    <description lang="ro">projectM este un plugin uimitor. Nu există nimic mai bun în lumea Unix. Măreția projectM vine din munca întregii comunități. Utilizatori ca și tine pot crea presetări care conectează muzica cu vizualizări incredibile. Încearcă și tu!&#10;Vizualizarea projectM este o reimplementare LGPL a lui Milkdrop sub OpenGL.&#10;Tot ceea ce necesită projectM este o placă video cu accelerare 3D și muzica ta favorită.</description>
    <description lang="ru">projectM удивительным образом визуализирует музыку. В мире Unix нет ничего лучше. projectM является результатом напряжённой работы сообщества. Пользователи могут создавать наборы настроек, которые объединяют музыку и невероятные визуальные эффекты. Попробуйте сами!⏎&#10;Визуализация projectM представляет собой LGPL-реализацию Milkdrop на основе OpenGL⏎&#10;Всё, что требуется для визуализации — это видеокарта с 3D-ускорением и любимая музыка.</description>
    <description lang="sk">projektM je úžasný hudobný vizualizér. Vo svete Unixu neexistuje nič lepšie. Veľkosť projectM pramení z tvrdej práce komunity. Užívatelia ako ty vytvárajú Predvoľby, ktoré spájajú hudbu s fantastickými vizualizáciami. Vyskúšaj to![CR] projectM vizualizácie sú LGPL implementáciou vizualizácií Milkdrop s použitím OpenGL.[CR] Jediné čo projectM potrebuje je grafickú kartu s 3D akceleráciou a Vašu obľúbenú hudbu.</description>
    <description lang="sl">projectM je glasbeni vizualizator. Nič ni boljšega v svetu Unixa. Veličina ProjectM izhaja iz garanja skupnosti. Uporabniki, kot si lahko ustvarite prednastavitve, ki povezujejo glasbo z neverjetno vizualizacijo. Poskusi!&#10;projectM Vizualizacija je LGPL'ed reimplementacija od Milkdrop v okviru OpenGL. Za delovanje projectM je potrebna grafična kartica s 3D pospeševanjem in vašo najljubšo glasbo.</description>
    <description lang="sv">projectM är en fantastisk musikvisualisering. Det finns inget bättre i Unixvärlden. projectM's storhet kommer från gemenskapens hårda jobb. Användare som du kan skapa förval som förenar musiken med otroliga visualiseringar. Prova det!&#10;projectM visualisering är en LGPL-implementation av Milkdrop i OpenGL&#10;Alla projectM kräver ett grafikkort med 3D-acceleration och din favoritmusik.</description>
    <description lang="zh">projectM是一个音乐可视化效果。它是Unix世界中最好的。它的伟大来自于社区的辛苦工作。使用者可以创建预设参数把音乐和难以置信的可视化效果连接起来。试试吧！&#10;projectM可视化效果是用OpenGL按照LGPL协议对Milkdrop的重新实现&#10;projectM所要求的仅是一块有3D加速功能的显卡和你喜爱的音乐。</description>
    <platform>linux osx wingl</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
