<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="screensaver.xbmc.builtin.dim"
       name="Dim"
       version="1.0.26"
       provider-name="Team-Kodi">
  <extension point="xbmc.ui.screensaver" library=""/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Sluimerskerm wat jou skerm verdof</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">شاشة توقف تمكن من تظليم الشاشة</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Ахоўнік экрану што зацямняе экран</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Скрийнсейвър, който затъмнява екрана</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Estalvi de pantalla que enfosqueix la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Spořič obrazovky, který ztmaví vaši obrazovku</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Arbedwr sgrin sy'n pylu eich sgrin</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Pauseskærm som dæmper din skærm</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Bildschirmschoner zum Abdunkeln des Bildschirmes</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Προφύλαξη οθόνης που σκιάζει την οθόνη σας</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Screensaver that dims your screen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Screensaver that dims your screen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Screensaver that dims your screen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Screensaver that dims your screen</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Un protector de pantalla que oscurece su pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Un salvapantallas que atenúa tu pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Protector de pantalla que obscurece su pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Ekraanisäästja, mis hämardab ekraani</summary>
    <summary lang="eu_ES">Pantaila iluntzen duen pantaila-babeslea</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">محافظ تاریک کننده صفحه نمایش</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Ruudun himmennys</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Un économiseur d'écran qui baisse la luminosité de votre écran</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Un économiseur qui assombrit votre écran</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">O  protector de pantalla atenúa a súa pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">שומר מסך אשר מעמעם את המסך</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Čuvar zaslona koji zatamnjuje vaš zaslon</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Képernyővédő ami elhalványítja a képernyőt</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Penyelamat layar yang meredupkan layar Anda</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Skjáhvíla sem lækkar birtustigið á skjánum</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Salvaschermo che oscura lo schermo</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">画面を薄暗くするスクリーンセーバー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">화면을 어둡게 하는 화면 보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Ekrano vaizdas pritemdantis foną Jūsų ekrane</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Ekrānsaudzētājs, kas aptumšo jūsu ekrānu</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Заштита што го стемнува екранот</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Penyelamat skrin yang memalapkan skrin anda</summary>
    <summary lang="my_MM">သင်၏စကရင်ကို မှေးမှိန်စေသော Screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Skjermsparer som demper skjermen din</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Schermbeveiliging die je scherm dimt</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Wygaszacz ekranu przyciemniający ekran</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Protetor de tela que escurece sua tela</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Protector de ecrã que obscurece o seu ecrã</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Protector ecran ce întunecă ecranul</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Заставка, постепенно затемняющая экран</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Šetrič obrazovky, ktorý zatemní  Vašu obrazovku </summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Ohranjevalnik zaslona, ki zatemni zaslon</summary>
    <summary lang="sq_AL">Ruajtës ekrani, që errëson ekranin</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Чувар екрана који затамни ваш екран.</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">En skärmsläckare som tonar ned din skärm</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Пардаи экран бо таъсири «Пардаи экрани камнур»</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">สกรีนเซฟเวอร์ที่หรี่หน้าจอของคุณ</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Ekranınızı karanlıklaştıran ekran koruyucu</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Проста заставка що затемняє екран.</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Trình bảo vệ màn hình này làm mờ màn hình của bạn</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">淡出屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">讓螢幕變暗的螢幕保護程式</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Die Verdof sluimerskerm is 'n eenvoudige sluimerskerm wat jou skerm verdof (uit vaag) tot 'n stelbare waarde tussen 20 en 100%</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">Dim عبارة عن شاشة توقف  تمكن من  تظليم (صورة خافتة) الشاشة إلى قيمة قابلة للتحديد بين 20 و 100%</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a setable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Скрийнсейвърът "Dim" затъмнява екрана, до стойност, която Вие определяте предварително (между 20 и 100%).</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">L'estalvi de pantalla Dim és un estalvi de pantalla simple que enfosquirà (fos en negre) la seva pantalla a un valor que es pot configurar entre 20 i 100%.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Jednoduchý spořič obrazovky Ztmavení ztmaví (začerní) vaši obrazovku podle nastavitelné hodnoty mezi 20 a 100%.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae arbedwr sgrin Dim yn arbedwr sgrin syml sy'n pylu (tywyllu) eich sgrin i werth gosodadwy rhwyg 20 a 100%.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Dæmpningspauseskærmen er en simpel pauseskærm, der dæmper (nedtoner) din skærm til en valgfri værdi mellem 20 og 100%.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Der Dimmer-Bildschirmschoner ist ein einfacher Bildschirmschoner, welcher den Bildschirm auf einen benutzerdefinierten Wert zwischen 20 und 100% abdunkelt.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Η προφύλαξη οθόνης Dim είναι μία απλή προφύλαξη η οποία σκιάζει την οθόνη σας σε μία τιμή που μπορεί να ρυθμιστεί μεταξύ 20 και 100%.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a setable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a setable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a setable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="en_US">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a settable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Dim es un sencillo protector de pantalla que oscurece la misma. El valor es configurable entre el 20% y el 100%.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Dim es un sencillo salvapantallas que atenúa tu pantalla. El valor es configurable entre el 20% y el 100%.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">El protector de pantalla de obscurecimiento, es un protector simple que obscurece (fade out) su pantalla en un valor entre 20 y 100%</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">Lihtne ekraanisäästja, mis hämardab (tumestab) ekraani vastavalt valitud väärtusele vahemikus 20 kuni 100%.</description>
    <description lang="eu_ES">Dim  %20 eta %100 artean zure pantaila iluntzeko (belztu) konfiguratu daitekeen pantaila babesle soil bat da.</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">محافظ تاریک کننده صفحه نمایش یک محافظ ساده است که نور صفحه نمایش را (بطور تدریجی) تا سطح تعریف شده بین 20 تا 100% کم می کند.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Dim on yksinkertainen näytönsäästäjä joka himmentää ruudun valitulle tasolle välillä 20-100%.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">L'économiseur Dim est un économiseur d'écran simple qui abaissera la luminosité de votre écran à une valeur réglable entre 20 à 100 %.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">L'économiseur Dim est un simple économiseur qui assombrira votre écran. L'assombrissement est paramétrable de 20 à 100 %.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">O  protector de pantalla de Atenuación atenuará a súa pantalla nun valor configurábel entre o 20% e o 100%</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">שומר המסך Dim הוא שומר מסך פשוט אשר מעמעם את המסך לערך מוגדר בין 20% ל־100%.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Dim čuvar zaslona je jednostavan čuvar zaslona koji će zatamniti (postepeno isčeznuti) vaš zaslon na odabranu vrijednost između 20 i 100% .</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A Dim képernyővédő egyszerűen elhalványítja a képernyőt egy előre beállítható sötétségi szintre 20 és 100% között.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Penyelamat layar Redup adalah penyelamat layar sederhana yang akan meredupkan (membuat gambar menjadi hilang) layar Anda ke suatu nilai yang dapat diatur antara 20 dan 100%.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Dim er einföld skjáhvíla sem lækkar birtustigið á skjánum um stillanlegt gildi á milli 20 og 100%</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">'Dim' è un semplice salvaschermo che diminuirà la luminosità del tuo schermo ad un valore (regolabile) tra il 20% ed il 100%.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">Dim はシンプルなスクリーンセーバーで、画面を(フェードアウトで)薄暗くします。値は20%から100%まで設定可能です。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">Dim 화면보호기는 화면을 어둡게(페이드 아웃)하는 간단한 화면 보호기 입니다. 어둡게 하는 정도를 20-100%사이에서 설정할 수 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Pritemdyta ekrano užsklanda yra paprasta ekrano užsklanda,katra pamažu (pamažu mažinant vaizdo ryškumą) jūsų ekrano ryškuma sumažins nuo 20 iki 100%.</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Aptumsuma ekrānsaudzētājs ir vienkāršs ekrānsaudzētājs, kas aptumšo (padara tumšāku) jūsu ekrānu līdz uzstādāmai robežai starp 20 un 100%.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">ДИМ Заштитата на екран е едноставно стемнување на екранот, може да се одбере вредност помеѓу 20 и 100%</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Penyelamat skrin malap adapah penyelamat skrin ringkas yang memalapkan (lenyapkan) skrin anda kepada nilai boleh ditetap diantara 20 hingga 100%.</description>
    <description lang="my_MM">Dim screensaver သည် ရိုးရှင်းသော Screensaver တစ်ခုဖြစ်သည်။ ၎င်းသည် သင်၏ စခရင် ကို ၂၀% မှ ၁၀၀% အတွင်း မှေးမှိန်သွားအောင်ပြုလုပ်လိမ့်မည်</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Dim er en enkel skjermsparer som demper skjermen din til en justerbar verdi mellom 20-100%</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">De Dim-schermbeveiliging is een eenvoudige schermbeveiliging die uw scherm geleidelijk dimt. U kan een waarde gaande van 20 tot 100% instellen.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Wygaszacz Przyciemnienie jest prostym wygaszaczem, który płynnie przyciemnia (wygasza) ekran do ustawionego poziomu między 20-100%.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O Dim ("Escurecer") é um protetor de tela simples que diminui a intensidade da luz de sua tela (escurece), com um valor selecionável entre 20 e 100%.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">O protetor de ecrã "Obscurecer" é um protector simples que obscurece (diminui a intensidade luminosa) o seu ecrã para um valor definível entre 20 e 100%.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Dim este un protector ecran simplu care va întuneca (reduce intensitatea luminii) ecranului dumneavoastră la o valoare configurabilă cuprinsă între 20 și 100% .</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Эта заставка постепенно затемняет изображение на экране до заданного значения (от 20% до 100%).</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">"Dim" šetrič obrazovky je jednoduchý šetrič, ktorý zatemní Vašu obrazovku podľa nastavenia v rozsahu 20 až 100%.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Dim je enostaven ohranjevalnik zaslona, ki zatemni zaslon do izbrane svetlosti med 20 in 100%.</description>
    <description lang="sq_AL">Errësuesi i ekranit është një mbrojtës i thjeshtë ekrani, i cili errëson (zbeh) ekranin tuaj në varësi të një vlere të axhustueshme nga 20 deri në 100%. </description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Dim чувар екрана је једноставан чувар екрана који ће затамнети (постепено) ваш екран на подешену вредност између 20 и 100%.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Detta är en enkel skärmsläckare som tonar ned ljusstyrkan på din skärm till ett angivet värde mellan 20 och 100%</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Ин пардаи экран бо таъсири «Пардаи экрани камнур» хеле осон мебошад, ки сатҳи камнури экранро то дараҷае байни 20% ва 100% тағйир меёбад.</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">สกรีนเซฟเวอร์หรี่หน้าจอเป็นสกรีนเซฟเวอร์แบบพื้นฐานที่ช่วยหรี่หน้าจอของคุณซึ่งสามารถตั้งค่าการหรี่หน้าจอได้ตั้งแต่ 20% ถึง 100%</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Dim ekran koruyucusu, değeri %20 ila %100 arasında ayarlanabilen ve ekranınızı karanlıklaştıran (silikleştiren) basit bir ekran koruyucudur.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Ця заставка затемняє екран (зменшує яскравість) на встановлене значення в межах від 20% до 100%.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Trình bảo vệ Dim là trình bảo vệ đơn giản để làm tối (mờ dần) màn hình của bạn theo giá trị được sắp đặt từ 20 cho đến 100%.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">淡出屏保是一个简单的屏幕保护程序，它使你的屏幕显示内容变暗（淡出效果），暗化度可在20%至100%之间调节。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Dim </description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
