<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="screensaver.xbmc.builtin.dim"
       name="Dim"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <extension point="xbmc.ui.screensaver" library=""/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Sluimerskerm wat jou skerm verdof</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">شاشة توقف تمكن من تظليم الشاشة</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Screensaver that dims your screen</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Скрийнсейвър, който затъмнява екрана</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Estalvi de pantalla que enfosqueix la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Spořič obrazovky, který ztmaví vaši obrazovku</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Pauseskærm, der dæmper din skærm</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Bildschirmschoner zum Abdunkeln des Bildschirmes</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Προφύλαξη οθόνης που σκιάζει την οθόνη σας</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Screensaver that dims your screen</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Un salvapantallas que oscurece tu pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Protector de pantalla que obscurece su pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Ekraanisäästja, mis hämardab ekraani</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Ruudun himmennys</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Un économiseur qui assombrit votre écran</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">O Gardapantallas atenúa a súa pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="he">שומר מסך אשר מעמעם את המסך</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Čuvar zaslona koji će zatamniti ekran</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Képernyővédő ami elhalványítja a képernyőt</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Skjáhvíla sem lækkar birtustigið á skjánum</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Salvaschermo che oscura lo schermo</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">画面を暗くするスクリーンセーバー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">화면을 어둡게 하는 화면보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Ekrano vaizdas pritemdantis foną Jūsų ekrane</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Schermbeveiliging die je scherm dimt</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Skjermsparer som dimmer skjermen din</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wygaszacz ekranu przyciemniający ekran</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Protecção que esvanece o seu ecrã</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Protetor de tela que diminui a intensidade luminosa de sua tela</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Screensaver ce întunecă ecranul</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Заставка, постепенно затемняющая экран</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Šetrič obrazovky, ktorý zatemní  Vašu obrazovku </summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Ohranjevalnik zaslona, ki zatemni zaslon</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Ruajtës ekrani, që errëson ekranin</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">En skärmsläckare som tonar ned din skärm</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Проста заставка що затемняє екран.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">淡出屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">讓螢幕變暗的螢幕保護程式</summary>
    <description lang="af">Die Verdof sluimerskerm is 'n eenvoudige sluimerskerm wat jou skerm verdof (uit vaag) tot 'n stelbare waarde tussen 20 en 100%</description>
    <description lang="ar">Dim عبارة عن شاشة توقف  تمكن من  تظليم (صورة خافتة) الشاشة إلى قيمة قابلة للتحديد بين 20 و 100%</description>
    <description lang="be">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a setable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="bg">Скрийнсейвърът "Dim" затъмнява екрана, до стойност, която Вие определяте предварително (между 20 и 100%).</description>
    <description lang="ca">L'estalvi de pantalla Dim és un estalvi de pantalla simple que enfosquirà (fos en negre) la seva pantalla a un valor que es pot configurar entre 20 i 100%.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Jednoduchý spořič obrazovky Ztmavení ztmaví (začerní) vaši obrazovku podle nastavitelné hodnoty mezi 20 a 100%.</description>
    <description lang="da">Dæmpningspauseskærmen er en simpel pauseskærm, der dæmper(toner ud) din skærm til en valgfri værdi mellem 20 og 100%.</description>
    <description lang="de">Der Dimmer-Bildschirmschoner ist ein einfacher Bildschirmschoner, welcher den Bildschirm auf einen benutzerdefinierten Wert zwischen 20 und 100% abdunkelt.</description>
    <description lang="el">Η προφύλαξη οθόνης Dim είναι μία απλή προφύλαξη η οποία σκιάζει την οθόνη σας σε μία τιμή που μπορεί να ρυθμιστεί μεταξύ 20 και 100%.</description>
    <description lang="en">The Dim screensaver is a simple screensaver that will dim (fade out) your screen to a setable value between 20 and 100% .</description>
    <description lang="es">Dim es un sencillo salvapantallas que oscurece tu pantalla. El valor es configurable entre el 20% y el 100%.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">El protector de pantalla de obscurecimiento, es un protector simple que obscurece (fade out) su pantalla en un valor entre 20 y 100%</description>
    <description lang="et">Lihtne ekraanisäästja, mis hämardab (tumestab) ekraani vastavalt valitud väärtusele vahemikus 20 kuni 100%.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Dim on yksinkertainen näytönsäästäjä joka himmentää ruudun valitulle tasolle välillä 20-100%.</description>
    <description lang="fr">L'économiseur Dim est un simple économiseur qui assombrira votre écran. L'assombrissement est paramétrable de 20 à 100 %.</description>
    <description lang="gl">O gardapantallas de Atenuación é un gardapantallas simple que atenuará o súa pantall a un valor configurable entre o 20% e o 100%</description>
    <description lang="he">שומר המסך Dim הוא שומר מסך פשוט אשר יעמעם (fade out) את המסך לערך מוגדר בין 20% ל-100%</description>
    <description lang="hr">Dim  je jednostavni čuvar zaslona koji će zatamniti ekran (postepeno se gubiti) na odabranu vrijednost između 20 i 100% .</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Dim képernyővédő egyszerűen elhalványítja a képernyőt egy előre beállítható sötétségi szintre 20 és 100% között.</description>
    <description lang="is">Dim er einföld skjáhvíla sem lækkar birtustigið á skjánum um stillanlegt gildi á milli 20 og 100%</description>
    <description lang="it">'Dim' è un semplice salvaschermo che diminuirà la luminosità del tuo schermo ad un valore (regolabile) tra il 20% ed il 100%.</description>
    <description lang="ja">Dim はその名の通りシンプルなスクリーンセーバーで、画面をフェードアウトしながら暗くします。値は20%から100%まで設定可能です。</description>
    <description lang="ko">Dim 화면보호기는 화면을 어둡게(페이드 아웃)하는 간단한 화면보호기 입니다. 어둡게 하는 정도를 20-100%사이에서 설정할 수 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Pritemdyta ekrano užsklanda yra paprasta ekrano užsklanda,katra pamažu (pamažu mažinant vaizdo ryškumą) jūsų ekrano ryškuma sumažins nuo 20 iki 100%.</description>
    <description lang="nl">De Dim-schermbeveiliging is een eenvoudige schermbeveiliging die uw scherm geleidelijk dimt. U kan een waarde gaande van 20 tot 100% instellen.</description>
    <description lang="no">Dim er en enkel skjermsparer som dimer skjermen din til en justerbar verdi mellom 20 og 100%</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten wygaszacz ekranu płynnie przyciemnia ekran po upływie ustawionego czasu. Przyciemnienie jest ustawialne w przedziale 20-100%.</description>
    <description lang="pt">A protecção de ecrã esvanecente permite-lhe diminuir a intensidade luminosa do seu ecrã. Pode ser configurada para valores entre 20 e 100%.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O protetor de tela Dim é um screensaver  que diminui a intensidade da luminosidade (fade out) de sua tela, com um valor selecionável entre 20 e 100%</description>
    <description lang="ro">Dim este un screensaver simplu care va întuneca (reduce intensitatea luminii) ecranului dumneavoastră la o valoare configurabilă cuprinsă între 20 și 100% .</description>
    <description lang="ru">Эта заставка постепенно затемняет изображение на экране до заданного значения (от 20% до 100%).</description>
    <description lang="sk">"Dim" šetrič obrazovky je jednoduchý šetrič, ktorý zatemní Vašu obrazovku podľa nastavenia v rozsahu 20 až 100%.</description>
    <description lang="sl">Dim je enostaven ohranjevalnik zaslona, ki postopoma zatemni zaslon do izbrane svetlosti med 20 in 100%.</description>
    <description lang="sq">Errësuesi i ekranit është një mbrojtës i thjeshtë ekrani, i cili errëson (zbeh) ekranin tuaj në varësi të një vlere të axhustueshme nga 20 deri në 100%. </description>
    <description lang="sv">Detta är en enkel skärmsläckare som tonar ned ljusstyrkan på din skärm till ett angivet värde mellan 20 och 100%</description>
    <description lang="uk">Ця заставка затемняє екран (зменшує яскравість) на встановлене значення в межах від 20% до 100%.</description>
    <description lang="zh">淡出屏保是一个简单的屏幕保护程序，它使你的屏幕显示内容变暗（淡出效果），暗化度可在20%至100%之间调节。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Dim </description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

