<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="screensaver.rsxs.plasma"
  version="1.0.26"
  name="Plasma"
  provider-name="mogumbo, Team-Kodi">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.ui.screensaver"
    library_linux="Plasma.xbs"
    library_osx="Plasma.xbs"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Seker die tweede mees psigedeliese sluimerskerm ooit</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">ربما شاشة التوقف الثانية الأكثر هدوء على الإطلاق</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Напэўна, другі найбольш псіхадэлічны ахоўнік экрану</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Вероятно вторият най-халюциногенен скрийнсейвър</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Probablement el segon estalvi de pantalla més psicodèlic mai creat</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Pravděpodobně druhý nejdivočejší šetřič obrazovky všech dob</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Mwy na thebyg yr ail arbedwr sgrin mwyaf seicadelig</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Formodentlig den anden mest psykedeliske pauseskærm nogensinde</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Wahrscheinlich der zweit-psychodelischste Bildschirmschoner überhaupt</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Πιθανότατα η δεύτερη πιο ψυχεδελική προφύλαξη οθόνης που έγινε ποτέ</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Probablemente el segundo protector de pantalla más psicodélico jamás creado</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Probablemente el segundo salvapantallas más psicodélico jamás creado</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Probablemente el segundo protector de pantalla más psicodélico</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Arvatavasti teine kõige psühhedeelsem ekraanisäästja, mis iial tehtud</summary>
    <summary lang="eu_ES">Ziurrenik inoizko bigarren pantaila-babesle psikodelikoena</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">این محافظ صفحه نمایش احتمالا مقام دوم را در توهم زایی دارد</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Todennäköisesti toiseksi psykedeelisin näytönsäästäjä koskaan</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Probablement le deuxième économiseur d'écran le plus psychédélique</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Probablement le deuxième économiseur d'écran le plus psychédélique jamais créé</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Probabelmente o segundo protector de pantalla máis psicodélico.</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">כנראה שומר המסך השני בדירוג הפסיכדליות</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Vjerojatno drugi najveći psihodelični čuvar zaslona ikad</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">A második legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Mungkin screensaver paling psikedelik nomor dua yang pernah ada</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Líklega í öðru sæti yfir klikkuðustu skjáhvíluna</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Probabilmente il secondo salvaschermo più psichedelico di sempre</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">世界で2番目にサイケなスクリーンセーバー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">아마도 지금까지 두번째로 가장 환상적인 화면 보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Tikriausiai antra labiausiai psichodelinė ekrano užsklanda pasaulyje.</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Iespējams viens no vispsihodēliskākajiem ekrānsaudzētājiem pasaulē</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Можеби втора нај психоделична заштита на екран</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Berkemungkinan penyelamat skrin kedua yang paling psikedelik</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Helt sikkert den nest mest psykedeliske skjermspareren som finnes</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Waarschijnlijk de op één na meest psychedelische schermbeveiliging ooit</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Prawdopodobnie drugi, najbardziej psychodeliczny wygaszacz na świecie</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Provavelmente a segunda mais psicodélica proteção de tela já vista</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Este é provavelmente o segundo melhor protector de ecrã psicadélico de sempre</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Probabil al doilea cel mai năucitor protector ecran care a existat vreodată</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Наверное, вторая из самых психоделических заставок в мире</summary>
    <summary lang="si_LK">පෙනෙන විදියට සදා දෙවන මහත් අධිචිත්ත වේගී තිරමෙහෙකරු</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Pravdepodobne druhý najviac hypnotizujúci šetrič obrazovky vôbec</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Gotovo drugi najbolj psihadelični ohranjevalnik zaslona na svetu</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Вероватно други нај психоделичнији чувар екрана икада</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Troligen den näst mest psykedeliska skärmsläckaren någonsin.</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Эҳтимол аст, ки имрӯз дар тамоми ҷаҳон ин пардаи экран ҷои дуюмро мегирад</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Muhtemelen insanı hayallere sürükleyen en iyi ikinci ekran koruyucu</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Напевно, друга серед найбільш психоделічних заставок</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Xứng đáng làm trình bảo vệ màn hình gây ảo giác mạnh thứ hai</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">或许是排名第二的迷幻效果屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">可能是有史以來第二最夢幻的螢幕保護程式保護程式</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Seker die tweede mees psigedeliese sluimerskerm wat bestaan. Verbeel jou net al daai kleure wat rond beweeg.</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">ربما شاشة التوقف الثانية الأكثر هدوء في الوجود. فقط حاول تصوير هذه الألوان المتحركة .</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Вероятно вторият по сила халюциногенен скрийнсейвър създаван някога. Просто се опитайте да съзрете всички тези цветове.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Probablement el segon estalvi de pantalla més psicodèlic que existeix. Intenta imaginar tots aquests colors movent-se.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Pravděpodobně druhý nejdivočejší šetřič obrazovky všech dob. Zkuste si představit všechny ty poletující barvy.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mwy na thebyg yr ail arbedwr sgrin mwyaf seicadelig sy'n bod. Ceisiwch ddychmygu'r holl liwiau na'n symud o gwmpas.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Formodentlig den anden mest psykedeliske pauseskærm, der eksisterer. Forestil dig alle de farver, der bevæger sig omkring.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Wahrscheinlich der zweit-psychodelischste Bildschirmschoner, den es gibt. Versuche doch alle diese Farben, die sich umher bewegen, festzuhalten.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Πιθανότατα η δεύτερη πιο ψυχεδελική προφύλαξη οθόνης που υπάρχει. Απλά προσπαθήστε να φανταστείτε όλα αυτά τα χρώματα σε κίνηση.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colours moving around.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colours moving around.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colours moving around.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Probablemente el segundo protector de pantalla más psicodélico que existe. Solo intente imaginarse todos esos colores moviéndose.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Probablemente el segundo salvapantallas más psicodélico que existe. Intente imaginarse todos esos colores moviéndose.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Probablemente el segundo protector de pantallas más psicodélico.  Solo trate de captar todos los colores moviéndose alrededor.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">Arvatavasti ajaloo teine kõige psühhedeelsem ekraanisäästja. Püüa lihtsalt kujutleda kõiki neid värve, mis ringi liiguvad.</description>
    <description lang="eu_ES">Ziurrenik existitzen den bigarren pantaila-babesle psikodelikoena. Saiatu kolore guzti horiek mugitzen irudikatzen.</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">این محافظ احتمالا در میان تمام محافظ های موجود مقام دوم را در توهم زایی دارد. سعی کنید همه این رنگ هایی را که در حال حرکت هستند، نگه دارید.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Todennäköisesti toiseksi psykedeelisin olemassa oleva näytönsäästäjä. Kuvittelepa vain kaikki nuo värit lentelemässä ympäriinsä.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Probablement le deuxième économiseur d'écran le plus psychédélique de l'histoire. Essayez seulement d'imaginer toutes ces couleurs en mouvement.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Probablement le deuxième économiseur d'écran le plus psychédélique de l'histoire. Essayez seulement d'imaginer toutes ces couleurs en mouvement.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Probabelmente o segundo protector de pantalla máis psicodélico do mundo. Tan só probe a imaxinarse todas esas cores movéndose ó redor.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">כנראה שומר המסך השני בדירוג הפסיכדליות שקיים כיום. פשוט נסו לדמיין את כל הצבעים האלו נעים ממקום למקום.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Vjerojatno drugi najveći psihodelični čuvar zaslona koji postoji. Samo pokušajte zamisliti sve te boje koje se gibaju okolo.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Valószínüleg a második legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő ami létezik. Csak képzeld el mindezt a színkavalkádot mozogni.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Mungkin screensaver paling psikedelik nomor dua yang pernah ada. Coba bayangkan warna-warni itu bergerak ke sana kemari.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Líklega í öðru sæti yfir klikkuðustu skjáhvíluna sem til er. Reyndi bara að ímynda þér alla þessa liti á hreyfingu.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Probabilmente il secondo salvaschermo più psichedelico di sempre. Prova semplicemente a guardare tutti quei colori che si muovono.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">아마도 존재하는 두번째로 가장 환상적인 화면 보호기. 모든 색깔들이 움직이는 것을 상상해보세요.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Turbūt antra labiausiai psichodelinė ekrano užsklanda pasaulyje. Išbandykite ją ir pamatysite judančių spalvų šventę.</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Iespējams viens no vispsihodēliskākajiem ekrānsaudzētājiem pasaulē. Pamēģiniet, lai gūtu priekšstatu par krāsu kustību un plūsmu visapkārt.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Можеби втора нај психоделична заштита на екран. Само обидете се да ги согледате сите тие бои кои се движат.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Berkemungkinan penyelamat skrin kedua yang paling psikedelik yang ada. Hanya cuba gambarkan semua warna yang bergerak disekitar.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Helt sikkert den nest mest psykadeliske skjermsparern i verden. Bare prøv å se for deg alle de fargene som beveger seg rundt.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Waarschlijnlijk de op één na meest psychedelische schermbeveliging ooit. Probeer u het voor te stellen: al die kleuren die door elkaar lopen.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Prawdopodobnie drugi, najbardziej psychodeliczny wygaszacz na świecie. Spróbuj i zobacz ferie poruszających się barw.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Provavelmente a segundo mais psicodélica proteção de tela existente.  Experimente ver todas essas cores se movimentando ao redor da tela.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Provavelmente, o segundo melhor protector de ecrã psicadélico de sempre. Experimente visualizar todas as cores a moverem-se.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Probabil al doilea cel mai năucitor protector ecran care a existat vreodată. Doar încercați să vă imaginați toate acele culori mișcându-se.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Просто попробуйте представить себе все цвета в движении.</description>
    <description lang="si_LK">පෙනෙන විදියට සදා පවතින දෙවන මහත් අධිචිත්ත වේගී තිරමෙහෙකරු.වටේ තිබෙන එම සියළු වර්ණ ඡායාරූප කිරීමට උත්සාහ කිරීම පමණයි. </description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Pravdepodobne druhý najviac hypnotizujúci šetrič obrazovky aký vôbec existuje. Iba si skúste predstaviť všetky tie farby pohybujúc sa okolo.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Gotovo drugi najbolj psihadelični ohranjevalnik zaslona na svetu. Samo predstavljajte si vse te barve, ki letijo naokrog.</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Вероватно други нај психоделичнији чувар екрана који је икада постојао. Само пробајте да замислите све те боје како шетају наоколо.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Troligen den näst mest psykedeliska skärmsläckaren som existerar. Bara tänk dig alla färgerna som rör på sig.</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Эҳтимол аст, ки имрӯз дар тамоми ҷаҳон ин пардаи экран ҷои дуюмро мегирад. Танҳо тасаввур кунед, ки чӣ қадар зебо ҳамаи рангҳояш бозӣ мекунанд.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Muhtemelen insanı hayallere sürükleyen en iyi ikinci ekran koruyucu. Ekranda dolaşan tüm renkleri seyretmeye çalışın.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Напевно, друга серед найбільш психоделічних заставок. Лише уявіть усі ці переливи кольорів.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Đây có thể là trình bảo vệ màn hình gây ảo giác mạnh thứ hai tại thời điểm này. Hãy thử xem các hình ảnh tạo nên từ các màu sắc di chuyển khắp nơi</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">或许是排名第二的迷幻效果屏幕保护程序。你将看到所有颜色满处乱飞。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">可能是現存第二最夢幻的螢幕保護程式。快來嘗試想像一下所有移動中的色彩變化。</description>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
