<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="screensaver.rsxs.plasma"
  version="1.0.0"
  name="Plasma"
  provider-name="mogumbo, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.ui.screensaver"
    library_linux="Plasma.xbs"
    library_osx="Plasma.xbs"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Seker die tweede mees psigedeliese sluimerskerm ooit</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">ربما شاشة التوقف الثانية الأكثر هدوء على الإطلاق</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Вероятно вторият най-халюциногенен скрийнсейвър</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Probablement el segon estalvi de pantalla més psicodèlic mai creat</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Pravděpodobně druhý nejdivočejší šetřič obrazovky všech dob</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Formodentlig den anden mest psykedeliske pauseskærm nogensinde</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Wahrscheinlich der zweit-psychodelischste Bildschirmschoner überhaupt</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Πιθανότατα η δεύτερη πιο ψυχεδελική προφύλαξη οθόνης που έγινε ποτέ</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Probablemente el segundo salvapantallas más psicodélico jamás creado</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Probablemente el segundo protector de pantalla más psicodélico</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Arvatavasti teine kõige psühhedeelsem ekraanisäästja, mis iial tehtud</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Todennäköisesti toiseksi psykedeelisin näytönsäästäjä koskaan</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Probablement le deuxième économiseur d'écran le plus psychédélique jamais créé</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Probablemente o segundo gardapantallas máis psicodélico endexamáis.</summary>
    <summary lang="he">כנראה השומר מסך הפסיכודאלי השני הפופאלי ביותר</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Vjerojatno drugi najveći ikad psihodelični čuvar zaslona</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A második legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Probabilmente il secondo salvaschermo più psichedelico di sempre</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">世界で2番目にサイケなスクリーンセーバー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">아마도 지금까지 두번째로 가장 환상적인 화면보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Tikriausiai antra labiausiai psichodeline ekrano uzsklanda pasaulyje.</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Waarschijnlijk de op één na meest psychedelische schermbeveiliging ooit</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Helt sikkert den nest psykadeliske skjermsparern som fins</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Prawdopodobnie drugi, najbardziej psychodeliczny wygaszacz na świecie</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Provavelmente, o segundo melhor protector de ecrã psicadélico de sempre.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Provavelmente o segundo protetor de tela mais psicodélico</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Probabil al doilea cel mai năucitor screensaver care a existat vreodată</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Наверное, вторая из самых психоделических заставок в мире</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Förmodligen den näst psykedeliska skärmsläckaren</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Pravdepodobne druhý najviac hypnotizujúci šetrič obrazovky vôbec</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Drugi najbolj psihadelični ohranjevalnik zaslona na svetu.</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Troligen den näst mest psykedeliska skärmsläckaren någonsin.</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Напевно, друга серед найбільш психоделічних заставок</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">也许是排名第二的迷幻效果屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <description lang="af">Seker die tweede mees psigedeliese sluimerskerm wat bestaan. Verbeel jou net al daai kleure wat rond beweeg.</description>
    <description lang="ar">ربما شاشة التوقف الثانية الأكثر هدوء في الوجود. فقط حاول تصوير هذه الألوان المتحركة .</description>
    <description lang="be">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="bg">Вероятно вторият по сила халюциногенен скрийнсейвър създаван някога. Просто се опитайте да съзрете всички тези цветове.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Probablement el segon estalvi de pantalla més psicodèlic que existeix. Intenti imaginar tots aquests colors movent-se.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Pravděpodobně druhý nejdivočejší šetřič obrazovky všech dob. Zkuste si představit všechny ty poletující barvy.</description>
    <description lang="da">Formodentlig den anden mest psykedeliske pauseskærm, der eksisterer. Forestil dig alle de farver, der bevæger sig omkring.</description>
    <description lang="de">Wahrscheinlich der zweit-psychodelischste Bildschirmschoner, den es gibt. Versuche doch alle diese Farben, die sich umher bewegen, festzuhalten.</description>
    <description lang="el">Πιθανότατα η δεύτερη πιο ψυχεδελική προφύλαξη οθόνης που υπάρχει. Απλά προσπαθήστε να φανταστείτε όλα αυτά τα χρώματα σε κίνηση.</description>
    <description lang="en">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="es">Probablemente el segundo salvapantallas más psicodélico que existe. Intente imaginarse todos esos colores moviéndose.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Probablemente el segundo protector de pantallas más psicodélico.  Solo trate de captar todos los colores moviéndose alrededor.</description>
    <description lang="et">Arvatavasti ajaloo teine kõige psühhedeelsem ekraanisäästja. Püüa lihtsalt kujutleda kõiki neid värve, mis ringi liiguvad.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Todennäköisesti toiseksi psykedeelisin olemassa oleva näytönsäästäjä. Kuvittelepa vain kaikki nuo värit lentelemässä ympäriinsä.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Probablement le deuxième économiseur d'écran le plus psychédélique de l'histoire. Essayez seulement d'imaginer toutes ces couleurs en mouvement.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Probalemente o segundo gardapantallas máis psicodélico na existencia. Tan só probe a imaxinarse todas esas cores movéndose ó redor.</description>
    <description lang="he">כנראה השומר מסך הפסיכודאלי השני הפופאלי ביותר. נסה לדמיין את כל הצבעים האלה זזים כל הזמן</description>
    <description lang="hr">Vjerojatno drugi najveći ikad psihodelični čuvar zaslona koji postoji. Samo Pokušajte zamisliti sve te boje koje se gibaju okolo.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Valószínüleg a második legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő ami létezik. Csak képzeld el mindezt a színkavalkádot mozogni.</description>
    <description lang="it">Probabilmente il secondo salvaschermo più psichedelico di sempre. Prova semplicemente a guardare tutti quei colori che si muovono.</description>
    <description lang="ja">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="ko">아마도 존재하는 두번째로 가장 환상적인 화면보호기. 모든 색깔들이 움직이는 것을 상상해보세요.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Turbut antra labiausiai psichodeline ekrano uzsklanda pasaulyje. Isbandykite ja ir pamatysite judanciu spalvu svente.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Waarschlijnlijk de op één na meest psychedelische schermbeveliging ooit. Probeer u het voor te stellen: al die kleuren die door elkaar lopen.</description>
    <description lang="no">Helt sikkert den nest psykadeliske skjermsparern i verden. Bare prøv å fårestill deg alle de fargene som beveger seg rundt.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Prawdopodobnie drugi, najbardziej psychodeliczny wygaszacz na świecie. Spróbuj i zobacz ferię poruszających się barw.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Provavelmente, o segundo melhor protector de ecrã psicadélico de sempre. Experimente-o e veja todas as cores movendo-se livremente.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Provavelmente, o segundo mais psicodélico screensaver existente.  Experimente-a para ver todas as cores moverem-se livremente.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Probabil al doilea cel mai năucitor screensaver care a existat vreodată. Doar încercați să vă imaginați toate acele culori mișcându-se.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Просто попробуйте представить себе все цвета в движении.</description>
    <description lang="se">Förmodligen den näst psykedeliska skärmsläckaren som finns. Försök bara att uppfatta alla färger som rör sig runt och runt.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Pravdepodobne druhý najviac hypnotizujúci šetrič obrazovky aký vôbec existuje. Iba si skúste predstaviť všetky tie farby pohybujúc sa okolo.</description>
    <description lang="sl">Drugi najbolj psihadelični ohranjevalnik zaslona na svetu. Samo predstavljajte si vse te barve, ki letijo naokrog.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Troligen den näst mest psykedeliska skärmsläckaren som existerar. Bara tänk dig alla färgerna som rör på sig.</description>
    <description lang="uk">Напевно, друга серед найбільш психоделічних заставок. Лише уявіть усі ці переливи кольорів.</description>
    <description lang="zh">也许是排名第二的迷幻效果屏幕保护程序。你将看到所有颜色满处乱飞。</description>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

