<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="screensaver.rsxs.plasma"
  version="1.0.0"
  name="Plasma"
  provider-name="mogumbo, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.ui.screensaver"
    library_linux="Plasma.xbs"
    library_osx="Plasma.xbs"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Вероятно вторият най-халюциногенен скрийнсейвър</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver ever</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Probablemente el segundo salvapantallas más psicodélico jamás creado</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Todennäköisesti toiseksi psykedeelisin näytönsäästäjä koskaan</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Probablement le second écran de veille le plus psychédélique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A második legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">아마도 두번째로 가장 사이키델릭한 화면보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Waarschijnlijk de op één na meest psychedelische schermbeveiliging ooit</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Prawdopodobnie drugi, najbardziej psychodeliczny wygaszacz na świecie</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Provavelmente a segunda mais psicadélica protecção de ecrã</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Förmodligen den näst psykedeliska skärmsläckaren</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">也许是排名第二的迷幻效果屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Вероятно вторият по сила халюциногенен скрийнсейвър създаван някога. Просто се опитайте да съзрете всички тези цветове.</description>
    <description lang="en">Probably the second most psychedelic screensaver in existence. Just try to picture all those colors moving around.</description>
    <description lang="es">Probablemente el segundo salvapantallas más psicodélico que existe. Intente imaginarse todos esos colores moviéndose.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Todennäköisesti toiseksi psykedeelisin olemassa oleva näytönsäästäjä. Kuvittelepa vain kaikki nuo värit lentelemässä ympäriinsä.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Probablement le second économiseur le plus psychédélique de l'histoire. Essayez seulement d'imaginer toutes ces couleurs en mouvement.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Valószínüleg a második legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő ami létezik. Csak képzeld el mindezt a színkavalkádot mozogni.</description>
    <description lang="ko">아마도 이세상에 존재하는것중 두번째로 가장 사이키델릭한 화면보호기. 오만가지 색상이 돌아다니는걸 상상해보세요.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Waarschlijnlijk de op één na meest psychedelische schermbeveliging ooit. Probeer u het voor te stellen: al die kleuren die door mekaar lopen.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Prawdopodobnie drugi, najbardziej psychodeliczny wygaszacz na świecie. Spróbuj i zobacz ferię poruszających się barw.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Provavelmente a segunda mais psicadélica protecção de ecrã de sempre. Experimente-a para ver todas as cores moverem-se livremente.</description>
    <description lang="se">Förmodligen den näst psykedeliska skärmsläckaren som finns. Försök bara att uppfatta alla färger som rör sig runt och runt.</description>
    <description lang="zh">也许是排名第二的迷幻效果屏幕保护程序。你将看到所有颜色满处乱飞。</description>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
