<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="screensaver.rsxs.euphoria"
  version="1.0.26"
  name="Euphoria"
  provider-name="mogumbo, Team-Kodi">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.ui.screensaver"
    library_linux="Euphoria.xbs"
    library_osx="Euphoria.xbs"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Omtrent so psigedelies soos sluimerskerm kan kom</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">حول الحصول على مهدء كشاشة التوقف</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Падобны на псіхадэлічны ахоўнік экрану</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Колкото халюциногенен може да бъде един скрийнсейвър</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Quant al més psicodèlic dels estalvis de pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Nejdivočejší šetřič obrazovky všech dob</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Mor seicadelig ag y mae modd bod</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Omtrent så psykedelisk som en pauseskærm kan blive.</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">So psychedelisch wie ein Bildschirmschoner nur sein kann</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Όσο πιο ψυχεδελική μπορεί να είναι μία προφύλαξη οθόνης</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">About as psychedelic as screensavers get</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">About as psychedelic as screensavers get</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">About as psychedelic as screensavers get</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">About as psychedelic as screensavers get</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Tan psicodélico como un protector de pantalla pueda serlo</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">El más psicodélico de los salvapantallas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Tan psicodélico como cualquier protector de pantalla debería</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Nii psühhedeelne kui üks ekraanisäästja olla saab</summary>
    <summary lang="eu_ES">Pantaila-babesleetatik psikodelikoena</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">نهایت توهم زایی یک محافظ صفحه نمایش</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Mahdollisesti kaikkein psykedeelisin näytönsäästäjä</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Il y a pas d'économiseur d'écran plus psychédélique</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Difficilement plus psychédélique comme économiseur d'écran</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Máis ou menos tan psicodélico como o pode ser un protector de pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">זהו שומר המסך הפסיכדלי ביותר שיכול להיות</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Psihodeličan koliko čuvar zaslona može biti </summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">A legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Sepsikedelik mungkin dari sebuah screensaver</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Eins geggjuð og skjáhvíla getur orðið</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Quanto di più psichedelico possa essere un salvaschermo</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">スクリーンセーバーはここまでサイケになれる</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">싸이키델릭 화면 보호기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Psihodelinė užsklanda nunešanti stoga</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Cik nu vien psihodēlisks ekrānsaudzētājs var būt</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Најпсиходелична заштита на екран</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Perihal as psychedelic as screensavers get</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Så psykadelisk som en skjermsparer kan bli</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Een meer psychedelische schermbeveiliging vindt u niet</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Tak psychodeliczny jak tylko się da</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Protetor de Tela Psicodélico</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Um protector de ecrã mais psicadélico do que este? Impossível.</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Un protector ecran cât se poate de năucitor</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Самая психоделическая в мире заставка</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Tak psychodelický ako to len ide</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Najbolj psihadelični ohranjevalnik zaslona</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Психоделичан колико то један чувар екрана може да буде.</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Ungefär så psykedelisk som en skärmsläckare kan bli</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Дар тамоми ҷаҳон ин пардаи экран аз ҳама беҳтарин аст</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">İnsanı hayallere sürükleyen bir ekran koruyucu</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Настільки психоделічна наскільки можливо для заставки</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Tạo ra ảo giác mạnh nhất mà trình bảo vệ màn hình có thể có được</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">最具迷幻效果的屏幕保护程序</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">最具夢幻效果的螢幕保護程式</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Die is omtrent so psigedelies soos sluimerskerm kan kom. mogumbo het gedink sy Plasma beskermer was heel voor in die koor, maar die een sal jou maag selfs meer laat draai. Jy beter een van daardie vlug siekte sakke kry voor jy te lank na hierdie een staar.</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">هذا حول الحصول على مهدء كشاشة التوقف. اعتقد موغمبو أن شاشة توقف البلازمة خاصته في قمة الجدول, لكن هذا مقرف أكثر. الأفضل أن تجد أحد أكياس الغثيان قبل أن تنظر لهذا لوقت طويل.</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Точно колкото може един скрийнсейвър. mogumbo смяташе, че неговият "Plasma saver" е върхът, но този е по-смущаващ. Препоръчвам Ви да вземете една торбичка/леген, преди да зазяпате в скрийнсейвъра по-дълго отколкото трябва.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Aquest és probablement el més psicodèlic dels estalvis de pantalla. mogumbo va pensar que el seu estalvi Plasma estava al capdamunt, però aquest és més nauseabund. Serà millor que agafis una bossa per als marejos si has d'estar molta estona mirant-lo.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Asi nejdivočejší šetřič obrazovky všech dob.  Použití plazmového šetřiče bývalo vrcholem, ale tento spořič je ještě více zneklidňující. Připravte si pytlíky na zvracení pokud se jej rozhodnete sledovat příliš dlouho.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mor seicadelig ag y mae modd bod. Roedd mogumbo'n meddwl fod ei arbedwr Plasma ar frig y rhestr, ond mae hwn hyd yn oed yn fwy troëdig. Gwell dod o hyd i fag salwch cyn edrych ar hwn yn rhy hir.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Dette er omtrent så psykedelisk som en pauseskærm kan blive. Mogumbo troede hans Plasma-pauseskærm var i toppen af skalaen, men denne er endnu mere kvalmende. Du må hellere finde en papirpose, inden du kigger alt for længe på denne.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">In etwa so ​​psychedelisch wie ein Bildschirmschoner nur sein kann. mogumbo dachte, sein Plasma-Bildschirmschoner wäre bereits abstoßend, aber dieser hier ist noch verabscheuenswürdiger. Kram' besser schon mal eine Kotztüte hervor, bevor Du diesen Bildschirmschoner zu lange anstarrst.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Αυτή είναι η πιο ψυχεδελική προφύλαξη οθόνης που υπάρχει. Ο mogumbo  νόμιζε ότι η Plasma προφ. οθόνης του ήταν η κορυφαία, αλλά αυτή είναι ακόμα πιο μπερδεμένη. Καλύτερα να βρείτε μία από εκείνες τις σακούλες για τη ναυτία προτού την κοιτάξετε για πολλή ώρα.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este es probablemente el más psicodélico de los protectores de pantalla. mogumbo pensó que su protector de Plasma estaba en lo mas alto, pero éste es más repugnante. Será mejor que busques una bolsa para los mareos si vas a estar mucho tiempo viéndolo.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Este es probablemente el más psicodélico de los salvapantallas. Mogumbo -el autor- pensó que su protector 'Plasma' estaba en lo más alto, pero éste es más repugnante. Será mejor que cojas una bolsa para los mareos si vas a estar mucho tiempo viéndolo.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Esto es tan psicodélico como un protector de pantalla debe ser, mogumbo pensó que su protector Plasma estaba en la cima del mundo, pero éste es aún más nauseabundo. Deberías conseguir una bolsa para mareos antes de quedarte observando por mucho tiempo.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">See on nii psühhedeelne kui üks ekraanisäästja olla saab. mogumbo arvas, et tema Plasma säästja oli tippude tipp, aga see on isegi rohkem iiveldama ajav. Parem otsi endale üks neist lennuki oksekottidest enne kui liiga kauaks seda siin vaatama jääd.</description>
    <description lang="eu_ES">Hau ziurrenik inoiz sortu den pantaila-babesle psikodelikoena da. Mogunbo sortzaileak bere Plasma babeslea garaiena zuela uste zuen baina hau oraindik nazkagarriago da. Ikusten denbora asko egon behar bazara hobe zorabiorako poltsa bat edukitzea.</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">این محافظ تقریبا از نهایت توهم زایی یک محافظ صفحه نمایش برخوردار است. ماگومبو فکر می کرد محافظ پلاسمایی او نهایت کار است، اما این یکی از آن هم تهوع آور تر است. بهتر است قبل از آنکه مدت طولانی به این محافظ خیره شوید یکی از آن پاکت های مخصوص حالت تهوع هواپیماها را تهیه کنید.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tämä on mahdollisesti niin psykedeelinen kuin vain näytönsäästäjä voi olla. mogumbo luuli, että hänen Plasma-näytönäästäjänsä oli asteikon huipulla, mutta tämä ohittaa senkin. Oksennuspussin hakeminen on suositeltavaa ennen pitkäaikaista tuijottamista.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">On fait difficilement plus psychédélique comme économiseur d'écran. mogumbo pensait que son économiseur Plasma était tout en haut de l'échelle mais, celui-ci donne encore plus la nausée. Vous devriez trouver un de ces sacs pour le mal de l'air avant de le fixer trop longtemps.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">En terme d'économiseur, on fait difficilement plus psychédélique. Mogumbo pensait son économiseur Plasma tout en haut de l'échelle mais, celui-ci donne encore plus la nausée. Mieux vaut se munir d'un de ces sachets pour le mal de l'air avant de le regarder trop longtemps.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Este é máis ou menos tan psicodélico como pode selo un protector de pantalla. mogumbo pensou que o seu protector de pantalla Plasma era do mello, pero este é aínda máis mareante. Será mellor que colla unha bolsa contra o mareo antes de quedar pampo mirando para el.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">זהו שומר מסך הכי פסיכדלי שניתן להיות. mogumbo חשב ששומר מסך הפלזמה שלו הגיע לראש הטבלה, אך שומר זה יגרום לתחושת סחרחורת גדולה יותר. מוטב להצטייד במספר שקיות הקאה בטרם בהיה ממושכת.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Psihodeličan koliko čuvar zaslona može biti. Mogumbo kroz svoj plazma čuvar zaslona je bio vrh, ali od ovog vam je još više loše. Bilo bi vam bolje da pronađete jednu od onih vrećica za mučninu što dijele u avionima prije nego počnete zuriti u ovaj.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Ez a legpszihedelikusabb képernyővédő. mogumbo úgy gondolta, hogy a Plasma képernyővédő van a lista tetején,de ez még inkább kábító. Jobb ha keresel egy légibetegség zacskót mielőtt túl sokáig néznéd a képernyőt.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Ini adalah sepsikedelik mungkin dari sebuah screensaver. mogumbo mengira Plasma savernya berada di puncak, Tapi ini bahkan lebih memabukkan. Anda sebaiknya mencari kantung mabuk terlebih dahulu sebelum menatapnya terlalu lama.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Þetta er líklega eins geggjað og skjáhvílur geta orðið. mogumbo hélt að Plasma skjáhvílan væri á toppnum, en þessi gerir þig meira flökurt. Best fyrir þig að redda þér ælupoka áður en þú starir á þetta í einhvern tíma. </description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Questo è quanto di più psichedelico possa essere un salvaschermo. mogumbo pensava che il suo salvaschermo 'Plasma' fosse al massimo della psichedelicità, ma questo è anche più nauseante. Faresti meglio a cercare uno di quei sacchetti per il mal d'aria prima di fissarlo troppo a lungo.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">싸이키델릭한 화면보호기입니다. 거의 토나올 정도의 화면보호기로 오래 쳐다보려면 봉투를 준비하는것이 좋을겁니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Tai stogą nunešanti psichodelinė užsklanda. Mogumbo galvojo, kad jo Plasma užsklandos niekas neperšoks, tačiau ši užsklanda tai kažkas tokio. Geriau susiraskite vieną iš tų lėktuvo maišelių, jei supykintų, prieš spoksant į tai per ilgai..</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Ekrānsaudzētājs nevarētu būt vēl vairāk psihodēlisks. mogumbo domāja, ka viņa "Plasma saver" bija saraksta augšgalā, bet šis ir vēl šķebinošāks. Labāk apsēdies un sameklē kādu maisņu nelabai dūšai pirms skaties šo pārāk ilgi.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">This is about as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo thought his Plasma saver was at the top of the scale, but this one is even more nauseating. You'd better find one of those air sickness bags before you stare at this one for too long.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Ia mengenai as psychedelic as screensavers get. mogumbo berpendapat penyelamat Plasmanya adlaah yang terbaik, tetapi yang ini adalah lebih meloyakan. Oleh itu anda perlu cari beg muntah sebelum anda melihatnya dengan lebih lama.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Dette er så psykadelisk som en skjermsparer kan bli. Mogumbo trodde hans Plasma skjermsparer var på toppen av skalaen, men denne er enda mer kvalmende. Du bør skaffe deg en sånn spypose som de deler ut på fly før du stirrer på denne for lenge.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Ongetwijfeld de meest psychedelische screensaver. mogumbo dacht dat zijn Plasmascreensaver al bovenaan deze lijst stond, maar deze is nóg meer misselijkmakend. Houd uw braakzakje bij de hand, mocht u hier te lang naar staren.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Tak psychodeliczny wygaszacz jak tylko się da. Lepiej zaopatrz się w worki na chorobę lokomocyjną.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Esta é provavelmente a proteção de tela mais psicodélica de todos os tempos. O mogumbo, pensou que a sua proteção de tela  'Plasma' estava no topo da escala de proteções nauseantes mas esta parece ainda pior. Procure um saco de enjoo e sente-se, se vai ficar muito tempo a olhar para a tela.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Provavelmente o protector de ecrã mais psicadélico de sempre. O autor, mogumbo, julgava que a sua proteção 'Plasma' estava no topo da escala, mas este é ainda mais repugnante. É melhor encontrar um desses sacos de enjoo antes de ficar pregado nele durante muito tempo.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Acesta este un protector ecran cât se poate de năucitor. mogumbo credea că screensaverul creat de el, Plasma este pe primul loc, dar acest screensaver este și mai amețitor. Ar trebui să căutați o pungă să nu vi se facă rău înainte de a vă uita la acesta prea mult.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Самая психоделическая в мире заставка. mogumbo считал, что никто не сможет достичь эффекта его заставки Plasma, но от этой заставки укачивает ещё сильнее. Если будете смотреть на эту заставку слишком долго, вам очень скоро понадобится гигиенический пакет.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Tento šetrič je tak psychodelický ako to len ide. Mogumbo myslel, že Plasma šetrič je na vrchole rebríčka, ale tento je ešte viac zvrátený. Radšej si nájdite hygienické vrecko skôr než naň budete civieť pridlho.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Težko bi si zamislili bolj psihadeličen ohranjevalnik zaslona. mogumbo je menil, da je njegov ohranjevalnik Plasma na vrhu, to da ta še bolj vzbuja slabost. Bolje, da najdete eno izmed tistih vrečk za bruhanje, preden predolgo strmite vanj.</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Психоделичан колико то један чувар екрана може да буде. Mogumbo је мислио да је његов Plasma чувар екрана на врху скале, али од овога ће вам бити још лошије. Боље да пронађете једну од оних кесица за мучнину које деле у авионима пре него што почнете да зурите у овај превише дуго.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Detta är ungefär så psykedelisk som en skärmsläckare kan bli. mogumbo trodde att hans Plasma Saver var toppen på skalan, men denna gör dig ännu mer illamående. Det är nog bäst att du letar upp en påse för flygsjuka innan du sätter dig ned och stirrar på denna för länge.</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Дар тамоми ҷаҳон ин пардаи экран аз ҳама беҳтарин буда дар рейтинги пардаҳои экран ҷои якумро бо пардаи плазмаи худ гирифт. Вақте ки истифодаи ин пардаи экранро сар мекунед, аз истифодаи он ҳеҷ гоҳ рад намекунед.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Bu, insanı hayallere sürükleyen bir ekran koruyucudur. mogumbo kendisine ait bu Plazma ekran koruyucunun skalanın en üstünde olduğunu düşünüyor, ancak daha ziyade insanın içini kaldırıyor. Bu ekran koruyucuyu uzun süre seyretmeden önce mide bulantınız için gerekli önlemleri almanız iyi olur.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Сама психоделічна в світі заставка. mogumbo вважав, що ніхто не зможе досягти ефекту його заставки плазми, але від цієї заставки заколисує ще сильніше. Якщо будете дивитися на цю заставку занадто довго, вам дуже скоро знадобиться гігієнічний пакет.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Chú trọng để tạo ra ảo giác mạnh nhất mà trình bảo vệ màn hình có thể có được. Mogumbo từng nghĩ trình bảo vệ Plasma của mình đã đỉnh, nhưng trình này còn kinh khủng hơn. Tốt hơn hết là bạn nên chuẩn bị một túi chống nôn cho mình trước khi bắt đầu nhìn vào nó quá lâu</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">这大概是最具迷幻效果的屏幕保护程序了。mogumbo 以为他的 Plasma 屏保已经是数一数二了，但这个更令人犯晕。如果你要长时间盯视它最好先准备一个晕机袋。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">這大概是最具夢幻效果的屏幕保護程序了。 mogumbo以為他的電漿螢幕保護程式已經是數一數二了，但這個更令人頭昏腦脹。如果你要長時間盯視它最好先準備一個夠用的暈機嘔吐袋。</description>
    <platform>linux osx</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
