<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="visualization.waveform"
  version="1.0.0"
  name="Waveform"
  provider-name="MrC">
  <extension
    point="xbmc.player.musicviz"
    library_linux="Waveform.vis"
    library_windx="Waveform_win32.vis"
    library_osx="Waveform.vis"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Визуализация представяща графика на две осцилиращи вълни на екрана</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Visualización mostrando 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Eine Visualisierung, welche 2 wellenförmige Grafiken auf dem Bildschirm zeigt</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Kaksi aaltomuotograafia</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Visualisation montrant 2 graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vizualizáció két hullámformával</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">두개의 웨이브폼을 보여주는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Visualisatie die twee grafieken in golfvorm weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazująca dwie fale dźwięku</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Visualização que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Vizualizare care arată 2 grafice Waveform pe ecran</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Visualisering som visar 2 vågformsgrafer på skärmen</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">在屏幕上显示两个波形图的可视化效果</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Waveform представя графика на две осцилиращи вълни на екрана, по една за всеки канал (ляв и десен), който реагират на ритъма на музиката.</description>
    <description lang="en">Waveform is a simple Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="es">Waveform es un sencillo visualizador que muestra 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla, uno para cada canal, derecho e izquierdo, que se mueven al ritmo de la música.</description>
    <description lang="de">Waveform  ist eine einfache Visualisierung, welche 2 wellenförmige Grafiken zeigt. Je eine Grafik für den linken und rechten Kanal, welche sich im Takt der Musik bewegen</description>
    <description lang="fi">Waveform on kaksi aaltomuotograafia näyttävä yksinkertainen visualisointi. Toinen on vasemmalle ja toinen oikealle kanavalla ja ne liikkuvat musiikin tahdissa.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Waveform une simple visualisation montrant deux graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran. Une pour chaque voie, gauche et droite, qui bouge en fonction du tempo</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Waveform egy egyszerű vizualizáció, amely 2db hullámot mutat reprezentálva a bal és a jobb hangcsatornákat, melyek a zene ritmusára mozognak.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Waveform은 간단히 두개의 웨이브폼을 화면에 보여줍니다. 각각 왼쪽, 오른쪽 채널이고 음악의 비트에 따라 움직입니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Waveform is een simpele muziekvisualisatie die twee golfvormen op het scherm toont, respectievelijk voor het linker- en rechtergeluidskanaal. De golfvormen bewegen mee met de beat van de muziek.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Waveform jest prostą wizualizacją pokazującą dwie fale dźwiękowe na ekranie. Każda na jeden kanał dźwięku.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O Waveform é um visualizador simples que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes no ecrã, um para cada canal estéreo.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Waveform este o vizualizare simplă care arată 2 grafice Waveform pe ecran, câte unul pentru fiecare canal stâng și drept și care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii</description>
    <description lang="se">Waveform är en enkel visualisering som visar 2 vågformsgrafer på skärmen, en för vänster och en för höger kanal som rör sig i takt med musiken</description>
    <description lang="zh">Waveform是一个简单的可视化效果，它在屏幕上显示两个波形图，分别与音乐左右声道的节拍相呼应。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
