<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.tvshows.themoviedb.org.python"
  name="TMDb TV Shows"
  version="1.6.0"
  provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.tvshows" library="main.py" cachepersistence="00:15"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <news>1.6.0
change to use new JSON based episodeguide format to handle multiple providers
fixes for last minute changes to new Nexus Python bindings
	</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
	<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=357232</forum>
    <website>https://www.themoviedb.org</website>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/metadata.tvshows.themoviedb.org.python</source>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Атрымліваць метаданыя серыялаў з themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Agafa les metadades de les sèries de themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Získat metadata pro seriály z themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Hent metadata til tv-shows fra themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">TV-Show-Metadaten von themoviedb.org abrufen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Fetch TV Show metadata from themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Obtener metadatos de Serie de TV de themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Obtener metadatos de series de themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Hangi seriaali metaandmed allikast themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">The Movie Database (TMDB) -tietolähde televisiosarjoille</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Récupérer les métadonnées d&apos;une série depuis themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Ambil metadata Acara TV dari themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Sækja lýsigögn sjónvarpsþátta frá themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Recupera i metadati dei programmi TV da themovedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">themoviedb.org에서 TV쇼 메타데이터를 가져옵니다</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Haal metadata van tv-programma&apos;s op van themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Pobieraj metadane programów telewizyjnch z themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Obter metadados de Séries em themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Получение метаданных о сериалах с сайта themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Hämta metadata för TV-serier från themoviedb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">TV Programları meta verilerini themoviedb.org sitesinden al</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">从 themoviedb.org 获取剧集信息</summary>
    <description lang="be_BY">The Movie Database (TMDb) - база даных фільмаў і серыялаў, створаная супольнасцю. Усе даныя дадавалі ўдзельнікі гэтай цудоўнай супольнасці, пачынаючы з 2008. Шматнацыянасць і разнастайнасць даных - тое, чым мы вельмі ганарымся. Калі сказаць прасцей, то мы жывем супольнасцю, і гэта адрознівае нас ад іншых.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">The Movie Database (TMDb) és una base de dades de pel·lícules i sèries creada per la comunitat. Cada dada ha estat afegida per la nostra increïble comunitat que data de 2008. El fort enfoc internacional i la quantitat de dades de TMDb és en gran mesura inigualable i una cosa de la qual estem increïblement orgullosos. En poques paraules, vivim i respirem comunitat i això és precisament el que ens fa diferents.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">The Movie Database (TMDb) je komunitní databáze filmů a seriálů. Každý kousek dat byl přidán naší úžasnou komunitou sahající až do roku 2008. Silné mezinárodní zaměření a rozsah dat TMDb jsou do značné míry bezkonkurenční a jsme na ně nesmírně hrdí. Jednoduše řečeno, žijeme a dýcháme komunitou, a to je přesně to, co nás odlišuje.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">The Movie Database (TMDb) er en community-bygget film- og tv-database. Hvert stykke data er blevet tilføjet af vores fantastiske community, der går tilbage til 2008. TMDbs stærke internationale fokus og bredde af data er stort set uovertruffen, og noget vi er utroligt stolte af. Enkelt sagt, vi lever og ånder community, og det er netop det, der gør os forskellige.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">The Movie Database (TMDb) ist eine Film- und TV-Datenbank. Seit 2008 wurde jeder einzelne Datensatz von einer tollen Community beigesteuert. TMDb&apos;s starker internationaler Fokus und die Vielfalt der Daten ist weitgehend unübertroffen. Die Betreiber von TMDb sind darauf sehr stolz. Vereinfacht gesagt, lebt und atmet TMDb den Community-Gedanken und das genau macht den Unterschied.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">The Movie Database (TMDb) is a community built movie and TV database. Every piece of data has been added by our amazing community dating back to 2008. TMDb&apos;s strong international focus and breadth of data is largely unmatched and something we&apos;re incredibly proud of. Put simply, we live and breathe community and that&apos;s precisely what makes us different.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">The Movie Database (TMDb) es una base de datos contruida comunitariamente sobre películas y TV. Cada pedazo de información ha sido añadida por nuestra increible comunidad desde 2008. El sólido enfoque internacional y la amplitud de datos de TMDb son en gran medida incomparables y es algo de lo que estamos increíblemente orgullosos. En pocas palabras, vivimos y respiramos en comunidad y eso es precisamente lo que nos hace diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">The Movie Database (TMDb) es una base de datos de películas y series creada por la comunidad. Cada pedazo de información ha sido agregada por nuestra increíble comunidad desde 2008. El fuerte enfoque internacional de TMDb y la variedad de información son en gran medida incomparables y algo de lo que estamos increíblemente orgullosos. En pocas palabras, vivimos y respiramos comunidad y eso es precisamente lo que nos hace diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">The Movie Database (TMDb) on kogukonna loodud filmide ja sarjade andmebaas. Meie imeline kogukond on lisanud kõik need andmed alates aastast 2008. TMDb tugev rahvusvaheline fookus ja andmete laius on suures osas võrreldamatud ja selle üle oleme ääretult uhked. Lihtsamalt öeldes elame ja hingame kogukonnas ning just see teebki meid erinevaks.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">The Movie Database (TMDB) on yhteisön ylläpitämä, ilmainen ja avoin tietokanta elokuville ja televisiosarjoille. Palvelulla on miljoonia kuukausittaisia käyttäjiä ja sen tehokkaan rajapinnan avulla Kodi ja monet muut mediasovellukset voivat hyödyntää palvelun metatietoja ja mediakuvituksia käyttökokemuksen parantamiseen. Tietokannan vahva painotus kansaivälisyyteen ja kattava tietomäärä on suurelta osin ylivertainen ja olemme tästä erittäin ylpeitä. Yksinkertaisesti sanoen, elämme ja hengitämme yhteisönä ja juuri se tekee meistä erilaisia.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">La base de données The Movie Database (TMDb) est un projet communautaire visant à référencer les informations de films et séries télé. Chaque information a été ajoutée par notre incroyable communauté, et ce depuis 2008. La force internationale du projet TMBd, ainsi que la diversité et l&apos;étendue de ces données l&apos;ont rendu leader dans ce domaine et nous en sommes extrêmement fière. Décrit simplement, nous vivons et respirons communauté et c&apos;est précisément ce qui nous rend différent.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">The Movie Database (TMDb) adalah database film dan TV yang dibangun oleh komunitas. Setiap bagian data telah ditambahkan oleh komunitas kami yang luar biasa sejak tahun 2008. Fokus internasional TMDb yang kuat dan luasnya data sebagian besar tak tertandingi dan sesuatu yang sangat kami banggakan. Sederhananya, kita hidup dan bernafas dalam komunitas dan justru itulah yang membuat kita berbeda.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">The Movie Database (TMDb) er samfélagslegur gagnagrunnur kvikmynda- og sjónvarpsefnis. Hver einasti gagnabútur hefur verið settur inn af frábærum liðsmönnum okkar allar götur síðan 2008. Mikil alþjóðleg áhersla TMDb ásamt breiðu sviði gagna sést óvíða og er eitthvað sem við erum ótrúlega stolt af. Sett fram á einfaldan máta, við lifum og hrærumst í þessu samfélagi og það er nákvæmlega þess vegna sem við erum öðruvísi.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Il Movie Database (TMDb) è un database di film e TV creato dalla comunità. Ogni dato è stato aggiunto dalla nostra straordinaria comunità che risale al 2008. La forte attenzione internazionale e l&apos;ampiezza dei dati di TMDb sono in gran parte impareggiabili e qualcosa di cui siamo incredibilmente orgogliosi. In parole povere, viviamo e respiriamo in comunità ed è proprio questo che ci rende diversi.</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">The Movie Database (TMDb)는 영화와 TV 데이터베이스를 구축한 커뮤니티입니다. 모든 자료들은 우리 놀라운 커뮤니티에서 2008년부터 추가돼 온 것들입니다. TMDb의 강력한 국제적 초점과 광범위한 데이터는 타의 추종을 불허하며 우리가 자랑스러워하는 점입니다. 간단히 말해, 우리는 커뮤니티와 살고 호흡하며 그것이 우리가 다른 점입니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">De Movie Database (TMDb) is een door de gemeenschap gebouwde film- en tv-database. Elk stukje data is toegevoegd door onze geweldige community die teruggaat tot 2008. TMDb&apos;s sterke internationale focus en brede waaier aan data is grotendeels ongeëvenaard en iets waar we ongelooflijk trots op zijn. Simpel gezegd, we leven en ademen gemeenschap en dat is precies wat ons anders maakt.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">The Movie Database (TMDb) to baza filmów i programów telewizyjnych zbudowana przez społeczność. Każdy element danych został dodany przez naszą niesamowitą społeczność od 2008 roku. Silna międzynarodowa koncentracja TMDb i zakres danych są w dużej mierze niezrównane i jesteśmy z tego niesamowicie dumni. Mówiąc prościej, żyjemy i oddychamy wspólnotą i właśnie to nas wyróżnia.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">The Movie Database (TMDb) é um banco de dados de filmes e séries criado pela comunidade. Cada um dos pedaços de dados foram adicionados por nossa incrível comunidade desde 2008. O forte foco internacional e a amplitude de dados do TMDb são incomparáveis, algo do qual temos muito orgulho. Resumindo, vivemos e respiramos comunidade e é precisamente isso que nos torna diferentes.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">The Movie Database (TMDb) - это база данных фильмов и сериалов, созданная сообществом. Все данные были добавлены нашим замечательным сообществом, начиная с 2008 года. Международная направленность и широта данных TMDb во многом не имеют себе равных, и это то, чем мы невероятно гордимся. Проще говоря, мы живём и дышим сообществом, и именно это отличает нас от других.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">The Movie Database (TMDb) är en communitybyggd film- och TV-databas. All data har lagts till av våra fantastiska medlemmar ända sen 2008. TMDbs starka internationella fokus och bredd är i stort sett oöverträffad och något vi är väldigt stolta över. Communityn är hjärtat i det hela och det är det som skiljer oss från mängden.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">The Movie Database (TMDb), topluluk tarafından oluşturulmuş bir film ve TV veritabanıdır. Her bir veri parçası, 2008 yılına dayanan muhteşem topluluğumuz tarafından eklenmiştir. TMDb&apos;nin güçlü uluslararası odağı ve veri genişliği büyük ölçüde benzersizdir ve inanılmaz derecede gurur duyduğumuz bir şeydir. Basitçe söylemek gerekirse, topluluk içinde yaşıyor ve nefes alıyoruz ve bizi farklı kılan da tam olarak bu.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">TMDb 是一个由网络社区创建的影视数据库。每一条数据都是由我们令人惊叹的社区添加的，可以追溯到2008年。TMDb 强大的国际关注度和数据广度在很大程度上是无与伦比的，我们对此感到无比自豪。简单地说，我们生活在社区中，呼吸着社区的气息，这正是我们与众不同的原因。</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

